<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Booster Meeting on Monday and Membership</title>
  <description>Hi Everyone,
 
Band Booster Meeting
Our next Band Booster Meeting is this Monday, September 29 at 7:</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Band Booster Meeting&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our next Band Booster Meeting is this &lt;b&gt;Monday, September 29 at 7:00 P.M. in the NRHS Community Room&lt;/b&gt; located in the front of the high school. We look forward to seeing you there! &lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Membership&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although becoming a Band Booster Member is always welcome at any time during the year, we are nearing the end of our Membership drive. Currently, our numbers are about 10% lower than last year. Perhaps this is because of our website transition, or simply because it has slipped your mind.  Realizing that this organization directly benefits our kids and enhances their experience in the high school band program, we strongly feel it is important that all parents support the band boosters.  Please consider becoming a member. To do so, complete the &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/band-booster-membership"&gt;membership form&lt;/a&gt;, fill it out and have your student place it in the white box in the band room. (Please mark your envelope “Band Booster Membership.”)  Another option would be to attend our booster meeting on Monday, September 29. Spirit wear and membership will be displayed and available to all interested.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Spirit Wear Sale&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the Booster meeting select spirit wear from our inventory will be on sale.  Please note most sale merchandise is black-colored and sizes are limited.  If you have any questions, please contact Shirley at &lt;a href="mailto:saberish@hotmail.com"&gt;saberish@hotmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thank goodness for a relatively calm week for everyone!  See you Friday at the game!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;br&gt;
Band Booster President&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-09-27 07:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-09-27 07:59:00</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>booster-meeting-on-monday-and-membership</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>