<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Concert Uniform Turn In Info and Used Tux Sale</title>
  <description>Dear Band Families,
 
It is the end of the year and time for concert uniforms to be turned in!
 
Tur</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;It is the end of the year and time for concert uniforms to be turned in!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Turn-in will be in the new uniform room, room 310 on:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuesday, May 19, 6:30-8:00pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thursday, May 21, 6:30-8:00pm&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;SENIORS – YOU MUST RETURN YOUR UNIFORM ON TUESDAY, MAY 19. &lt;/b&gt;Concert tuxes and dresses are school property. Mr. Vitale cannot sign your exit card unless you turn in your tux or dress Tuesday, May 19. If you cannot return your tux or dress yourself, get a trusted friend or relative to turn it in for you.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;BOYS - IF YOU ARE IN WIND ENSEMBLE OR SYMPHONIC BAND YOU MUST TAKE YOUR TUX TO ON THE SPOT DRY CLEANERS TO BE DRY CLEANED.&lt;/b&gt; If you are in Concert or Freshman Band you do not need to dry clean your tux. All boys - please be sure to return your tie, cummerbund and suit bag as well as your tux!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;GIRLS - &lt;/b&gt;Please wash your dress in cold water and line dry. Do not iron! Please return on a hanger.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Used Tux Sale:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will also be selling our old tuxes during uniform turn in. Our gentlemen are in need of new cummerbunds and bow ties for next concert season. This sale will help offset the cost. If you know a family member or a friend in need of a tux, pass along the dates and times so they can purchase theirs as well! The prices are reasonable!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jackets - $20&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pants - $10&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will accept cash only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please contact Stacy at 440-263-1855 or Tracey at 216-533-9710 with any questions.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;br&gt;Stacy and Tracey&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-05-11 20:05:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-05-11 20:55:46</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>concert-uniform-turn-in-info-and-used-tux-sale</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>