<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Thanks for a Great Band Fest and More</title>
  <description>Hi Everyone! 
&amp;nbsp;What a great night for a Festival of Bands!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We couldn't have had a be</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What a great night for a Festival of Bands! We couldn't have had a better evening for this event! Hosting in September seems to really be a good thing...September historically is a beautiful and relatively dry month...but we do live in the unpredictable northeast Ohio area! Thank goodness we dodged a rainy bullet last night! That truly could make or break an event like this!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for all the hard work of all our volunteers! Especially Rich and Monica Hrin, and Chris and Beth Burdick for organizing this event! It is turning out to be a great fundraiser for us! This was our 3rd year for this event and there were many compliments and thank you's for hosting this festival. Concessions and ticket sales worked particularly hard feeding the crowd and bands and selling tickets to nearly 1400 people as well as selling programs! 50/50 deserves a big shout out for not only selling tickets but helping with crowd control and any seating concerns. We had several ushers navigating the guests to their seats to avoid congestion and the Pit Crew parked all the buses in the high school staff lot! A great effort was made by all! It looks like this event is becoming quite popular and we will&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;definitely&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;need more help next year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although I did not get to see any bands, except our own, the comments I heard were that it was a very entertaining show! Mr. Vitale's talents and efforts once again proved to be exceptional last night! What a complicated and amazing show and our kids performed their hearts out! It gives me goose bumps to see 280 kids working together to sell this performance to the audience. I can't wait to see what it looks like when they perform at State Competition!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking forward...&lt;/strong&gt;next week is Homecoming and our first contest is October 4th&amp;nbsp;at Perkins High School in Sandusky. Purchase your spirit wear and booster membership apparel so that we can show our support in the stands if you haven't done so already! Membership and spirit wear will be available at our next booster meeting, Sept. 29. You can also download a form from our website,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandboosters.com/" target="_blank"&gt;northroyaltonbandboosters.com&lt;/a&gt;, and have your student put it in the white band box (mark your envelope ‘Booster Membership’). Additionally, we have only 5 "bling" items left. Get yours before they are sold out! Please contact Shirley at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="mailto:saberish@hotmail.com" target="_blank"&gt;saberish@hotmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="tel:440-717-1532" value="+14407171532" target="_blank"&gt;440-717-1532&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;with any questions regarding spirit wear or membership.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks again for all the hard work of our parent volunteers! Your efforts DID NOT go unnoticed! We truly are fortunate to be a part of such a great organization!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-09-21 15:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-09-22 15:41:00</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>thanks-for-a-great-band-fest-and-more</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>