<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>NRMB Newsletter – September 26, 2016</title>
  <description>Our first CONTEST is Saturday, October 1st, at Maumee High School. Check Mr. Vitale’s website and lo</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Our first CONTEST is Saturday, October 1st, at Maumee High School. Check Mr. Vitale’s website and look under ‘Performances’ for all the details! Hope to see you there to support our Marching Band!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cleveland.com is running a Best High School Marching Band of Greater Cleveland contest, and North Royalton has been chosen as one of the finalists! Voting goes through Wednesday to determine which bands continue to the next round.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We know we are the best so &lt;a href="http://www.cleveland.com/best/2016/09/its_time_to_vote_for_greater_c.html"&gt;follow this link and vote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LINKS you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Mr. Vitale’s Website:&lt;/a&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;     
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandboosters.com"&gt;Band Booster’s Website:&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/North-Royalton-Band-Boosters/164850233634290"&gt;FaceBook North Royalton Band Boosters -- Like Us!!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other Fundraisers: GFS and Smile.Amazon.com (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;DATES you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SEPT 26 – BAND BOOSTER MEETING – MEDIA CENTER 7PM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 30 – Football game – AWAY Wadsworth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 30 – Car Raffle Tickets are DUE in white band box.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 1 – CONTEST – Maumee High School&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 7 – SENIOR BAND NIGHT -- see below!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oct 7 – Football game – HOME Brecksville/Broadview Hts --- HOMECOMING!&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;North Royalton Stadium Foundation Car Raffle&lt;/h3&gt;
 &lt;p&gt;Marching Band sales have until SEPTEMBER 30th to sell raffle tickets!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please return your sold ticket stubs and money to the white band box by Friday, September 30th. If you have not sold them by then, return them in the original ticket envelope. The $20.00 cost of any tickets not returned will be charged to you.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Please email or text me if you need additional tickets or have questions. Jane Coleman mattnjane.coleman@att.net 440-759-9864 Thank You!&lt;/p&gt;
 
 
&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sale --- Keep Selling Fruit! We would love to sell a TRUCKload&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Marching Band Fruit Sale is officially underway If you need extra forms, they are in the band room. Forms are due back to the White Band box by October 15th!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Senior Band Night&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Senior Band night is OCTOBER 7. All seniors should have received their invitation. Please remember to send back your RSVP to Helen Kelly. Also, check Mr. Vitale’s site for your Senior Band Night Information sheet under ‘Forms’.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions, please contact Helen Kelly: alandhelenkelly@cox.net&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Membership&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our membership drive is underway! JOIN the Band Boosters! There are many membership levels! Print the form at the bottom of this newsletter OR go to www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com and select the Membership button to get the form! Questions?&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Contest Hoodies: Hoodies will NOT be available on Wednesday due to a printing delay. We are hopeful that the hoodies will be in and available by OCT 1st!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Contact: Shirley Berish – 440-667-0811&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;50/50 Raffle - We Still Need Help&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our nest home game is SENIOR BAND night and our senior parent volunteers will be enjoying dinner with their bando. Please consider filling the gap and helping us out!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We can use help with our next two home games! Please &lt;a href="http://www.SignUpGenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-5050"&gt;click on this link&lt;/a&gt; or contact: Elisa Race -- 216-407-5625&lt;/p&gt;
 

 
&lt;h3&gt;Other Fundraisers:&lt;/h3&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;GFS: If you shop at GFS, remember to mention : North Royalton Band Boosters and Marching Band at checkout. We have an account there and accumulate $$$$ for everything YOU spend!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Smile.Amazon Are you an Amazon shopper? Set up a SMILE.AMAZON account and a percentage of what you purchase will be added to the North Royalton Band Booster account:&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;YOU can help North Royalton High School Band Boosters when you shop for back-to-school supplies and many other items that you purchase from Amazon! This link will help you set up your SMILE account!.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Support us when you shop for back-to-school items. #StartWithaSmile at &lt;a href="https://smile.amazon.com/gp/r.html?C=3POFUA774BDCO&amp;amp;R=20U6TRGLZLFEA&amp;amp;T=C&amp;amp;U=http%3A%2F%2Fsmile.amazon.com%2Fch%2F34-1817202%3Fref_%3Dpe_732550_202916120&amp;amp;A=XIHW9ORMLERAKV041SF6OWULFVKA&amp;amp;H=AKVNUC0SMEMMU85TCZJJDWMEREWA&amp;amp;ref_=pe_732550_202916120"&gt;http://smile.amazon.com/ch/34-1817202&lt;/a&gt; and Amazon donates.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-09-27 11:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-09-27 11:45:36</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>nrmb-newsletter-september-26-2016</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>