<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>NRHS Band Program Newsletter – MAY 1, 2017</title>
  <description>CONGRATS to all our Concert Bands for amazing performances this weekend! We are very proud of all of</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;CONGRATS to all our Concert Bands for amazing performances this weekend! We are very proud of all of you!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;A very BIG THANK YOU to ALL of the volunteers that made the State OMEA contest and Easter Seals Fill the Truck HUGE successes! We could not have done it without YOU!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LINKS you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Mr. Vitale’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandboosters.com"&gt;Band Booster’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/North-Royalton-Band-Boosters/164850233634290"&gt;FaceBook North Royalton Band Boosters -- Like Us!!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;FINAL DATES for the season that you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May 6 – Basket Raffle – 3Spot – Tickets still available! See Below!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May 10 – Band Awards Banquet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May 22 – Band Booster Meeting in the Media Center at 7PM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May 24 – Band-A-Rama – 7PM in Gym 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May 29 – Memorial Day Parade&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;May is a very busy month to end the season. Please Check Mr. Vitale’s website regularly for all the details.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;MAY 6 – Basket Raffle&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our annual Basket Raffle event will be MAY 6th and 3Spot in North Royalton. The 3Spot will be giving us the MAIN DINING room for our event this year! If you are interested in attending, please email BECKY HUMES at bandghumes@sbcglobal.net to make your reservation. You can pay at the door!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We still need a few folks to help us out that evening. If you can help us, &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080c4da5ae23a6fc1-nrbb"&gt;please sign up here&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
 

 
&lt;h3&gt;MAY 10 – Band Awards Banquet&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;REMINDER: We are on the homestretch to the end of the school year and the Band Awards Banquet is fast approaching. &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/FILES%2f2017%2f05%2f2017BandAwardsDinnerInvitation-rev.pdf.axdx"&gt;Attached is the invitation and RSVP form&lt;/a&gt;. (The RSVP is the second page of the document.) RSVP’s are due back on May 1.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;A check is needed to pay for everyone attending who is not a Senior Band Student. The cost is $11 per person. Seniors band members are free. Please put the RSVP and payment in an envelope and mark it, “Awards Banquet Night” and have your student drop it off in the white band box.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even if you do not attend the dinner, everyone is welcome and encouraged to attend the Band Awards program which starts at 7:00pm. It is a great way to spend an enjoyable evening with family and friends.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-05-01 11:05:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-05-01 11:41:17</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>nrhs-band-program-newsletter-may-1-2017</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>