<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>OMEA State Contest Volunteers Needed</title>
  <description>Band families,
 
Preparations are underway for the OMEA Northeast Region State Band Adjudicated Even</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Band families,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Preparations are underway for the OMEA Northeast Region State Band Adjudicated Event - held right here at North Royalton High School. We are very excited that we are the only band program to have four concert bands participating at the state level for this region, and we are also excited that we are able to host this event right here at our own home school. (Schedules and itineraries can be found on the Band Website.)&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;However, there is a great deal of responsibility entrusted to us for hosting this event. We have each of the students volunteering to help with volunteer shifts, but there are certain shifts that can only be held by adults.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We are asking for a few more adult volunteers to please help us out the weekend of April 28 and 29. We have minimized the number of adult shifts required based on absolute need.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;If you can volunteer even a few hours - it would be greatly appreciated - and the jobs are not difficult. Jobs range from making sure doors remained closed during a performance, to making sure the sightreading areas are closed to the public.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;If you can volunteer just a few hours - &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054eafa729a02-omea1"&gt;please click the enclosed link to our page on Sign-Up-Genius&lt;/a&gt; – and anything you can contribute is appreciated. We would not be able to host this event without the support of the Band Boosters and volunteers like you!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;-Mr. Vitale&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-04-18 21:04:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-04-18 21:52:59</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>omea-state-contest-volunteers-needed</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>fa6094d0-c8e0-4964-8deb-b6349a6dd281</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>