<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Booster Newsletter 8/16</title>
  <description>Hi Everyone,
It's hard to believe we get to see the 2014 North Royalton High School Marching Band pe</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's hard to believe we get to see the 2014 North Royalton High School Marching Band perform on Sunday at 7 pm! Everyone has been working hard to make this another great season! Please be sure you are checking the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandbooster.com/" target="_blank"&gt;northroyaltonbandbooster.com&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;website regularly for the most current information. The Directors Page should be a tab that is always open on your computer, tablet or phone during marching band season.&lt;/p&gt;[more]
&lt;h3&gt;Band Booster Membership&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many opportunities exist for band and front line parents to become members!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;There are several levels in which to participate.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;There are new items available in each package.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Look for the Band Booster Membership tables at the stadium&amp;nbsp;on Sunday, our 1st Band Booster meeting&amp;nbsp;on Monday, the Freshman/New Member meeting also on Monday, and at the tailgate party on Friday, Sept 5&amp;nbsp;at The 3 Spot. &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/band-booster-membership"&gt;The form is also available for you to print from our website&lt;/a&gt;. There will be a packet sent home with membership forms in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Band Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Band button pictures were taken on picture day and are a fundraiser. Parents purchase buttons sporting their students’ pictures and wear them to our band events. They are worn with pride! Buttons will be available for purchase starting at&amp;nbsp;6:00pm&amp;nbsp;before the Band’s performance on Parent Preview Night.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At this event, you may look at the picture and pay for the button. &lt;strong&gt;The cost is $4.00 each&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;Buttons purchased at Parent Preview Night will be available for pick-up at the first home game. You may continue to purchase buttons throughout the season at booster meetings or at the first home games. Just look for the table.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Air Show Update - Urgent Message!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although we have gotten 26 more people to fill the spots for the Cleveland Airshow we are still far short of the amount needed to meet our requirements.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We have had only 70 families out of over 270 families volunteer at this time.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;It is very important that we do our part. &lt;strong&gt;If these spots are not filled, we will lose $35 per spot&lt;/strong&gt; and we (the boosters) will still have to find people to fill these spots. If everyone gives up a little, no one will have to do a lot.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Please consider adding us to your Labor Day weekend plans to help with this fundraiser! Below is the most current information on the upcoming event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Air Show details&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;August 30, 31 and&amp;nbsp;Sept. 1&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We need more help at the Cleveland Airshow!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We must fill 40 more spots on Sunday, August 31, and 50 more spots on Monday, September 1. &lt;/strong&gt;This is one of our largest fundraisers and we need to fill these spots to make the $10,000 this year and to keep the fundraiser for next year. Please make time in your schedule to fill these spots. Volunteers must be at least 15 years old or be an incoming freshman.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Volunteers may be other family members or friends!&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you can help, please contact Kathy Pishnery at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="tel:440-503-5457" value="+14405035457"&gt;440-503-5457&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:kathypish@aol.com"&gt;kathypish@aol.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you&amp;nbsp;Sunday!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Holly&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-08-17 08:08:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-08-17 08:11:49</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-booster-newsletter-8-16</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>a70d94a8-5d3c-44aa-b4d6-29cb41d521c4</category>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>