<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Newsletter - Booster Meeting, Air Show, Easter Seals, Band Fest and More!</title>
  <description>Hi everyone!

    Well, the first football game is in the books! And as always, the band did not dis</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Well, the first football game is in the books! And as always, the band did not disappoint! I heard so many positive comments from the people on the North Ridgeville side during the performance. I wanted to let you know that I reached out to the North Ridgeville Band Boosters to thank them for all the great food they gave ours Bandos at the game on Friday! Both my children came home talking about the way they were treated by the North Ridgeville band and parents. That was Sportsmanship at its best! It was so nice to see so many band parents in the stands last week! Congratulations to the freshman on their first successful marching experience with the awesome NRHS Marching Band! Next week's game is away against Parma at Byer's field.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Band Booster Meeting -&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our first Band Booster Meeting takes place TOMORROW, &lt;b&gt;Monday, August 31 &lt;/b&gt;in the High School Community Room located in the front of the high school. The &lt;b&gt;meeting starts at 7 PM&lt;/b&gt;. Please come join us! We will have membership, sportswear, button sales as well as many fundraising event updates. Get involved, and join the fun! We would love to see you! Mr. Vitale will stop by at the end of the meeting to give his update on what's happening with the band.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Air Show Update -&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The airshow is THIS WEEKEND! Thank you to everyone who volunteered and to Becky Cozzens, Becky Humes and Heidi Eisaman for all of your efforts putting this event together! VOLUNTEERS – PICK UP YOUR INFORMATION AND PARKING PASSES before or after the Band Booster Meeting on &lt;b&gt;Monday or on Wednesday at 5:30pm&lt;/b&gt; before the evening rehearsal.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Easter Seals -&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This event was such a success that we have decided to add another date. &lt;b&gt;Saturday, September 19 from 9 AM until 9 PM&lt;/b&gt; is the next collection. We will be sending another sign up genius with opportunities for you to help with this event Check out the most recent issue of The Post for a very nice article about our band and their involvement in this event.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Band Festival -&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our Band Festival, also scheduled for &lt;b&gt;Saturday, September 19, at 7 PM&lt;/b&gt; is a very important event for the booster organization. Please read your emails in order to stay up to date on volunteer needs.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Munching for Music -&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our next event takes place at Sweet Cece's this &lt;b&gt;Wednesday September 2&lt;/b&gt;. Just visit Sweet CeCe's on the corner of Broadview and 82, show them our flyer (printed or on your phone) and they will donate 20% of your purchase back to the band. Our last event earned us over $300! The students have an early release day scheduled, so perhaps buying some ice cream after a hot day at school would be a great treat that would also help out the band!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Florida Trip –&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The deadline is fast approaching! &lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com/"&gt; please check mr. vitale’s website&lt;/a&gt; for details!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you at the game on Friday!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-08-31 11:08:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-08-31 11:46:57</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>newsletter-booster-meeting-air-show-easter-seals-band-fest-and-more</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>