<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Thank You for a Successful Fruit Sale</title>
  <description>Hello, Band Families.
 
We hope all of you had a great break with your families! There are a few of </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello, Band Families.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We hope all of you had a great break with your families! There are a few of you that deserve a big THANK YOU from us. If you proofread and sent out countless emails for us, read emails from us or had lengthy discussions about emails with us, we thank you! If you revised all of the fruit sale information for us to use this year, helped sign out fruit blitz packets, drove your kids to sell during the blitz weekend, actually sold during the blitz weekend, helped with pizza the Monday after the blitz weekend, turned in a packet from the blitz weekend or helped us get packets back from the blitz weekend, we thank you! If you bought fruit, sold fruit, told others about the fruit or made announcements about the fruit, we thank you! If you unloaded fruit from the truck, stacked boxes, took inventory, bagged fruit, copied fruit tags, moved boxes around or pre-picked orders, we thank you! If you pulled orders on pick-up day, helped families get their orders to their cars, rode on the dollies, pushed someone else on a dolly, fixed problems, hauled boxes of fruit around, drove around delivering miscellaneous orders, made phone calls, enjoyed hot chocolate and doughnuts, we thank you! If you picked up your order on one of the pick-up days, delivered customers' fruit in a timely manner, drove your kids around to deliver, thanked people for supporting the band, gave fruit as gifts (personal or business), kept fruit for yourself and your family, ate fruit or wished you had more fruit, we thank you! Basically, if you helped or offered to help us in any way, including listening to us talk about and push the fruit sale for a few months, we thank you! Hopefully we've remembered to include everything that each of you did. The success of this sale would not have been possible without all of you helping! &lt;b&gt;We made over $9,000 for the band! Thank you so much!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We also want to thank Lake Erie Graphics for printing up all of our color fruit sheets and order forms! We truly appreciate this generous donation to our band! The business is located in Brook Park and the phone number is 216-265-7575. Please consider using &lt;a href="http://www.lakeeriegraphics.com/" style=""&gt;Lake Erie Graphics&lt;/a&gt; for any printing needs you have in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Karen and Susie&lt;br&gt;Fruit Sale Committee Chairs&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-01-16 07:01:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-01-16 08:00:23</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>thank-you-for-a-successful-fruit-sale</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>