<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Front Registration 2018</title>
  <description>Hello Band Front Families,
It is time to register for the 2018-2019 band season. Band Front Registra</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Band Front Families,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is time to register for the 2018-2019 band season. Band Front Registration will be taking place on-line over the next few days. &lt;strong&gt;The deadline is June 11. &lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;All fees and information are needed at this time. &lt;strong&gt;All payments are made though PayPal only&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To complete the process you must submit 2 forms (Band Front Registration Form and Volunteer Form). &lt;em&gt;Once you have completed your registration you will receive three emails:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; One&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; from PayPal with your payment information; and two from Band Boosters (one with your Band Front information and one with your Volunteer information).&lt;/em&gt; We recommend saving these emails as they are your receipt for your registration and you may wish to refer to them later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Band Front Registration Form&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/band-front-registration"&gt;http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/band-front-registration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On this form, you will be filling out parent and student information and paying the band front, course and activities fees. After filling out the form click Submit and you will be taken to PayPal to pay your fees and complete this portion of the registration process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Volunteer Form&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/volunteer-form"&gt;http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/volunteer-form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We ask each family to support their student and the band by signing up for at least four activities. One of the reasons we have a great band is the high level of parent and family support and involvement. The majority of the funds needed to support the band (uniforms, flags, etc.) come from these fundraisers. Note that we will close individual activities once we have enough volunteers, so sooner is better than later if you prefer specific activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When you finish the Volunteer Form you will be taken to the Band Registration Form. Do NOT fill out the Band Registration Form. You are done registering, just close the browser window. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or problems, please don’t hesitate to ask!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2018-05-25 07:05:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2018-05-25 07:34:06</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-front-registration-2018</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>