<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>NRMB Newsletter – September 12, 2016</title>
  <description>Thank you to all the Bandos that participated in the FRUIT BLITZ this weekend. The weather cooperate</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Thank you to all the Bandos that participated in the FRUIT BLITZ this weekend. The weather cooperated both days! Enjoy your Pizza Party as a Thank You for your efforts!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LINKS you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Mr. Vitale’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandboosters.com"&gt;Band Booster’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/North-Royalton-Band-Boosters/164850233634290"&gt;FaceBook North Royalton Band Boosters -- Like Us!!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other Fundraisers: GFS and Smile.Amazon.com (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;DATES you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sept 16&lt;/b&gt; – Football game HOME&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sept 17&lt;/b&gt; – Festival of Bands (see Mr. Vitale’s site for report times)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sept 23&lt;/b&gt; – Football game – AWAY Hudson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEPT 26&lt;/b&gt; – BAND BOOSTER MEETING – MEDIA CENTER 7PM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sept 30&lt;/b&gt; – Football game – AWAY Wadsworth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sept 30&lt;/b&gt; – Car Raffle Tickets are DUE in white band box.&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Festival of Bands - Volunteers Needed&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are still in need of MANY volunteers for this event. Please signup below and help make this fundraiser a HUGE success!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;North Royalton Band Festival is a great opportunity for our band and community to shine! This will be the first performance of the North Royalton High School Marching Band 2016 Contest Show: The Elements! We will host bands from around Northeast Ohio as they showcase their talent. Many hands are needed for an enjoyable evening of music and marching. Volunteer opportunities are easy and fun! Please sign-up to assist with one of our final fundraisers of the season. All volunteer duties will pause while NRHS performs so no one will miss the show! &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080948a9ac2aa75-nrhs"&gt;To volunteer, click on this link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;North Royalton Stadium Foundation Car Raffle&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a reminder that your car raffle tickets must be turned into the White Band Box NO LATER than September 30th. Tickets are to be returned whether they are sold or unsold!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Contact: Jane Coleman – 440-759-9864&lt;/p&gt;
 
 
&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sale&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Marching Band Fruit Sale is officially underway. Your bando will receive their PERSONAL packet to sell fruit to family and friends. Forms are due back to the White Band box by October 15th!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Membership&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our membership drive is underway! JOIN the Band Boosters! There are many membership levels! Go to the &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/band-booster-membership"&gt;Membership page&lt;/a&gt; to get the form! Questions?&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Contact: Shirley Berish – 440-667-0811&lt;/p&gt;
 
 
&lt;h3&gt;50/50 Raffle: We Still Need Help&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did you hear how large our payout was on Sept 2? Larger than the first game and it is all due to you--- our volunteers! Let’s keep the payout growing!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We can use help with our next home game and Band Fest! &lt;a href="http://www.SignUpGenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-5050"&gt;Please click on this &lt;/a&gt;link or call Elisa. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact: Elisa Race -- 216-407-5625&lt;/p&gt;
 
 &lt;h3&gt;Other Fundraisers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GFS: If you shop at GFS, remember to mention : North Royalton Band Boosters and Marching Band at checkout. We have an account there and accumulate $$$$ for everything YOU spend!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Smile.Amazon&lt;/b&gt; Are you an Amazon shopper? Set up a SMILE.AMAZON account and a percentage of what you purchase will be added to the North Royalton Band Booster account:&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;YOU can help North Royalton High School Band Boosters when you shop for back-to-school supplies and many other items that you purchase from Amazon! This link will help you set up your SMILE account!.&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt;Support us when you shop for back-to-school items. #StartWithaSmile at &lt;a href="http://smile.amazon.com/ch/34-1817202"&gt;http://smile.amazon.com/ch/34-1817202&lt;/a&gt; and Amazon donates.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-09-12 18:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-09-12 18:58:21</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>nrmb-newsletter-september-12-2016</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>