<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Registration for 2016-2017</title>
  <description>Dear Band Families,

It is time to register for the 2016-2017 band season. Registration will be taki</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is time to register for the 2016-2017 band season. Registration will be taking place on-line over the next few weeks. The &lt;b&gt;deadline is March 31&lt;/b&gt;. All fees and information are needed at this time. All payments are made through &lt;b&gt;PayPal only&lt;/b&gt;. If you know of any parents of 8th graders who will be in band next year, please forward this e-mail to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To complete the process you must submit 2 forms (Volunteer Form and Band Registration Form) and pay through PayPal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please begin with the &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/volunteer-form"&gt;Volunteer Form&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;We ask each family to support their student and the band by signing up for &lt;b&gt;at least two activities&lt;/b&gt;. One of the reasons we have a great band is the high level of parent and family support and involvement!&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;When you finish the &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/volunteer-form"&gt;Volunteer Form&lt;/a&gt; you will be taken directly to the Band Registration Form. &lt;/b&gt;On this form you will be filling out parent and student information and paying the band, course and activities fees. There is also a section for uniform measurement information. If you are a freshman or you were unhappy with your uniform fit last year you will be asked to provide measurement information. (Make sure the appropriate gender is checked at the top of the form.) If you do not provide this information a uniform cannot be preselected for your student and uniform pick-up and selection will be delayed.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;After filling out the Registration Form, click Submit and you will be taken to PayPal to pay your fees&lt;/b&gt; and complete this portion of the registration process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you have completed your registration you will receive three emails: One from PayPal with your payment information; and two from Band Boosters (one with your Volunteer information and one with your Band Registration information). We recommend saving these emails as they are your receipt for your registration and you may wish to refer to them later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you have more than one student&lt;/b&gt;, register the first starting with the Volunteer Form (be sure to list all your students on the form) and for the rest go directly to the &lt;href="http: www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com="" page="" band-registration-form"=""&gt;Band Registration Form. &lt;b&gt;Please Do NOT fill out the Volunteer Form twice&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/href="http:&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;For Band Front (Royalaires and Royalettes): &lt;/b&gt;If you have a student who participates in band for the full year, you need to register now. If they switch to band front after May auditions, you will have extra band front fees that you will need to pay later via a Band Front Registration Form that will open up in May. If you have a student that only wants to participate in the band front, but not in the concert bands, you should wait and register using the Band Front Registration form in May after your student finds out if they are selected. At that time, you will need to pay the class/activity/uniform fees plus the band front fees. Note that you may want to sign up for volunteer activities now since we close out activities once we reach the optimal number of volunteers.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or problems, please don’t hesitate to ask!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-02-27 06:02:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-02-27 06:30:02</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-registration-for-2016-2017</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>