<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Fruit Sale Pick-Up</title>
  <description>Dear Band Families,
 
The Fruit Season is finally coming to an end.  We will be needing volunteers t</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Families,
 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Fruit Season is finally coming to an end.  We will be needing volunteers to help us with the delivery date and pick up dates.  Any and all help is welcome, even if all you can manage is an hour...also the high schoolers are MORE than welcome to volunteer, too!   Here are some important dates, please take note:

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have a fruit delivery date of Wednesday, December 6.  We will be needing A LOT of volunteers that day from 3:30-9 pm at the annex.  We will need people to help bag fruit and arrange it.  The annex is located behind the Board of Education office and it is directly to the right of the football stadium.  There are stairs that lead up to building from the middle school parking lot.  There may also be parking at the Board of Education office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, there are a couple of dates for fruit pick up.  Due to the perishable nature of the cheesecake, it must be delivered ASAP to customers.  These dates are as following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Large order pick-ups will be on Friday, December 8th from 6-8 pm.  We will also need volunteers that night from 5:30-8:30 pm to help hand out orders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For all of those who did not have a large order, pick up will be Saturday, December 9th from 9 am to 1 pm.  This is a big day and we will need A LOT of volunteers from 8:15-1:30 pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, last chance pick up for fruit is the following Tuesday on the 12th from 6-9 pm. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you cannot pick up any of those days, you must contact us and make another arrangement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These will be the ONLY fruit and cheesecake pick up days.  Any items not picked up after that time (and if alternate arrangements have not been made with us) will be donated to charity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are aware of a fellow band family that does not check their email or Facebook, please inform them of the pick-up dates/times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you all again for all of your support in making this another successful fundraiser!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Call or email us with any questions you may have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heidi Cmich&lt;br&gt;
216-224-2968&lt;br&gt;
heidi.cmich@gmail.com &lt;/p&gt;    

&lt;p&gt;Jaimie Poplin     &lt;br&gt;      
228-217-8084&lt;br&gt;
jaimie.poplin@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-11-30 07:11:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-11-30 07:10:22</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>fruit-sale-pick-up1</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>