<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Booster Newsletter</title>
  <description>Hi Everyone,

It is hard to believe 2014 is drawing to a close! Our upcoming concerts (Sunday, Dec. </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is hard to believe 2014 is drawing to a close! Our upcoming concerts (Sunday, Dec. 14 and Monday, Dec. 15) are always a joyous event!  Invite your family and friends to take a break from the craziness of the holiday season and join us for this event. Any "Pre-Order" Ticket requests will be taken through Wednesday, 12/10. The "Pre-Order" Box Office will close on Wednesday, and any further ticket requests after Wednesday will have to be made in person right before the performance. All three performances typically sell out, and if you did not "Pre-Order" your tickets, it is recommended you arrive a half hour early to the performance to see what tickets are still available for that particular performance. The &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonhighschoolband.com/yahoo_site_admin/assets/docs/Holiday_Concert_Ticket_Order_Form.31084730.pdf"&gt;form for pre-ordering is on Mr. Vitale’s website&lt;/a&gt;. Be sure you are ordering tickets for the concert that your child will actually be performing at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Membership/Sportswear, Fruit &amp;amp; Holiday Ornaments&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Membership/sportswear, a limited fruit selection and our annual Christmas ornament will be available at all of the holiday concerts.  So, if you are looking for that extra special something for your bando, perhaps we have just what you are looking for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Drive&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fruit drive has successfully come to an end.  I believe it was the best one we have had in years!  A huge thank you to those that helped out!..Students and parents alike.  Please be sure you deliver the fruit in a timely fashion since fresh picked fruit tastes so much better. It is important to have returning customer base next year. We were informed that our fruit was freshly picked last week!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Email&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you can see, a great deal of band booster correspondence takes place through email.  We have found that some parents do not receive our reminders and updates.  Please be sure we are sending our emails to the most current and active email address.  There is a great deal of information that we wish to convey to you. We would like to do it in the most efficient way possible. If you would like to add or change your email address, please send an email to &lt;a href="mailto:northroyaltonbandboosters@gmail.com"&gt;northroyaltonbandboosters@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; with the new email address as well as your student’s name and grade, and we will update our data base. Often times our information is placed on the website or Facebook, but it does not include all of our important correspondences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing all of you at our upcoming concerts!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-12-10 19:12:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-12-10 19:52:19</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-booster-newsletter</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>