<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Top Rating, T-shirts, Tickets, Trip, and much more...</title>
  <description>CONGRATS to our SUPERIOR Marching Band on an amazing performance!!  We have qualified for States!

 </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;CONGRATS to our SUPERIOR Marching Band on an amazing performance!! We have qualified for States!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Band Best T-Shirts!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you did not get a chance to purchase a Band Fest Tshirt, you still can get one!! The printer has given us a link that will be open for ONE week. &lt;a href="https://norogear.secure-decoration.com/shop/category/Band-Fest-2017?c=1878378&amp;amp;ctype=0"&gt;Click here to order your Band Fest Tshirt&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Car Raffle Tickets&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your bando received two car raffle tickets to sell. Sold tickets and payment should be returned to the white band box no later than October 11th.. You can get extra tickets to sell by contacting Joyce Fink: 440-237-1636&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Disney Trip Registration Is Still Open!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is not too late to register for the Disney trip! Registration will remain open until the end of October. &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonhighschoolband.com/yahoo_site_admin/assets/docs/Disney2018FirstLetterHome.pdf"&gt;To register&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;h3&gt;Senior Band Night&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a reminder to all the SENIORS… please turn in your RSVP to the white band box as soon as possible…. Which would be now. The Hospitality team needs to get their final orders in soon for flowers and food! Don’t delay! The invitation and RSVP have been emailed to you and are on our website. Questions? Please call Amy 216-702-1682 or Kristen 440-476-6960&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Senior Band Night Volunteers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We still are in need of volunteers to help set up and clean up for this event. Please keep in mind the band will not perform until after the football game is complete so volunteering for this event will not prevent you from seeing the Of Wishes and Dream performance. &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-20177"&gt;To volunteer&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;h3&gt;Volunteer Button On Band Booster Website&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An easy, one stop volunteer location is now on the homepage of the Band Booster website. The button is top right and by clicking you can see every event this going on with &lt;a href="/page/volunteer-now" style=""&gt;open volunteer opportunities&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mark Your Calendar!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oct 6 – HOME – Wadsworth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 11 – ALL CAR RAFFLE TICKETS MUST BE TURNED IN TO THE WHITE BAND BOX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
 </content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-10-02 20:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-10-02 20:28:04</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>top-rating-t-shirts-tickets-trip-and-much-more</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>