<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Car Raffle Reminder</title>
  <description>Dear Band Members and Band Boosters,
 
This is an early reminder that we only have until the end of </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Members and Band Boosters,
 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is an early reminder that &lt;b&gt;we only have until the end of October to sell our share of the Stadium Foundation Raffle Tickets&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
 
&lt;p&gt;I hope you have already been in touch with people about this great opportunity to win a brand new car.  In case you would like to contact some folks via email, I have attached a form letter you can easily personalize to help get the word out. Please consider sending a note to family and friends this weekend and watch for their replies.  Don't forget to put something that identifies you in the 'subject' field so they know it is safe to open the attachment. Or you can copy and paste the letter directly into the body of your email.  (Paste without formatting.)&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Kids, this is a great way to reach more people who want to support you!  Just take a few minutes to edit the letter, make it more personal and send it out.  It would be great to sell the winning ticket to someone you know!&lt;/p&gt; 
 
&lt;p&gt;Sell two tickets?  You can do that.&lt;br&gt;
Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;                                                              
 
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or want more tickets, please email or call me.
&lt;a href="tel:440-759-9864"&gt;440-759-9864&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="mailto:mattnjane.coleman@att.net"&gt;mattnjane.coleman@att.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thanks,&lt;br&gt;
Jane Coleman&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-10-04 07:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-10-04 07:52:20</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>car-raffle-reminder</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>