<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Welcome Freshman Parents! Meetings, Band Shirts &amp; More!</title>
  <description>Hello Band Parents!
Just a friendly reminder we have 2 informational meetings this Tuesday evening a</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Band Parents!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a friendly reminder we have 2 informational meetings this Tuesday evening and we are welcoming all incoming freshman parents! We are excited to have your freshman in the band. To help “ease” you into the band program, we are hosting a new parent meeting on Tuesday, June 12th at 6:30 pm at the media center.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Just drop off your Bando and come join us. We will be handing out a “cheat sheet” of tidbits we think you will find helpful and answer questions you may have. Band starts off with a bang and can be overwhelming. Our goal is to help make the band season fun and less stressful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***Following the Freshman parent meeting we will have an "All" Band Parent meeting. This meeting should conclude at 8pm when Band practice ends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The purple band polos shirts and the white band tee-shirts will be for sale this week at meeting/practice. If you are not able to make it please send your Bando with cash or check.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When writing a check please make it out to North Royalton Band Boosters.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purple polos will be sold for $20&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;White band tee-shirts are $10. We highly recommend&amp;nbsp;two white tee-shirts, one for football games and one for Saturday competitions.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to call me at 440-476-8027 or e-mail me at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="mailto:kathleenmpayne@gmail.com" target="_blank"&gt;kathleenmpayne@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; with any questions or comments. We look forward to seeing you on the 12th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kathy Payne&lt;br&gt;2018-2019 NRHS Band Booster President&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2018-06-12 07:06:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2018-06-12 07:34:38</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>welcome-freshman-parents-meetings-band-shirts-and-more</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>