<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Fruit Sale Info</title>
  <description>Hello, Band Families.
 
A huge Thank You to all of you who gave up part of your weekend to get our f</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello, Band Families.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;A huge Thank You to all of you who gave up part of your weekend to get our fruit sale off to a great start! If you did not take your blitz weekend packet into school yet, please get it in ASAP. We have to have all of the packets accounted for and we will be tracking down any that are missing.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;The personal sale packets will be passed out this Wednesday evening. The next day, Thursday, will be our Teacher Blitz Day. Bring your personal packet back to school and ask all of your teachers to support our band program by ordering fruit. This would be a great day to wear some kind of band t-shirt!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;The personal sale will then continue through October 17th, which is the Saturday of the Norton band contest. Ask family and friends to purchase fruit for themselves or to give as gifts. Feel free to ask your neighbors in case they were not home and did not have a chance to order during the blitz weekend. Also consider ordering extra fruit and donating it to the North Royalton Food Bank. Get creative to help our cause!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;The money raised from the fruit is used for many different things such as music, uniforms, flags, band front costumes, fees, and much more. Everyone benefits in some way so that's why it is so important to have everyone help out in some way. There will be no pie sale this year so please consider redirecting the money you would have spent on pies to buying some healthy fruit instead.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We have attached the &lt;a href="FILES%2f2015%2f09%2fFruitSaleFlyer2015.pdf.axdx"&gt;color flyer&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="/FILES%2f2015%2f09%2fFruitSaleOrderForm2015.pdf.axdx"&gt;order form&lt;/a&gt; so you can print extras if you need them.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Susie Perez &amp;amp; Karen Svoboda&lt;br&gt;Fruit Sale Chairs&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-09-15 20:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-09-16 20:35:34</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>fruit-sale-info</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>