<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>2015 Fruit Sale</title>
  <description>Hello Band Families!
 
We hope you are enjoying marching season so far! We want to let you know abou</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Band Families!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We hope you are enjoying marching season so far! We want to let you know about a big fundraiser that will be starting soon - &lt;b&gt;the annual fruit sale!&lt;/b&gt; The proceeds from this sale go into the general band fund. The company we use for this fundraiser is Florida Indian River Groves, located in Vero Beach, Florida. We will be selling navel oranges, grapefruit, tangelos and a few combination packages.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;To kick off this fundraiser our kids will have a &lt;b&gt;blitz weekend on September 12th and 13th&lt;/b&gt; when students will be &lt;b&gt;out in teams &lt;/b&gt;and selling door to door. Packets for that weekend will be coming home with one person per team on Wednesday, September 9th. Each team can pick which day works best for them to go out and sell. It is mandatory that everyone participate, and it has been listed on the band calendar since spring. Everyone is to wear the band purple polo shirt or the white band shirt. All of the orders and money that is collected during the blitz is to be brought back to school that Monday, September 14th, and turned into the white band box. The kids will be treated to a pizza and pop after late band practice that day to thank them for pounding the pavement over the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;That Wednesday the kids will bring home a new fruit packet. They will first use it for our new &lt;b&gt;Teacher Blitz Day. Thursday, September 17th&lt;/b&gt; we would like all of the students to personally ask each of their teachers to order some fruit and support the band. This would also be a good day to wear some kind of North Royalton band shirt! This same packet will continue to be used to ask family and friends for fruit orders. All orders are due by Saturday, October 17th, the day of the Perkins Contest.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Please mark your calendars for the blitz weekend and blitz day to help make this sale as successful as possible!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Susie Perez 440-877-1299 and Karen Svoboda 440-213-6414&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-09-06 07:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-09-06 07:46:38</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>2015-fruit-sale</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>