<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>2017 Band Awards Night</title>
  <description>Dear Band Families,
 
We are on the homestretch to the end of the school year and the Band Awards Ba</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We are on the homestretch to the end of the school year and the Band Awards Banquet is fast approaching. &lt;a href="/FILES%2f2017%2f05%2f2017BandAwardsDinnerInvitation-rev.pdf.axdx"&gt;Download the invitation and RSVP form&lt;/a&gt;. (The RSVP is the second page of the document.) RSVP’s are due back on May 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Band Award Night RSVPs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVPs are requested ASAP so we can order the correct amount of food. If your RSVP is not received on time we cannot guarantee we will have enough food for your family. A check is needed to pay for everyone attending who is not a Senior Band Student. The cost is $11 per person. Seniors band members are free. Please put the RSVP and payment in an envelope and mark it, “Awards Banquet Night” and have your student drop it off in the white band box.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even if you do not attend the dinner, everyone is welcome and encouraged to attend the Band Awards program which starts at 7:00pm. It is a great way to spend an enjoyable evening with family and friends.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Volunteers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We need a few volunteers to help set-up, serve and clean-up after the dinner. Please indicate the time slot that you would be available to help for the Band Award Night dinner. &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/409044daeab2da20-band1"&gt;See the Signup Genius link&lt;/a&gt; and if you could help out it would be greatly appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Drinks&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are asking band families to kindly donate some beverages for this event. The drinks can be dropped off at Cafeteria I beginning at 3:00 PM on Wednesday, May 10, 2017. Someone will be in Cafeteria I to accept your donation. NO beverages should be dropped off in the band room or the main office. &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/409044DAEAB2DA20-drink1"&gt;Please click this Signup Genius link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;p&gt;Thanks in advance for your assistance and donations!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Helen&lt;br&gt;Hospitality&lt;br&gt;440 746-9048&lt;br&gt;alandhelenkelly@cox.net&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/FILES%2f2017%2f05%2f2017BandAwardsDinnerInvitation-rev.pdf.axdx"&gt;&lt;b&gt;2017BandAwardsDinnerInvitation-rev.pdf (90.8KB)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-05-01 11:05:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-05-01 11:37:14</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>2017-band-awards-night</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
    <category>fa6094d0-c8e0-4964-8deb-b6349a6dd281</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>