<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Fest and Fruit Sale and Football!</title>
  <description>Band Fest - September 16
The preview of our contest show will be Saturday, Sept 16 at Band Fest!  We</description>
  <content>&lt;h3&gt;Band Fest - September 16&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The preview of our contest show will be Saturday, Sept 16 at Band Fest!  We will be hosting 13 bands in total and there will be more than 2000 performers!  WOW!!!!!  Plan to come for the entire evening to enjoy the show.  Tshirts will be sold at the event!    WE NEED VOLUNTEERS FOR CONCESSIONS, USHERS AND PROGRAM SALES.  You WILL be able to see our marching band march….  We close all station so you will be able to enjoy the debut of ‘Of Wishes and Dreams’ …. &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-20174"&gt;To volunteer&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

 

&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sale Blitz Weekend&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Fruit Sale Blitz weekend has been changed to SEPT 23 – 24  due to Hurricane Irma.  We appreciate your flexibility… Packets will be passed out Sept. 20 after 6-9 practice.  Please see Mr.  Vitale’s website for report time changes for the Twinsburg game due to the Pizza Party the Boosters will be giving the band.  after extended practice, stop by Café 2 for Pizza as a Thank You from the Boosters!  Any questions?  Contact:  Jayme Poplin – 440-457-7417 or Heidi Cmich – 216-244-2968&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Football Game Date Change!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a reminder that the Twinsburg game is SATURDAY, SEPTEMBER 23 at 7pm  We still need chaperones!!! &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-20175"&gt;To volunteer&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Car Raffle Tickets&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your bando received two car raffle tickets to sell after the practice last Wednesday.  Sold tickets and payment should be returned to the white band box.  You can get extra tickets to sell by contacting Joyce Fink:  440-376-5765&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Volunteer Button on Band Booster Webpage&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An easy, one stop volunteer location is now on the homepage of the Band Booster website.  The button is top left and by clicking you can see every event this going on with open volunteer opportunities!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;The Boosters appreciate all our volunteers! We only ask for exactly the number of volunteers we need so if your schedule changes, PLEASE let the chairperson know you are unable to attend and remove your name from SignUpGenius.  Thank you….  &lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Mark Your Calendar!&lt;/h3&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 15 – AWAY - Stow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 16 – Festival of Bands – check Mr. Vitale’s website for reporting details&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 23 – ** NEW DATE** FRUIT SALE BLITZ AND PIZZA PARTY.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 23 – AWAY – Twinsburg  NOTE THE DATE CHANGE!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 25 – Booster Meeting  - 7pm in the Media Center&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 29 – HOME  - Hudson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 30 – CONTEST – Avon Lake&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-09-13 07:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-09-13 07:27:58</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-fest-and-fruit-sale</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>