<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Booster Newsletter - August 8th</title>
  <description>Band Camp Starts this WEEK!!!!!

A quick first week at Band Camp and the weather is working in our f</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;A quick first week at Band Camp and the weather is working in our favor!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Important dates listed below!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Just a few dates and links you need to know as we move into August:&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Mr. Vitale’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandboosters.com"&gt;Band Booster’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FaceBook North Royalton Band Boosters -- Like Us!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Parent Meeting: AUGUST 10 @ 6:15pm – Media Center (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Band Booster Meeting: AUGUST 29 @ 7pm – Media Center&lt;/li&gt;
 
&lt;li&gt;Aug 8 – MAKEUP date for uniform pickup (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aug 10 – NEW PARENT meeting – 6:15pm – Media Center (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aug 10 – Ice Cream Social ORDER DUE!!!! (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aug 12 – Picture Day (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aug 20 -21 – Easter Seals Drive (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aug 21 – Homedays Parade -- Refer to Mr. Vitale’s website as we near the date&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aug 22 – Parent Preview Night – ICE CREAM SOCIAL FUNDRAISER – (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 3-5 - Air Show (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Make-up Date for Uniform Pickup&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our uniform committee will offer ONE MORE DAY to pick up your uniform for the season. THIS IS YOUR LAST CHANCE TO GET YOUR UNIFORM!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; 
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;DATE: &lt;/b&gt;AUGUST 8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;TIME: &lt;/b&gt;5:30-7:30pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHERE:&lt;/b&gt; UNIFORM ROOM 310&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enter the building by the Community Room&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The required Tshirts and polos will also be for sale at the uniform distribution. T-shirts are $10 and polos are $20. CASH or CHECK ONLY!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CONTACTS:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Anthony Amato&lt;/b&gt; Marching Band 216-401-7763&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Carolyn Srp&lt;/b&gt; Royalaires 440-582-1860&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jennifer Rozek&lt;/b&gt; Royalettes 440-241-4215&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;New Parent Meeting – August 10th&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are a freshman parent or new to our band parent, the Band Boosters would like to welcome you to the 2016-17 Marching season. Please stop into the Media Center on August 10th at 6:15pm (right after you have dropped off your bando for the mandatory painting session) and meet the Exec board, many chairpersons and participate in a Q&amp;amp;A session. Not sure where the media center is located? Please park in the parking lot near the Performing Arts Center. Locate the Bell Tower and enter through the doors nearest the Bell Tower (your bandos will be going in through that door) and the Media Center is immediately on the left!&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Contact: &lt;/b&gt;Amanda Kost 440-864-6543&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Ice Cream Social Order and Money Due&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a reminder that the last day to get your orders in for the Ice Cream Social at the Parent Preview Night (August 22 @ 7pm) is this Wednesday, AUGUST 10th!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;All order forms and payment MUST be in the white band mailbox at the end of the 6 – 9 practice on AUGUST 10th. Please note that although the Bandos will be eating their pre-ordered ice cream after their performance at the preview, families and friends can enjoy their ice cream any time during the evening beginning at 6:00pm!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;If you cannot find your order form, one is attached!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Contact: &lt;/b&gt;Karen Svoboda 440-213-6414&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Picture Day -- Photo Buttons:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On picture day, Friday, August 12, each student will have their picture taken by the Band Booster parents. These pictures will be taken after the group pictures and Mr. Vitale will instruct the kids where to line up for these pictures. These pictures will be used to make photo buttons with all proceeds from buttons sale going to the Band Boosters. Students can also get pictures taken with their friends and siblings if desired. This is a big fundraiser for the band and we ask that you support the band by purchasing these buttons. Orders for buttons will be taken at Preview Night on August 22nd. The buttons will be ready for pick up at the home football game on SEPTEMBER 2nd. Thank you for your support of the NRHS Marching Band!&lt;/p&gt;  
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Any questions?&lt;/b&gt; Call Nancy Chester – 440-503-4522&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Easter Seals Fundraiser – Help Us Fill The Truck&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As our Easter Seals event draws closer, we are working harder than ever to spread the word about this event. If you happen to visit, or know someone that is involved with a garage sale, rummage sale, street sale, moving sale, flea market or yard sale, kindly let the seller know that after their sale, they can donate their unsold SOFT GOOD items to our Easter Seals event (NR Home Days) on Sat/Sun August 20-21 next to the board office. We also have a location to drop off items ahead of time if this time is inconvenient!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-easter2"&gt;follow this link to volunteer your time&lt;/a&gt;! It is an easy and extremely helpful way to show your support!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Contact&lt;/b&gt;: Holly Michalke 216-926-8836&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Air Show&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The largest Band Booster fundraiser of the year is coming up fast – The Cleveland National Air Show September 3-5th.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;The North Royalton Band Boosters have provided manpower to the air show for many years and we are given preferential treatment by the organizers due to the large number of hard working and enthusiastic volunteers we offer. When fully staffed, this event earns the Band up to $10,000!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;In order to fully staff the air show and maximize our fundraising opportunity, we need to supply 80 volunteers each day of the air show. We will sell and collect tickets at the Plaza booth and at Gate 13, where we will also managing the parking. For those of you who have not worked the air show before, this is a great way to get to know your fellow band parents and have a fun time meeting people. Volunteering at the Air Show is usually a family event so moms, dads, and siblings are all welcome along with our “Bandos.” Children must be 15 years of age to participate.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;To sign up for your slots, we have set up a form at &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/20f054ba8ab2ca1f49-nrband"&gt;www.signupgenius.com&lt;/a&gt;. All you need to do is select your day, indicate the number of volunteers in your group and provide a phone number and email address.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/20f054ba8ab2ca1f49-nrband"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here is the link to our signup form&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note: Monday is usually the hardest day to fill so if you are available Monday, please select that day. Thank you to all the band parents who have already indicated you are planning on volunteering and to those who have yet to volunteer, please consider participating in this event.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;CONTACT: &lt;/b&gt;Gary Diehl 440-915-1178&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-08-08 20:08:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-08-09 21:07:59</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-booster-newsletter-august-8th</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>