<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Easter Seals 'Fill the Truck' Fundraiser</title>
  <description>Easter Seals Northern Ohio is partnering with North Royalton Band Boosters to give back to the commu</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Easter Seals Northern Ohio is partnering with North Royalton Band Boosters to give back to the community while helping children and adults with disabilities. North Royalton Band Boosters is hosting a “Fill the Truck” fundraiser to benefit the North Royalton Marching Band. We will be collecting any and all cloth items. Easter Seals will provide the truck to pick up all donations. This truck will be parked next to the North Royalton Board of Education, 6579 Royalton Road on August 22nd (9am – 6pm) and on August 23rd (1pm – 6pm).&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We need volunteers to help receive donations.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.SignUpGenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-easter"&gt;TO SIGN UP TO VOLUNTEER, CLICK THIS LINK&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;North Royalton Band Boosters will be compensated based on the number of bags/pounds of cloth collected. Acceptable items include (but are not limited to): clothing, comforters, blankets, towels, sheets, shoes, accessories, and purses. The Boosters will only earn money from those types of cloth donations listed above. Even stained or torn items can be recycled into something else.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We challenge every North Royalton student to donate at least one bag of cloth. Tell your friends and neighbors! You do not need to have a student at North Royalton to donate items. All donors will receive a tax deductible receipt! If you have any questions, please feel free to contact Amanda Kost at &lt;a href="mailto:amandabethkost@gmail.com"&gt;amandabethkost@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or at 440-864-6543.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-08-04 12:08:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-08-04 12:11:38</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>easter-seals-fill-the-truck-fundraiser</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>