<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Personal Water Jugs at Rehearsal</title>
  <description>Hi Parents, 
 We have been very fortunate to have had below normal temps for MOST of band camp. Howe</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Parents, &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; We have been very fortunate to have had below normal temps for MOST of band camp. However, yesterday was an exception. Please be sure your child comes prepared with a water jug or large water bottle WITH their name in sharpie clearly marked on the outside. It is very important that EVERYONE is drinking far more water during each water break than their normal intake. Especially during warmer temps! This is important to avoid dehydration. Students are allowed to bring water bottles and water jugs. No camelbacks or backpacks are permitted for many reasons. Water breaks are short, but are long enough to hydrate us if students are prepared. Although your student will not be denied a trip to the water fountain, understand that 280 band students lined up for a few water fountains probably does not allow enough time for proper hydration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Please avoid soda and caffeine as this intensifies dehydration. Gatorade is ok but does not hydrate as well as water in most cases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I hope you find these tips helpful! We hope to keep all of our bandos in good health! Be prepared! Practice! And drink lots and lots of water!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I really enjoyed the performance&amp;nbsp;Sunday night! It's gonna be a great year!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Holly Michalke&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>False</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>True</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-08-22 07:08:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-08-25 19:22:49</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>personal-water-jugs-at-rehearsal</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>