<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Membership, Contest Hoodies, and Bling Wear Blitz!</title>
  <description>Band Booster Membership

Please join Band Boosters if you haven’t already done so, this money suppor</description>
  <content>&lt;h3&gt;Band Booster Membership&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please join Band Boosters if you haven’t already done so, this money supports our scholarship program for senior band members and honors &amp;amp; awards for our band students. We are just shy of reaching our 200 member mark.  We have limited sizes in the tee shirts and also limited quantities on our NR Marching Band Tervis Tumbler (would make a great Christmas gift). Click here for a membership form for your convenience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Contest Hoodies and Pins &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have three extra hoodies to sell in size small, large, and extra large for $35 each.  Contest pins are also available for the price of $5 each. If you are interested please contact me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Blingwear Blitz &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are going to offer NR Band Blingwear for a very limited time.  Click here for the sizing information for the apparel and here for the actual order form.  Please refer to the forms for pricing.  If you have any questions please call me.  Please note these items are only available in purple and we are asking that all orders be into the white bandbox no later than Saturday, October 14.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Shirley Berish&lt;br&gt;   
saberish@hotmail.com&lt;br&gt;   
440-717-1532&lt;br&gt;
Membership Chairperson&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-10-10 21:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-10-10 21:31:25</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>membership-contest-hoodies-and-bling-wear-blitz</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>