<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>NRHS Band Program Newsletter – March 13, 2017</title>
  <description>CONGRATS to all our concert bands and our directors---- SUPERIOR ratings across the board! We are so</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;CONGRATS to all our concert bands and our directors---- SUPERIOR ratings across the board! We are so proud of all of you!! Now on to STATES!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Registration for 2017-2018 is OPEN. Visit &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/Band-Registration-Instructions"&gt;www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com to register&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LINKS you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Mr. Vitale’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandboosters.com"&gt;Band Booster’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/North-Royalton-Band-Boosters/164850233634290"&gt;FaceBook North Royalton Band Boosters -- Like Us!!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;DATES you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;March 20 – Band Booster Meeting – 7pm Media Center&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;OMEA State Contest Volunteers Needed!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be hosting the OMEA State event April 28-29 at NRHS. We are in need of 100 volunteers throughout the weekend to help make this event a success! We have many opportunities for volunteering: Concessions, Sight Reading Door Monitors, Stage Crew/Gym &amp;amp; PAC Door Monitors, Program Sales, Hospitality, and Parking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The link to SignupGenius to volunteer is below: Please consider signing up for more than one time slot. You will be able to see your concert band member perform! Any questions, please contact Amanda Kost at 440-864-6543 or by email: &lt;a href="mailto:memandy@ameritech.net"&gt;memandy@ameritech.net&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-omea1"&gt;Volunteer here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Easter Seals&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Band Boosters will be partnering once again with Easter Seals! Our event will be running the SAME DAYS as State Contest. Since it was so successful, we will be parking the Easter Seals truck right outside the PAC. We do need volunteers to work the truck during the event. Please consider helping us out with this event! Any questions, please contact Holly 216-926-8836. &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-easter1"&gt;Volunteer here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;State Band DVDs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The State Band DVDs will be distributed Monday, May 13. Please remind your student to pick up your DVD from Mr. Vitale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;MAY 6 – Basket Raffle&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our annual Basket Raffle event will be MAY 6th and 3Spot in North Royalton. The 3Spot will be giving us the MAIN DINING room for our event this year! The ticket order form has gone out! Please send your ticket reservation to Becky Humes (address on ticket order form) or deposit in the white band box! Looking forward to a warm, spring event.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h3&gt;OPEN Chairposition&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As mentioned above, we are in need of TWO people to chair our Fruit Sale next year. I can honestly say that I have worked with Susie and Karen this year and these gals have TOTALLY organized this committee and have fantastic notes for you to follow for next year. Consider volunteering NOW since both Karen and Susie are available to go over everything with you for next year! Call Amanda Kost 440-864-6543 or Susie Perez 440-877-1299 if you are interested in volunteering. It is a FUN committee!!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-03-13 19:03:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-03-13 19:47:10</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>nrhs-band-program-newsletter-march-13-2017</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>