<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Fruit Sale Blitz This Weekend</title>
  <description>Hello, Band Families!
    We hope you are enjoying marching season so far! We want to let you know a</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello, Band Families!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;We hope you are enjoying marching season so far! We want to let you know about a big fundraiser that will be starting this weekend - the annual fruit sale! The proceeds from this sale go into the general band fund. The company we use for this fundraiser is Florida Indian River Groves, located in Vero Beach, Florida. We will be selling navel oranges, grapefruits, tangelos, apples and a few combination packages. Here is some information for you:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;To kick off this fundraiser our kids will have a blitz weekend on September 13th and 14th when students will be out in teams and selling door to door. The packets for the blitz weekend will be signed out after late band practice this Wednesday, September 10th. Your child may take longer getting out to the car or getting home that night; hopefully no more than an extra 20 minutes or so. If possible, they are to go out selling Saturday morning, but if there is a conflict they can pick another time during the weekend. It is mandatory that everyone participate, and it has been listed on the band calendar since spring.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Everyone is to wear the band purple polo shirt and either khakis or shorts.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Each team will be picking streets where they want to sell. They are to sell for two hours. If they finish the streets they picked then they can move on to other streets.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;All of the orders and money that is collected is to be brought back to school that Monday, September 15th, and turned in to the white band box. The kids will be treated to a pizza, pop and dessert meal that day to thank them for pounding the pavement over the weekend. They will either eat after extended practice or their monitored practice. The team envelope needs to be turned in for that team to enjoy pizza.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;The kids will get a reminder sheet about the blitz weekend after the football game this Friday night.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Wednesday of next week the kids will bring home a new fruit packet so they can continue selling fruit to family and friends. The last day to turn in orders and money will be October 17th.  Details will be included with that packet.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Please read all of the information that your child brings home for both the blitz weekend and the personal fruit sale. If you have any questions you can contact either one of us.  Thank you, in advance, for helping us make this a very successful fundraiser!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Susie Perez &lt;a href="tel:440-877-1299"&gt;440-877-1299&lt;/a&gt; and Karen Svoboda &lt;a href="tel:440-213-6414"&gt;440-213-6414&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-09-08 20:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-09-08 20:28:24</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>fruit-sale-blitz-this-weekend</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>a70d94a8-5d3c-44aa-b4d6-29cb41d521c4</category>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>