<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Happy New Year News!</title>
  <description>Dear Band Families,

Merry Christmas and Happy New Year 2018 to all our Band Families!
 
It is hard </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Merry Christmas and Happy New Year 2018 to all our Band Families!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;It is hard to believe that 2017 is coming to end so quickly… What a fantastic year it was for our Band Program! Looking forward to the start of 2018 and all the events coming up until the end of the school year….&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Now that you have had a chance to catch your breath, I would like to list a few of the events coming up in 2018…. As always, we need YOUR help to make these events a success!!!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;First, we will be sponsoring &lt;b&gt;Rhythm and Raffle on February 24th&lt;/b&gt; at North Royalton High School Cafeteria 1 (right by the PAC). This is a FAMILY event with dinner, basket raffles and performances by Middle School, High School and Baldwin Wallace jazz bands, combos, and ensembles….. It will be a great night of music!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;But to host this event, we need help on our planning committees…. Please consider joining one of our committees…. Follow &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-rhythm"&gt;the SignUpGenius Link to read the committee descriptions and volunteer to help us plan the FUNDRAISING event&lt;/a&gt; for the Band Programs!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Second, in the near future, there will be a link available for &lt;b&gt;volunteering to chaperone our band members to the Concert Contests&lt;/b&gt;. Stay tuned for more information….&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Third, &lt;b&gt;our school will host the STATE contest&lt;/b&gt;. We will need almost 100 parents to help us run the two-day event! Details will be coming out in March regarding the event!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Finally, we will be needing help with the Band Award Banquet in May…. Again more details to follow…&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Please keep these events in mind as we wind down the Band Program season….&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;As always, thank you for your help and enjoy the rest of your time off. Happy 2018!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Amanda Kost&lt;br&gt;President, Band Boosters&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-12-31 07:12:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-12-31 07:38:59</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>happy-new-year-news</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>