<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Fruit Sale Website</title>
  <description>Hello, Fruit-Loving Band Families!
We hope all of you are continuing to collect orders for fruit! Pl</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello, Fruit-Loving Band Families!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope all of you are continuing to collect orders for fruit! Please remember you have through Saturday, October 15th to turn in your order forms and money. That is the day of the Copley Competition, so you can have your kids put the fruit envelopes into the white band box when they report for the day. If you need extra information packets, they are located in the band room, on the wall, next to the white band box, or you can print off what you need from the booster website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are happy to announce a brand new ordering option for this year. Drumroll please…you can now place orders for fruit from our e-commerce website! (Cymbal crash!) Yes, this is the world-launch of our &lt;a href="http://freshfruitorder.org/NRHSMarchingBand"&gt;Fruit Sale Fundraiser online ordering&lt;/a&gt; center! This site opens up all kinds of options for you and those you know. Here are some information points to help you use the website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Most of the items from our paper flyer are available to order online. When you order from here, those items will be shipped on the same truck that brings all of the other items that have been ordered using the paper order forms.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;During the ordering process you will be asked to add a student’s name which will be tied to the order. That student will be notified and those items will be the responsibility of him or her to deliver along with any other orders he or she has.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;There are special holiday assortments you will see on the site that are only available for direct shipment. These are clearly marked with a picture of a truck next to them as well as a description explaining they are direct ship items. Shipping charges are already included in these prices. This gives you a great chance to send fruit to a loved one while still supporting our band! These items are available to ship to the 48 contiguous states. You set up the shipment date, November 14-December 12.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;This eCommerce website only accepts credit cards.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;The website link can be sent to family and friends so they can shop online at their convenience. They can also have fruit directly shipped to others.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Using our new eCommerce website allows you to place fruit orders for an extended period of time. Our online ordering will be available through November 20th.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://freshfruitorder.org/NRHSMarchingBand"&gt;If you think you are ready to explore this very exciting addition to our annual fruit sale, click here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We would love to blow up Facebook with this new eCommerce site information! Please feel free to share with family and friends – maybe even add your bando’s picture for the “awww” factor! Our sales from the blitz are around $9,000. Last year we had around $21,000 in sales total for the entire sale, so let’s really take advantage of social media to get the word out and beat last year’s total.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy this new shopping experience! Please let us know if you have any questions. As always, thank you for supporting YOUR award-winning marching band!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-10-05 20:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-10-05 20:38:06</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>fruit-sale-website</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>