<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Fest Help Needed!</title>
  <description>Hello Band Parents and Supporters!
 
Our 2016 Band Festival is this coming Saturday, September 17. W</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Band Parents and Supporters!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Our 2016 Band Festival is this coming Saturday, September 17. We currently have very few people signed up to help. If you would like to help us out, &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080948a9ac2aa75-nrhs"&gt;please click here on this link . It will take you to the sign up genius&lt;/a&gt; where you can choose which volunteer opportunity you would like to do!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The jobs we need help with are as follows:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Program Sales (4) &lt;/b&gt;Sales will pause during NRHS Band's performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ushers (6)&lt;/b&gt; Volunteers will be assisting audience in the home stands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ticket Sales and Collections (10) &lt;/b&gt;Volunteers will be needed at the start of the evening. Once the number of people entering slows down, volunteers can trade shifts to man entrances. Sales will end before NRHS Band's performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Concessions (8)&lt;/b&gt; Sales will pause during NRHS Band's performance&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It really is an easy and fun evening and you will still get to see your student perform! Please sign up or let me know what you would like to do. If you have already signed up, thank you! Please feel free to ask a friend to sign up with you. Just forward them this email and they can click on the link or email me. Thanks for your help in making the Band Fest a great experience for our kids and our visitors from around Northeast Ohio!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Beth Burdick&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-09-12 18:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-09-12 18:45:42</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-fest-help-needed</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>fa6094d0-c8e0-4964-8deb-b6349a6dd281</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>