<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Booster Newsletter - Registration, States and More</title>
  <description>Hello Band Nation,
 
It looks like our band members had an awesome experience in Florida. The weathe</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Band Nation,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;It looks like our band members had an awesome experience in Florida. The weather was great, the parade was exciting, and the lifelong memories were made by many. It is hard to believe that we have begun the final stretch of the 2015-16 school year.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;It looks like over the next 8 weeks we will spend a fair amount of time together with our final 4 events.  These events include State Band Contest, Band O Rama, Band Banquet and the Memorial Day Parade. We definitely are a busy band nation! Please check the &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonhighschoolband.com/"&gt;director’s page&lt;/a&gt; often to stay on top of it all! If you haven't bookmarked this page, please do so. It is a very handy resource. &lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Registration&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although the deadline for registration has passed, it is not too late to sign up! Please &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/Band-Registration-Instructions"&gt;follow this link&lt;/a&gt; to secure your child's spot in the 2016-17 NRHS marching band today! &lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;States/Easter Seals &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our final fundraiser events will take place on April 22 and 23rd and include State Band Contest and Easter Seals. We need your support and need nearly 100 volunteers to organize these 2 events. Please check your calendar and sign up by April 15! The committees need to know who their team will be to make this event a success! Follow the link and join us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054eafa729a02-omea"&gt;Sign up Genius Link for States&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;h3&gt;Easter Seals&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attached is the Easter Seals link to the article in The Post for our event on Saturday, April 23. You can help by advertising through word of mouth or social media (Facebook, Instagram or Twitter) and save your spring cleaning items. Another possible source is to make your local church or any online garage sale sources aware of it. Feel free to use the attached link for promotion purposes. Click on the Sign up Genius link if you are interested in volunteering for this simple and profitable event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054eafa729a02-easter1"&gt;Sign up Genius link for Easter Seals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thepostnewspapers.com/north_royalton/breaking_news/band-asking-residents-to-help-fill-the-truck/article_45b88593-cf9b-5f7e-8756-3245167df342.html?utm_medium=social&amp;amp;utm_source=facebook&amp;amp;utm_campaign=user-share"&gt;Advertisement in The Post - Please share!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;h3&gt;Attention Freshman and Senior Parents&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are asking each Senior family to donate one last time. Please donate 1 or 2 boxes of prepackaged (store-bought) baked goods that we can sell at State Band Contest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are asking the Freshman families to donate the following based on the letter of your last name:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A – R:   12 - 20 oz. bottles of Gatorade/PowerAde (Also G2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S – Z:    24 - cans of pop – Please get some diet too&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those families interested in donating more, we can use anything pre-packaged. Rice Krispy Treats, Granola Bars, Muffins, etc. Anything you donate becomes a profit for the band.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donations can be dropped off at 13749 Woodcroft Trace (Woodcroft Glen development) beginning Monday, April 11, in the bin located by the side garage door.  Please bring it on or before Tuesday, April 19.  Please put your last name on the package.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;It looks like a busy spring for us all! See you soon!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;br&gt;
Band Booster President&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-04-09 07:04:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-04-09 07:45:51</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-booster-newsletter-registration-states-and-more</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>