<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Announcing Munching for Music</title>
  <description>Hello Band Families!
 
We want to let you know about a new program that will be starting soon - Munc</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Band Families!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We want to let you know about a new program that will be starting soon - Munching For Music! This is a give-back arrangement with local restaurants. On a specified day, at a certain restaurant, a percentage of sales will be donated back to the band. All you have to do to make this program a success is to dine at the restaurant we're working with for that day, and present either a paper flyer or show the flyer on your smart phone so that your purchase will be tied to the band. It's that simple! Please spread the word to your family and friends so that they will know of this easy way to help our kids. Our goal is to have these days several times during the year working with a variety of restaurants to help raise funds for the band. Please consider dining at these establishments on the upcoming days to support the band, and also on other days to let these businesses know how much we appreciate them giving back to us!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;The first Munching For Music day will be Wednesday, June 3rd at Sweet CeCe's in Broadview Heights. Please see the &lt;a href="/FILES%2f2015%2f05%2fSweet_CeCes_NRmarchband_flyer.pdf.axdx"&gt;attached flyer&lt;/a&gt; for details. Sweet CeCe's offers yummy frozen yogurts, sandwiches, salads, smoothies and other treats! What a great way to celebrate the end of the school year!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for supporting the North Royalton Bands!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/FILES%2f2015%2f05%2fSweet_CeCes_NRmarchband_flyer.pdf.axdx"&gt;Sweet CeCes flyer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-05-28 21:05:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-05-28 21:13:36</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>announcing-munching-for-music</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>a70d94a8-5d3c-44aa-b4d6-29cb41d521c4</category>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>