<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Booster News</title>
  <description>Hi Everyone,An exceptional job was done by our Bandos last night! These kids really raised the bar t</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An exceptional job was done by our Bandos last night! These kids really raised the bar this week. The improvement was very noticeable in every area. We were at Norton's new stadium last night. The weather was excellent. But it was such a shame their new stadium had so little seating. It makes us appreciate our facility so much more. We couldn't sit together to do our ROYALTON cheer either. However, on the positive, it was a very nice field for the kids to march on and the Norton Boosters were very gracious hosts!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Now to the awards...There were some pretty high powered bands at this contest. It was nice to see our band still come away with several well-deserved awards!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Best Auxiliary in AA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Best Auxiliary overall&lt;/li&gt;(I'd like to add that these ladies are doing an exceptional job this year. Wow, they truly deserved these awards!)&lt;li&gt;Best General Effect in AA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Best General Effect overall&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1st place in AA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grand Champions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And of course, received a Superior Rating! The winning streak continues. Congratulations kids!&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was also nice to see so many alumni last night! We not only have a great band, but we also have a Great Band community. This is what helps perpetuate this amazing tradition we are all a part of. Awesome!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Senior Night&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Friday is Senior Band Parent Night. Please read the past emails regarding parent responsibilities for help with the Senior dinner before the game. Also, underclassman will be given pizza after practice and before the game. Visit the &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonhighschoolband.com/"&gt;directors website&lt;/a&gt; for specific details regarding this week and plan accordingly. Report time is at 4:00 pm AND the band will perform the contest show post game as well.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sale&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the final week for the fruit drive. Please be sure to get your orders into the white band box by next Saturday. If you need more order forms, they are located in the band room or on our website. If you have any questions contact Susie Perez at 440-877-1299/&lt;a href="mailto:susielbp@juno.com"&gt;susielbp@juno.com&lt;/a&gt; or Karen Svoboda at 440-213-6414/&lt;a href="mailto:svo@wideopenwest.com"&gt;svo@wideopenwest.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reminder -&lt;/b&gt; This is our last major fundraiser for the year. Our potential profit is significant. Please do your part and sell fruit. We have met or exceeded every fundraiser so far. Let's see this one through to the end as well!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Concessions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With senior band night coming up this week Friday, we are in need of more volunteers than usual to help with concessions. (14 to be exact). If you are available, please contact Dawn Rembowski at 216-990-0271 or email her at &lt;a href="mailto:dawnrembowski@att.net"&gt;dawnrembowski@att.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Perkins Contest&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's competition takes us to Sandusky Perkins for our final regional performance. The schedule is already posted on the &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonhighschoolband.com/"&gt;directors site&lt;/a&gt;. This will be a very good show with many quality bands performing. Come join us to cheer our Bandos on!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for all you do! See you next weekend.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;br&gt;Band Booster President&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-10-12 20:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-10-12 21:04:17</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-booster-news1</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>