<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Copley Contest,Car Raffle,Senior Band Night Are Coming Up</title>
  <description>Copley Contest this weekend!  Come out and support our band!  Performance is scheduled for 8:30pm

C</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Copley Contest this weekend!&lt;/b&gt;  Come out and support our band!  Performance is scheduled for 8:30pm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Car Raffle Tickets Are Due This Wednesday!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your bando received two car raffle tickets to sell.   Sold tickets and payment should be returned to the white band box no later than October 11th..  You can get extra tickets to sell by contacting Joyce Fink:  440-237-1636&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sales&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal Fruit Sales are still going on!  Once you have completed your sales, place your order with payments in the WHITE Band Box Attention: Jaime Poplin or Heidi Cmich.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any questions?  Contact Jaime: 440-457-7417 or Heidi: 216-224-2968&lt;/p&gt;
 
 
&lt;h3&gt;50/50 Volunteers Needed for Senior Band Night, Oct 20th!!!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We only have 4 volunteers to sell raffle tickets for Senior Band Night….  We normally have 10 parents helping sell tickets.  Please consider selling tickets that night…  it is only 2 hours… done before half time… FUN!!!  It is a great way to help the band…. &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-20173"&gt;Please volunteer here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;h3&gt;Senior Band Night - All RSVPs Are Due Now!&lt;/h3&gt;   
&lt;p&gt;We are still missing 20 senior RSVPs for Senior Band Night.  We need to know either way if you are attending so we can get our final orders into the florist and the caterer.  Questions?  Please call Amy  216-702-1682 or Kristen 440-476-6960&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Senior Band Night Volunteers – We need SEVEN (7) volunteers for the event!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We still are in need of  SEVEN volunteers to help set up and clean up for this event.  Help us thank our senior families for a fantastic four years with the Band Program.  Please keep in mind the band will not perform until after the football game is complete so volunteering for this event will not prevent you from seeing the Of Wishes and Dream performance.  &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-20177"&gt;To volunteer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;h3&gt;Junior Families - Bakery Donations For Senior Band Night&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a reminder to ALL JUNIOR FAMILIES …  the Hospitality committee is in need of Bakery Donations for Senior Band Night.  You can send the bakery in with your Band member when they report to practice that afternoon.  &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-201710"&gt;Please follow this link to donate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Volunteer Button on Band Booster Webpage&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An easy, one stop volunteer location is now on the homepage of the Band Booster website.  The button is top left and by clicking you can see every event this going on with open volunteer opportunities!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mark Your Calendar!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 11 – ALL CAR RAFFLE TICKETS MUST BE TURNED IN TO THE WHITE BAND BOX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 13 – AWAY – Brecksville/Broadview Hts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 14 – CONTEST – Copley --  Performance at 8:30pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 20 – HOME – Nordonia --  SENIOR BAND NIGHT&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-10-10 21:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-10-10 21:26:52</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>copley-contest-car-raffle-senior-band-night-are-coming-up</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>