<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Registration for the 2018-2019 School Year</title>
  <description>Hello Band Families,
It is time to register for the 2018-2019 band season. Registration will be taki</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is time to register for the 2018-2019 band season. Registration will be taking place on-line over the next few weeks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;The deadline is&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="aBn" tabindex="0" data-term="goog_2009904931"&gt;&lt;span class="aQJ"&gt;April 8&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. All fees and information are needed at this time.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;All payments are made though PayPal only&lt;/strong&gt;. If you know of any parents of 8&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;graders who will be in band next year, please forward this e-mail to them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To complete the process you must submit 2 forms (Volunteer Form and Band Registration Form).&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Please begin with the Volunteer Form at &lt;a href="https://northroyaltonbandboosters.us15.list-manage.com/track/click?u=f9c4e414afe05390874757772&amp;amp;id=9d3c2f2632&amp;amp;e=79b990d89d" target="_blank" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;amp;q=https://northroyaltonbandboosters.us15.list-manage.com/track/click?u%3Df9c4e414afe05390874757772%26id%3D9d3c2f2632%26e%3D79b990d89d&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1519774060523000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHnPUSlM4rq0GJOxtTuFXHijAJZbw"&gt;http://www.&lt;wbr&gt;northroyaltonbandboosters.com/&lt;wbr&gt;page/volunteer-form&lt;/a&gt;. When you finish the Volunteer Form you will be taken directly to the Band Registration Form&lt;/strong&gt;. If you have more than one student, register the first starting with the Volunteer Form (be sure to list all your students on the form) and for the rest go directly to the Band Registration Form using the link below. &lt;strong&gt;Please Do NOT fill out the Volunteer form twice.&lt;/strong&gt; It is a good idea to have your calendar and your student’s measurements (if they are a freshman or they were unhappy with their uniform fit last year) handy when you begin registration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Once you have completed your registration you will receive three emails:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; One&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;from PayPal with your payment information; and two from Band Boosters (one with your Volunteer information and one with your Band Registration Information).&lt;/em&gt; We recommend saving these emails as they are your receipt for your registration and you may wish to refer to them later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please see below for important information about each form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Volunteer Form&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://northroyaltonbandboosters.us15.list-manage.com/track/click?u=f9c4e414afe05390874757772&amp;amp;id=abc718ec0e&amp;amp;e=79b990d89d" target="_blank" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;amp;q=https://northroyaltonbandboosters.us15.list-manage.com/track/click?u%3Df9c4e414afe05390874757772%26id%3Dabc718ec0e%26e%3D79b990d89d&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1519774060523000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNEPCzwa-XaRFxpJwgR8p_sJHeW11Q"&gt;http://www.&lt;wbr&gt;northroyaltonbandboosters.com/&lt;wbr&gt;page/volunteer-form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;We ask each family to support their student and the band by signing up for&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;at least four activities&lt;/strong&gt;. One of the reasons we have a great band is the high level of parent support and involvement. The majority of the funds needed to support the band (uniforms, instruments, etc.) come from these fundraisers.&amp;nbsp; Note that we will close individual activities once we have enough volunteers, so sooner is better than later if you prefer specific activities. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Registration Form&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://northroyaltonbandboosters.us15.list-manage.com/track/click?u=f9c4e414afe05390874757772&amp;amp;id=d345d5f8bb&amp;amp;e=79b990d89d" target="_blank" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;amp;q=https://northroyaltonbandboosters.us15.list-manage.com/track/click?u%3Df9c4e414afe05390874757772%26id%3Dd345d5f8bb%26e%3D79b990d89d&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1519774060523000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNGEPemWYwi3LdV9ALckskneBJwFWg"&gt;http://www.&lt;wbr&gt;northroyaltonbandboosters.com/&lt;wbr&gt;page/band-registration-form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;On this form, you will be filling out parent and student information, acknowledging policies and selecting the appropriate fees.&amp;nbsp; After filling out the form click Submit and you will be taken to PayPal to pay your fees and complete this portion of the registration process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please note:&amp;nbsp; There is a uniform section that asks for student measurements for incoming freshmen and for returning students unhappy with their uniform fit. &lt;strong&gt;If you do not provide this information a uniform cannot be preselected for your student and uniform pick-up and selection will be delayed.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For Band Front (Royalaires and Royalettes)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a student who participates in band for the full year, you need to register for band now. If they are selected for the band front, you will have additional band front fees that you will need to pay later via a Band Front Registration Form that will open up in May. If you have a student that only wants to participate in the band front, but not in the concert bands, you should wait and register using the Band Front Registration form in May after your student finds out if they are selected. You will then pay the course/participation/uniform fees plus the band front fees. Note that you may want to sign up for volunteer activities now since we close out activities once we reach the optimal number of volunteers. If you wait until May, you might not be able to sign up for your preferred volunteer activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or problems, please don’t hesitate to ask!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2018-02-26 18:02:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2018-02-26 18:34:04</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-registration-for-the-2018-2019-school-year</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>