<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Registration for the 2015-2016 School Year is Now Open</title>
  <description>Hello Band Families,
    It is time to register for the 2015-2016 band season. Registration will be </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It is time to register for the 2015-2016 band season. Registration will be taking place on-line over the next few weeks. The &lt;b&gt;deadline is April 2&lt;/b&gt;. All fees and information are needed at this time. All &lt;b&gt;payments are made though PayPal only&lt;/b&gt;. If you know of any parents of 8thgraders who will be in band next year, please forward this e-mail to them.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;To complete the process you must submit 2 forms (&lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/volunteer-form"&gt;Volunteer Form&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/band-registration-form"&gt;Band Registration Form&lt;/a&gt;). Please begin with the &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/volunteer-form"&gt;Volunteer Form&lt;/a&gt;. When you finish the Volunteer Form you will be taken directly to the Band Registration Form. If you have more than one student, register the first starting with the Volunteer Form (be sure to list all your students on the form) and for the rest go directly to the Band Registration Form using the link below. &lt;b&gt;Please Do NOT fill out the Volunteer form twice&lt;/b&gt;. It is a good idea to have your calendar and your student’s measurements (if they are a freshman or they were unhappy with their uniform fit last year) handy when you begin registration.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Once you have completed your registration you will receive three emails:&lt;/b&gt; One from PayPal with your payment information; and two from Band Boosters (one with your Volunteer information and one with your Band). We recommend saving these emails as they are your receipt for your registration and you may wish to refer to them later.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Please see below for important information about each form.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Volunteer Form:&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;We ask each family to support their student and the band by signing up for at least two activities. One of the reasons we have a great band is the high level of parent and family support and involvement. The majority of the funds needed to support the band (uniforms, instruments, etc.) come from these fundraisers. Note that we will close individual activities once we have enough volunteers, so sooner is better than later if you prefer specific activities.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="cta-purple buzz-out" href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/volunteer-form"&gt;Volunteer Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Registration Form:&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;On this form you will be filling out parent and student information and paying the band, course and activities fees.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="cta-purple buzz-out" href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/band-registration-form"&gt;Registration Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;There is a section for uniform measurement information.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If you are a returning student and you were happy with your uniform last year and your size has not changed, simply click the appropriate button and you will not have to provide measurement information.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If you are a freshman or you were unhappy with your uniform fit last year, make the appropriate selection and you will be asked to provide measurement information. If you don’t see the measurement portion of the form, make sure the appropriate gender is checked at the top of the form. The measurement information is needed to get an accurate estimate of sizes for required uniform and concert wear for next season. Have your student(s) and a cloth tape measure handy when you fill out this form.&lt;b&gt; If you do not provide this information a uniform cannot be preselected for your student and uniform pick-up and selection will be delayed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be sure to select the correct option for your student’s Band Registration Course and Activity Fees. If your student plays Flute, Clarinet, Alto Saxophone, Trumpet, or Trombone, choose Option 1 which does not include instrument rental. If your student plays French Horn, Baritone, Tuba, Percussion, Oboe (during Concert Season) or Bassoon (during Concert Season), choose Option 2 which includes instrument rental.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After filling out the form click Submit and you will be taken to PayPal to pay your fees and complete this portion of the registration process.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;For Band Front (Royalaires and Royalettes):&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a student who participates in band for the full year, you need to register now. If they make it into the band front, you will have extra band front fees that you will need to pay later via a Band Front Registration online form that will open up in May. If you have a student that only wants to participate in the band front, but not in the concert bands, then you should wait and register using the Band Front Registration form in May after your student finds out if they are selected. You will then also need to pay the class/activity/uniform fees plus the band front fees. Note that you may want to sign up for volunteer activities now since we close out activities once we reach the optimal number of volunteers. If you wait until May, you might not be able to sign up for your preferred volunteer activity.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or problems, please don’t hesitate to ask!&lt;br&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-02-25 19:02:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-03-05 12:26:40</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>registration-for-the-2015-2016-school-year-is-now-open</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>a70d94a8-5d3c-44aa-b4d6-29cb41d521c4</category>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>fa6094d0-c8e0-4964-8deb-b6349a6dd281</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>