<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Marching Band July Newsletter</title>
  <description>Happy Summer!
 
What a beautiful summer we are having this year! Hope you are able to enjoy the last</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Happy Summer!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;What a beautiful summer we are having this year! Hope you are able to enjoy the last few weeks before Marching Band Camp begins! Just a few dates and links you need to know as we move into August:&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Mr. Vitale’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;                
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Band Booster’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;            
&lt;li&gt;Band Booster Meeting: AUGUST 29 @ 7pm – Media Center&lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;li&gt;July 25-28 – Marching Band and Band Front Uniform distribution (See Below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aug 4 – Band Camp begins – Refer to Mr. Vitale’s website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aug 12 – Picture Day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aug 20 -21 – Easter Seals Drive (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aug 21 – Homeday Parade -- Refer to Mr. Vitale’s website as we near the date&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aug 22 – Parent Preview Night – Refer to Mr. Vitale’s website as we near the date&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 3-5 - Air Show (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Uniform Distribution&lt;/h3&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Marching Band uniforms will be distributed in room 310 from 5:30-8:30 on the following days:&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;                              
&lt;li&gt;July 25 Seniors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;July 26 Juniors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;July 27 Sophomores&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;July 28 Freshman&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Band Front uniforms will be distributed also from 5:30- 8:30 on the following day:&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
                                                &lt;li&gt;July 25 ALL Band Front&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The required Tshirts and polos will also be for sale at the uniform distribution. Tshirts are $10 and polos are $20. CASH or CHECK ONLY!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CONTACTS:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anthony Amato Marching Band 216-401-7763&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carolyn Srp Royalaires 440-582-1860&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jennifer Rozek Royalettes 440-241-4215&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amanda Kost Tshirts/Polos 440-864-6543&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Air Show&lt;/h3&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;The largest Band Booster fundraiser of the year is coming up fast – The Cleveland National Air Show September 3-5th.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;The North Royalton Band Boosters have provided manpower to the air show for many years and we are given preferential treatment by the organizers due to the large number of hard working and enthusiastic volunteers we offer. When fully staffed, this event earns the Band up to $10,000!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;In order to fully staff the air show and maximize our fundraising opportunity, we need to supply 80 volunteers each day of the air show. We will sell and collect tickets at the Plaza booth and at Gate 13, where we will also managing the parking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of you who have not worked the air show before, this is a great way to get to know your fellow band parents and have a fun time meeting people. Volunteering at the Air Show is usually a family event so moms, dads and siblings are all welcome along with our “Bandos.” Children must be 15 years of age to participate.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;To sign up for your slots, we have set up a form at www.signupgenious.com. All you need to do is select your day, indicate the number of volunteers in your group and provide a phone number and email address. All volunteers need to sign up on the SignupGenius link…. If you indicated that you would volunteer when you registered in the spring, THANK YOU, and please click the link below to choose your volunteer day!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/20f054ba8ab2ca1f49-nrband"&gt;Here is the link to our signup form&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note: Monday is usually the hardest day to fill so if you are available Monday, please select that day. Thank you to all the band parents who have already indicated you are planning on volunteering and to those who have yet to volunteer, please consider participating in this event.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CONTACT:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;         
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gary Diehl 440-915-1178&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Easter Seals Fundraiser – Help Us Fill The Truck&lt;/h3&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Please join us for our “Fill the Truck” event on August 20th and August 21st!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;North Royalton Band Boosters will partner with Easter Seals Northern Ohio to not only raise money for the North Royalton Marching Band, but also to help local children and adults with disabilities.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHO:&lt;/b&gt; We need YOU! Tell your friends, family, neighbors, churches, or anyone else looking to clear clutter and do something GOOD for a fine organization! We also need your help to man the truck! Please follow this link to volunteer for a 2 hour time slot! It is an easy way to help out the band! All volunteers need to sign up on the SignupGenius link…. If you indicated that you would volunteer when you registered in the spring, THANK YOU, please click the link below to choose your volunteer day!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.SignUpGenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-easter2"&gt;www.SignUpGenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-easter2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT:&lt;/b&gt; An Easter Seals truck will be parked west of the North Royalton Board of Education at 6579 Royalton Road to accept donations of clothing, blankets, towels, shoes, purses, stuffed animals, cloth lunchboxes and backpacks, etc. Even stained items can be recycled into something! The more items we donate, the more money we will raise! (*All donations are tax-deductible and you will receive a receipt when you drop off your items). Our goal is to collect over 1,500 large bags of cloth and raise over $3,000 to support our North Royalton Marching Band. We challenge every student to fill a bag with cloth items and return it to this event to support our fundraiser.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;In addition to the items listed above, Easter Seals will now be accepting&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;dishes/kitchenware&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;small picture frames/wall hangings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;small kids toys/games&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;knickknacks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;jewelry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;books/CDs/DVDs/VHS tapes&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;no encyclopedias or magazines please!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHEN:&lt;/b&gt; Saturday, August 20th from 9:00 am to 6:00 pm and Sunday, August 21st from 1:00 pm to 6:00 pm&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Start “stashing your stuff” in your bag and do something GOOD for NRHS Marching Band and children and adults with disabilities! You can use ANY bag for donations!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Contact:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Holly Michalke 216-926-8836&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;That is it for now!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Amanda Kost&lt;br&gt;NR Band Bootser President&lt;br&gt;440-864-6543&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-07-20 06:07:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-07-20 07:01:39</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>marching-band-july-newsletter</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>