<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Senior Band Night, State Finals and Such</title>
  <description>Congrats for earning a ‘SUPERIOR’ rating at Copley! On to Brunswick contest on Saturday: Performance</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Congrats for earning a ‘SUPERIOR’ rating at Copley!&lt;/b&gt; On to Brunswick contest on Saturday: Performance time: 7:45pm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sale Forms Are Due!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal Fruit Sale order forms are DUE NO later than October 18th. Once you have completed your sales, place your order with payments in the WHITE Band Box Attention: Jaime Poplin or Heidi Cmich. Any questions? Contact Jaime: 440-457-7417 or Heidi: 216-224-2968&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;DVD and CD Order Form for the 2017 State Finals and Marching Band Concert!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boosters will be offering two ways to remember the 2017 Marching Band season! In conjunction with SoundWaves of Cleveland, we will be offering a DVD of State Finals (the ONLY way to get a hard copy of the performance) and a CD recording of our Marching Band Concert! Please complete the attached order form and place your order in the white band box by NOV 3rd. We will only be ordering EXACTLY what we need… no extras!! Questions? Please contact: Amanda Kost: 440-864-6543&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Volunteers Needed for Senior Band Night!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are EXTREMELY short of volunteers for Senior Band Night…. Please consider volunteering a few hours of your time… our Senior parents will be enjoying a dinner with their bando as recognition for their four years of supporting the band program.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-20173"&gt;50/50&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;     
&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-20176"&gt;Concessions&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-20177"&gt;Senior Band Night&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Chaperones Needed&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are in need of chaperones for BOTH Brunswick Contest AND State Finals. Please consider &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-20175"&gt;volunteering for these events&lt;/a&gt;. You never have to worry about parking when you chaperone!&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;h3&gt;Volunteer Button on Band Booster Webpage&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An easy, one-stop volunteer location is now on the homepage of the Band Booster website. &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/volunteer-now"&gt;Click here to see every event this going on with open volunteer opportunities!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mark Your Calendar!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 18 – FRUIT SALE ORDERS ARE DUE!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 20 – HOME – Nordonia -- SENIOR BAND NIGHT&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 21 – Contest – Brunswick – Performance time: 7:45pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 27 – HOME – Cuyahoga Falls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 28 – STATES – HILLIARD DARBY HS – Performance time: 1:30pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 30 – BOOSTER MEETING – MEDIA CENTER @ 7PM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NOV 1 – Final Marching Band Concert – Gym 1 @ 7pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-10-16 20:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-10-16 20:22:28</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>senior-band-night-state-finals-and-such</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>