<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>It's Time To Turn In Your Uniform</title>
  <description>Dear Band Families,
 
Well, another marching band season has come to an end. What a great year again</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Well, another marching band season has come to an end. What a great year again! It is also time to turn in the marching band uniforms.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Uniforms will be turned in to the uniform room, room 310. It is on the first floor, located in the hallway behind the community room.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;UNIFORM TURN IN DATES:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;November 13, from 6:30 pm to 7:30 pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;November 14, from 6:30 pm to 7:30 pm.&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It would be appreciated if you can make every effort to return your uniform on these dates. However we understand there may be a few conflicts, just please contact us in advance to make other arrangements. If you have questions, please contact Anthony by email at &lt;a href="mailto:aja@aamatolaw.com"&gt;aja@aamatolaw.com&lt;/a&gt; or Joel by email at &lt;a href="mailto:joel.s.young@roadrunner.com"&gt;joel.s.young@roadrunner.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marching band uniforms must be DRY CLEANED. North Royalton Band Boosters will be paying for this cleaning ONLY IF you take your uniform to ON THE SPOT DRY CLEANING in Broadview Heights at the corner of Route 82 and Broadview Road, or in Parma at the corner of Pleasant Valley and State Roads. This would include the jacket, and both pairs of pants. Make sure you return the uniform in the plastic bag with the receipt attached.You will not be permitted to turn in your uniform unless it has been dry cleaned and you have the receipt. This is your responsibility!&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Remove the collar guard and machine wash at home. Remember to replace this on the jacket before returning your uniform.&lt;/li&gt;
 
&lt;li&gt;Wash your collar guard, rain coat, garment bag and, if applicable, your beret in cold water, gentle cycle and let them hang dry before you return them. Do not put the raincoat, beret, collar guard or garment bag in the dryer. Make sure all items are dry before uniform turn in night.&lt;/li&gt;· Wipe down your hat, inside and out, with a damp cloth.&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE FOLLOWING ITEMS MUST BE RETURNED ON UNIFORM TURN IN NIGHTS!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dry cleaned Uniform, including football pants, contest pants and jacket, in the plastic dry-cleaner bag with receipt attached.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clean and dry raincoat&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clean and dry garment bag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hat (Cleaned inside and out) or Beret&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Large plastic hanger the uniform came on when it was given out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beret, if applicable.&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;br&gt;The Uniform Committee&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-11-03 06:11:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-11-03 06:51:34</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>it-s-time-to-turn-in-your-uniform</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>