<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>A Superior Rating,State Finals,and Sales of Fruit,CDs,DVDs</title>
  <description>TWO wonderful events this week --- Senior Band Night was amazing--- thank you to Hospitality and the</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;TWO wonderful events this week --- Senior Band Night was amazing--- thank you to Hospitality and their team… wonderful memories for the Seniors…&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;AND a SUPERIOR rating at Brunswick – congrats to the Band and the Directors!&lt;/p&gt;
 

&lt;h3&gt;State Finals This Saturday at Hilliard Darby&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The final performance of the contest show ‘Of Wishes and Dreams’ will be this Saturday at Hilliard Darby High School at 1:30pm… Please consider making the trip to support our band! For all the details, please visit Mr. Vitale’s website and look under Performances :)&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sale Forms and Car Raffle Tickets are Due Now!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The due date has passed for both of these items. PLEASE get your forms and tickets into the white band box ASAP!!!! Thank you!!!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;DVD and CD Order Form for the 2017 State Finals and Marching Band Concert!&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;The Boosters will be offering two ways to remember the 2017 Marching Band season! In conjunction with SoundWaves of Cleveland, we will be offering a DVD of State Finals (the ONLY way to get a hard copy of the performance) and a CD recording of our Marching Band Concert! Please complete the attached order form and place your order in the white band box by NOV 3rd. We will only be ordering EXACTLY what we need… no extras!! Questions? Please contact: Amanda Kost: 440-864-6543&lt;/p&gt;
 
 
&lt;h3&gt;Volunteer Button on Band Booster Webpage&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An easy, one-stop volunteer location is now on the homepage of the Band Booster website. The button is top left and by clicking you can see every event this going on with open volunteer opportunities!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mark Your Calendar!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 27 – HOME – Cuyahoga Falls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 28 – STATES – HILLIARD DARBY HS – Performance time: 1:30pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 30 – BOOSTER MEETING – MEDIA CENTER @ 7PM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NOV 1 – Final Marching Band Concert – Gym 1 @ 7pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-10-25 07:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-10-25 07:19:32</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>a-superior-rating-state-finals-and-sales-of-fruit-cds-dvds</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>