<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>NRMB Newsletter – October 10, 2016</title>
  <description>Thank you to everyone that helped to make senior band night such a special evening for all the senio</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Thank you to everyone that helped to make senior band night such a special evening for all the senior families!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For all our Senior Parents, thank you for all you have done for the Band, Your Bando and the Band Boosters. IT IS APPRECIATED!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Support our band by attending our contest performance at Copley, October 15th at 7:00pm. You do not want to miss this show! It is FANTASTIC!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LINKS you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Mr. Vitale’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandboosters.com"&gt;Band Booster’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/North-Royalton-Band-Boosters/164850233634290"&gt;FaceBook North Royalton Band Boosters -- Like Us!!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other Fundraisers: GFS and Smile.Amazon.com (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;DATES you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oct 14 – Football game – AWAY Nordonia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oct 15 – Fruit sale order forms are due&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 15 – CONTEST – COPLEY Performance at 7:00pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oct 21 – Football game AWAY Cuyahoga Falls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 22 – CONTEST – BRUNSWICK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 24 – BAND BOOSTER MEETING -- 7PM MEDIA CENTER&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Car Raffle&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are still missing MANY car raffle tickets. Please check with your bando and return either sold or unsold tickets. We need to account for every ticket! Please place your envelope in the white band box asap.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sale --- Deadline: OCTOBER 15th&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Marching Band Fruit Sale is officially underway. If you need extra forms, they are in the band room. Forms are due back to the White Band box by October 15th! This is a firm deadline because we need to place our fruit order quickly to schedule delivery early December!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Other Fundraisers:&lt;/h3&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;GFS: If you shop at GFS, remember to mention: North Royalton Band Boosters and Marching Band at checkout. We have an account there and accumulate $$$$ for everything YOU spend!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Smile.Amazon Are you an Amazon shopper? Set up a SMILE.AMAZON account and a percentage of what you purchase will be added to the North Royalton Band Booster account:&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;YOU can help North Royalton High School Band Boosters when you shop for back-to-school supplies and many other items that you purchase from Amazon! This link will help you set up your SMILE account!.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Support us when you shop for back-to-school items. #StartWithaSmile at &lt;a href="http://smile.amazon.com/ch/34-1817202"&gt;http://smile.amazon.com/ch/34-1817202&lt;/a&gt; and Amazon donates.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-10-11 18:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-10-11 18:56:07</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>nrmb-newsletter-october-10-2016</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>