<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Booster Newsletter - Info on Districts, States, Registration and More!</title>
  <description>Hi Everyone,
 
We made it to Spring! It was a long and grueling winter, but clearly the directors an</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We made it to Spring! It was a long and grueling winter, but clearly the directors and the students were hard at work! After last week's showing at district band contest, it is quite apparent how unique our program has become. No other program in the northern 1/2 of the state was successful in achieving a Superior Rating (I) with all 4 competing bands. Because of this accomplishment, Freshman, Concert, Symphonic and Wind Ensemble all will be heading to State Band Competition on May 1 and 2! Congratulations kids!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;State Band Contest - Save the Date! - Fri. and Sat. May 1 and 2.&lt;/h3&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;State Band Contest will be hosted at Royalton once again this year. Not only is this a tremendous experience for our kids but it is also a fundraiser for us. There will be a need for MANY volunteers in order for this event to run smoothly. The volunteer needs are for...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Office staff (12 people)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bus parking (12 people)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ratings Collectors and Runners (12 people)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stage crew and announcers (16 people)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information desk and program distributors (8 people)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concessions (20 people).&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A grand total of 80 adult volunteers will be needed. Please plan to get involved. This is the perfect opportunity to join us! ALL of our children will be there! Come join the fun! We ask that you choose a 3-hour session that best fits your availability. If you can help either Friday or Saturday, please email me at &lt;a href="mailto:holly.rmc@gmail.com"&gt;holly.rmc@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;. The band directors do expect that the students sign up to help as well. More information will be coming regarding this event so please save the date!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Band Booster Meeting - Monday, March 30 at 7:00 pm in the High School Community Room -&lt;/h3&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Come join us! Especially if you are interested in getting involved in a committee or a board position. Our nominating committee will be hard at work preparing for elections in May. This is the time to get involved. Several of our committee chairs and board members are graduating with their children. The involvement can be very rewarding and it does allow us to support a truly tremendous band program and organization.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Band Registration for the 2015-16 School Year Is Underway -&lt;/h3&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;It is time to register! Please visit the &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/post/2015/02/25/registration-for-the-2015-2016-school-year-is-now-open"&gt;registration page&lt;/a&gt; and follow the procedures. It is a new format that is more user-friendly. Deadline is April 1st. Be sure to have your calendar ready in order to sign up for volunteer options as well.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Another Successful Raffle Fundraiser!&lt;/h3&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to Shirley Berish and Rima Chehade for organizing the Fundraiser and to Lynn Laurence, Kelly Albany and Regina Atkinson for getting such great prizes as well as all the helpers that ran the 50/50, sideboards and the behind the scene needs.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you on Monday, March 30!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-03-24 19:03:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-03-24 19:18:34</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-booster-newsletter-info-on-districts-states-registration-and-more</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>