<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>It's Our First Booster Meeting...Come Get The Scoop!</title>
  <description>First Booster Meeting of the Season
Stop in on Monday, Aug 28th in the Media Center at 7 pm for our </description>
  <content>&lt;h3&gt;First Booster Meeting of the Season&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stop in on Monday, Aug 28th in the Media Center at 7 pm for our first Booster Meeting… get caught up on what the board and committees are doing, order your Photo Buttons, turn in your Membership form and if you still need Tshirts or Polos, we can get them for you that evening! Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Become a Band Booster Member Now&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join the Band Boosters now! There are many membership levels to choose from and this year we have an ‘Add-On ’ item if you join the Boosters! &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/FILES%2f2017%2f08%2fNRHS-Band-Booster-Membership-2017-18.doc.axdx"&gt;Download the form following this link.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Return your membership form to: &lt;/b&gt;Parent Preview Night, the White Band Box or mail it in (the address is on the form)&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Please note: All chaperones and all chairpersons must be Booster members.&lt;/p&gt;
 
 
&lt;h3&gt;Air SHow and Chaperones&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a few hours out of your day to help us with Air Show and Chaperoning!! Follow these links for a description of the events and how to sign up to help us out!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-20172"&gt;&lt;b&gt;AIR SHOW&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-20175"&gt;&lt;b&gt;CHAPERONES&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  
 
&lt;h3&gt;Needed: Assistant Chairpersons for Various Committees&lt;/h3&gt;We are in need of a few parents to help out our committees. It is a lot of fun to work on these committees. You will meet wonderful parents and every minute of your time directly benefits our band program&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;To volunteer for a position:&lt;/b&gt; CONTACT AMANDA KOST: 4408646543 or &lt;a href="mailto:memandy@ameritech.net"&gt;memandy@ameritech.net&lt;/a&gt;. THANKS!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here is what we need:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;PHOTO BUTTONS –&lt;/b&gt; need a parent to help the chairperson with Picture Day, process the pictures, help make the buttons and distribute at home games. It is a lot of fun… especially making the buttons!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;50/50 RAFFLE – &lt;/b&gt;need a parent to assist our chairperson the nights of the home games. You would help check in our volunteers, distribute tickets to our volunteers to sell, collect money, tear tickets and help close out the raffle. Involvement is from 6 pm – halftime.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CHAPERONES – &lt;/b&gt;help chairperson to make sure all buses have chaperones. May require calling or emailing volunteers. Need to be able to chaperone the busses to away games and contests. It is a great way to meet the band and no worries about parking or driving to away events!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CONCERT UNIFORMS – &lt;/b&gt;need a parent to help the chairperson prepare the uniforms, distribute and collect for CONCERT season.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Mark Your Calendar!&lt;/h3&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;August 25 – Away – North Ridgeville&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;August 28 – BOOSTER MEETING – MEDIA CENTER 7pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 1 – Away – Parma Senior&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 2-4 – AIR SHOW – see below to volunteer!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 8 – HOME – Highland&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 9-10 – Fruit Sale Blitz Weekend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-08-25 06:08:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-08-25 06:25:00</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>it-s-our-first-booster-meeting-come-get-the-scoop</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>