<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>NRMB Newsletter – September 5 2016</title>
  <description>A very big thank you to everyone that volunteered at the AirShow! What a spectacular weekend to be d</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;A very big thank you to everyone that volunteered at the AirShow! What a spectacular weekend to be down there. Your donated time was greatly appreciated !!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LINKS you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Mr. Vitale’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandboosters.com"&gt;Band Booster’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/North-Royalton-Band-Boosters/164850233634290"&gt;FaceBook North Royalton Band Boosters&lt;/a&gt; -- Like Us!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other Fundraisers: GFS and Smile.Amazon.com (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;DATES you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sept 7: &lt;/b&gt;CONTEST HOODIE ORDERS DUE ! THIS IS A FIRM ORDER DATE!!!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sept 7 &lt;/b&gt;– Fruit sale packets will be going home&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sept 9&lt;/b&gt; – Football game AWAY&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sept 10-11&lt;/b&gt; – FRUIT SALE BLITZ!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sept 16&lt;/b&gt; – Football game HOME&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sept 17&lt;/b&gt; – Festival of Bands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sept 30&lt;/b&gt; – Car Raffle Tickets are DUE in white band box.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;After practice Wednesday, Sept 7, please pick up: FRUIT SALE PACKET, PHOTO BUTTONS and MEMBERSHIP ITEMS in Cafeteria 2!!!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Contest Hoodies&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The very last day to order your contest hoodie is SEPTEMBER 7TH --- NO exceptions. An order form is attached to this newsletter and can be found on the Band Booster webpage. See link above.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Membership&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our membership drive is underway! JOIN the Band Boosters! There are many membership levels! Print the form at the bottom of this newsletter OR go to &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/band-booster-membership"&gt;www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com and select the Membership button&lt;/a&gt; to get the form! If you are interested in becoming a GRAND STAFF member, your form is due SEPT 7th (because your membership includes the contest hoodie and that is the last day to order a contest hoodie) Questions?&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Contact: Shirley Berish – 440-667-0811&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Festival of the Bands - Volunteers Needed&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;North Royalton Band Festival is a great opportunity for our band and community to shine! This will be the first performance of the North Royalton High School Marching Band 2016 Contest Show: The Elements! We will host bands from around Northeast Ohio as they showcase their talent. Many hands are needed for an enjoyable evening of music and marching. Volunteer opportunities are easy and fun! Please sign-up to assist with one of our final fundraisers of the season. All volunteer duties will pause while NRHS performs so no one will miss the show! To volunteer, &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080948a9ac2aa75-nrhs"&gt;click on this link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;50/50 Raffle We Still Need Help&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did you hear how large our payout was on Sept 2? Larger than the first game and it is all due to you--- our volunteers! Let’s keep the payout growing!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We can use help with our next home game and Band Fest! Please &lt;a href="http://www.SignUpGenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-5050"&gt;click on this link&lt;/a&gt; or call Elisa. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
 

 
&lt;p&gt;Contact: Elisa Race -- 216-407-5625&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;North Royalton Stadium Foundation Car Raffle&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marching Band sales for the car raffle will begin on Tuesday, August 23rd and will end September 30th. Everyone should now have their raffle tickets. Please remember to turn in your sold tickets and payments in your car raffle envelope and place it in the white band box.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Contact: Jane Coleman – 440-759-9864&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h3&gt;Other Fundraisers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GFS: If you shop at GFS, remember to mention:&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;North Royalton Band Boosters and Marching Band at checkout. We have an account there and accumulate $$$$ for everything YOU spend!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Smile.Amazon Are you an Amazon shopper? Set up a SMILE.AMAZON account and a percentage of what you purchase will be added to the North Royalton Band Booster account:&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;YOU can help North Royalton High School Band Boosters when you shop for back-to-school supplies and many other items that you purchase from Amazon! This link will help you set up your SMILE account!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Support us when you shop for back-to-school items. #StartWithaSmile at &lt;a href="http://smile.amazon.com/ch/34-1817202"&gt;http://smile.amazon.com/ch/34-1817202&lt;/a&gt; and Amazon donates.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-09-06 17:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-09-06 18:06:27</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>nrmb-newsletter-september-5-2016</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>