<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Booster News - Halloween Candy, Booster Meeting, States, Concert and More</title>
  <description>Hi Everyone,
 
It will be nice to have a weekend off from contest. I hope all the kids have an oppor</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;It will be nice to have a weekend off from contest. I hope all the kids have an opportunity to enjoy it. The whole marching band is working so hard! If you haven't hugged your bando lately, give them a hug in support of all their efforts. No other organization offers quite the same experiences as marching band.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Home Game&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Friday will be the last home game of the season. Come check out the progress the group has made in the past week. It truly is incredible!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Halloween Candy&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have received a great response to our request for candy for the bandos this Halloween. Thank you to everyone who signed up.  Don’t forget to have your bando drop the candy off by Monday. It's also not too late to sign up. &lt;a href="www.signupgenius.com/go/10c0e49a4ac2ba4fc1-marching"&gt;If you are interested sign up here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Band Booster Meeting&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our next booster meeting will be held on Monday, Oct. 26, in the Media Center at 7 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;States&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have been given an 8:00 pm time slot on Oct. 31 in Columbus. Mr. Vitale has the details available on the &lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com/directors_notes"&gt;Director’s Notes page&lt;/a&gt;. Please make note of it. This is the latest we have played at STATES in my 4 years, which prevents us from making our traditional stop at Polaris in Columbus and has us arriving home after midnight. Please plan accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Marching Band Concert&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event, held on Nov. 4 in the gym at 7:00 pm, will mark the end of our 2015 season. This is always a fun (and warm) opportunity to hear our favorite music of the entire football/contest season. We hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sale Has Ended&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you to all that sold fruit! As soon as we know when the fruit will be harvested and sent to Ohio we will firm up the pick up date. It is usually in early December.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;See you at our upcoming events!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;br&gt;
Band Booster President&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-10-22 20:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-10-22 20:56:56</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-booster-news-halloween-candy-booster-meeting-states-concert-and-more</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>