<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Fruit Sale Pick Up is on Saturday and Monday</title>
  <description>Hello, Band Families!
 
Saturday, December 6th, from 8 am to 3 pm, or Monday, December 8th, from 6 p</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello, Band Families!
 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Saturday, December 6th, from 8 am to 3 pm, or Monday, December 8th, from 6 pm to 8 pm&lt;/b&gt;. We will be distributing it from the high school locker rooms, which are right behind the board of education offices, next to the stadium, on Route 82. You can park in front of the board offices and then walk between that building and the stadium.  We will be down just a little ways on the right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please remember these things:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each blitz day order will be filed under the team captain's name, so please make sure you know who that child is if you are picking up that order.
 
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Each customer is to receive a thank-you note with the fruit. You will get a stack of notes along with your order, so please give one to each customer on your list.  The team captain is ultimately responsible for insuring all fruit orders are delivered.
 
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;NEW THIS YEAR - BBYB (Bring Back Your Bags)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
We have to purchase the actual bags that are used for the 10 pound orders of fruit. They cost about $1.00 per bag and that comes directly out of our profit. Please help us save money next year by carefully opening your bags and then returning them to us. There will be a box in the band room so your child can bring back the bags and we will also have a box in the hallway just outside the auditorium during the holiday concerts. Thank you for helping us conserve and save money!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for helping us have a successful fruit sale! The profit from the sale is over $8,000! Your support will help insure the future of our band program. Enjoy your fruit!
 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Susie &lt;a href="tel:440-877-1299"&gt;440-877-1299&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;amp;  Karen &lt;a href="tel:440-213-6414"&gt;440-213-6414&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-12-03 18:12:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-12-03 18:39:51</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>fruit-sale-pick-up-is-on-saturday-and-monday</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>