<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Fill The Truck!</title>
  <description>Hello fellow band parents!
Our next Easter Seals fundraising event will take place during our holida</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello fellow band parents!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our next Easter Seals fundraising event will take place during our holiday concerts. Please share our event on all of your social media platforms (email, Facebook, Twitter, Instagram) that you use! So many people love this opportunity! The only thing that holds us back from filling the truck this holiday season is not getting the word out! We will have the info on our band website and Facebook. Please help us out by spreading the word! Just copy and paste.&lt;/p&gt;       
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please join us for our “Fill the Truck” event on Sunday, December 18th and Monday, December 19th!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;North Royalton Band Boosters will partner with Easter Seals Northern Ohio to not only raise money for the North Royalton Band program, but also to help local children and adults with disabilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHO: &lt;/b&gt;We need YOU! Tell your friends, family, neighbors, churches, or anyone else looking to clear clutter and do something GOOD for our community during this holiday season!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT:&lt;/b&gt; An Easter Seals truck will be parked at North Royalton High School, just outside of the Performing Arts Center 14713 Ridge Road to accept donations of clothing, blankets, towels, shoes, purses, stuffed animals, cloth lunchboxes and backpacks, etc. Even stained items can be recycled! The more items we donate, the more money we will raise! (*All donations are tax-deductible and you will receive a receipt when you drop off your items). Our goal is to Fill The Truck to capacity to support our North Royalton Band program. We challenge you to fill a bag with cloth items and donate it to our fundraiser this holiday season.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHEN: &lt;/b&gt;Sunday, December 18th from 12:00 pm until 2:00 pm and again from 4:00 pm until 7:00 pm. *between 2 pm and 4 pm donations can be left next to the truck as we will be enjoying the holiday performance of North Royalton’s finest musicians in the Performing Arts Center at this time. Monday, December 19th from 4:00 pm until 7:00 pm.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start “stashing your stuff” and do something GOOD for children and adults with disabilities while helping the North Royalton High School Band! You can use ANY bag for donations! No hard goods will be accepted at this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THANK YOU!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, come visit us at the Easter Seals truck and lend a hand! It's easy and fun work while connecting with our neighbors! &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/10c0a45a5a92ca4f49-easter/17896769"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here's the sign up genius link.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;br&gt;216-926-8836&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-12-10 07:12:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-12-10 07:53:19</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>fill-the-truck</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>