<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>A Note From Mr. Vitale</title>
  <description>Band Families,
 
Just a few reminders - because lots of things are happening as the school year draw</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Just a few reminders - because lots of things are happening as the school year draws to a close!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Royalette clinics begin this week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Royalaire clinics begin Thursday&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jazz Band I performs at Senior Honors and Awards Night on Thursday&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CYWS Auditions are Friday - right here at NRHS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watch your email for information about Band Tuxedo and Concert Dress turn in - reminder: Seniors WILL NOT have their exit card signed until ALL uniforms have been properly turned in&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Band Calendars and Band Camp Calendars have been distributed and also PDF’s have been posted online - please share with all family members - as all performances are required and attendance is mandatory at all events - so please copy and share with all family members and post on the refrigerator!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Royalton Music came into rehearsal today to fit and size students for band clothing - all band clothing orders should be made through Royalton Music - all payments for orders must be submitted by Friday - May 22 - Any order past this date will have a $10 shipping charge added&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reminder that the Memorial Day Parade is mandatory for all Freshman, Sophomores, and Juniors, but it is not required that seniors perform in this parade.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Even Juniors that are attending Prom MUST STILL perform at the Memorial Day Parade.  The parade is Monday, May 25 - the route starts at The Boneyard, and ends at the Broadview Community Center&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Students interested in auditioning for the OMEA All-State Band should have their application turned in by the end of the month&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-05-11 20:05:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-05-11 20:51:48</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>a-note-from-mr-vitale</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>