<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Fantastic Event</title>
  <description>Hi Everyone,
 
Did anyone notice the final set of our contest show last night? In case you did not s</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Did anyone notice the final set of our contest show last night? In case you did not see what I saw, it was a crescent moon. And it matched the crescent moon in the sky! Is it possible that Mr. Vitale and the design team planned our debut to match the current phase of the moon? Hmmm...&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;This was a busy weekend for us all. &lt;/b&gt;Wow, it is something special when you see an event like last night come off so well! The weather was perfect, the bands were spectacular, the audience was stimulated and we hosted like the class act that we are! There were many complements from our guests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Social media is a buzz with postings from our festival.&lt;/b&gt; A HUGE thanks to all that were involved with the planning, preparing and volunteering last night! Again, our kids see all that we do, which helps them put in perspective that what they do is really worth it. The community this creates alone is a huge reality. Not many school districts have what we have and it is largely because of you.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fundraising - &lt;/b&gt;With the exception of the fruit sale, the majority of our fall fundraisers are winding down. Although our membership drive is still active (please consider becoming a member of this fine organization if you haven't done so already) and still have 50/50 and button sales at the home games, we have successfully completed 2 Easter Seals drives, the air show, a band festival, car raffle, 1 Marching for Munchies gathering and our fruit sale blitz all in less than one month! Wow, that's amazing!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Now it's time to enjoy our kids during the upcoming contest season&lt;/b&gt;. October will be filled with Saturday performances of our Moonlight Reflections production. Our contest hoodies will be in just in time to wear to these events. I'm really looking forward to this next month. When traveling to the contest shows, try to sit together in the stands to form a "Sea of Purple" (wear purple or your spirit wear) to show our support. We will also see a return of our ROYALTON letters at some of the contest shows so be prepared to hold a letter. I look forward to seeing you there.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Moving forward from the booster side of things..&lt;/b&gt;.the fruit sale will be ongoing until October, as well as volunteering for concessions for home games, 50/50, pit crew and bus chaperones. Please let the chairperson know if you run into any conflicts so that spots can be filled with alternate volunteers. The number of spaces needed to run these components is carefully calculated, if we fall short it can be a problem.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Booster Meeting - &lt;/b&gt;Our next booster meeting will be held in the Media Center near Heritage Hall in the high school on &lt;b&gt;Monday, September 28 at 7 PM&lt;/b&gt;. Please come join us. Membership will be available as well as fruit sale fliers if you need extras.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Next Friday is Homecoming.&lt;/b&gt; Usually, after the game, our band performs the contest show. Plan to stick around to see the progress they have made.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thanks again, for all you do and see you at the games!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;br&gt;Band Booster President&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-09-23 19:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-09-24 18:51:58</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>fantastic-event</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>