<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>NoRo Schools Partner to Help Victims of Hurricane Harvey</title>
  <description>Dear Band Families,

North Royalton City Schools is partnering with Richard's Automotive Repair to h</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;North Royalton City Schools is partnering with Richard's Automotive Repair to help victims of Hurricane Harvey. The high school is collecting items in Heritage Hallway, and donations by check will be accepted in the main office or activities office through September 15. In addition, Richard's Automotive Repair and the schools will be collecting money and items for hurricane relief and the Red Cross at this Friday’s football game against Highland.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Suggested items to donate include the following.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New clothing (infant, toddler, children’s, men’s, women’s)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;new socks, underwear, shirts, t-shirts, hats, gloves&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;cases/pallets of water, Gatorade, juice boxes, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;can goods, non-perishable foods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;canned animal food, bags of dry animal food&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;cleaning supplies/bleach wipes, paper towels, glass cleaner, brooms, trash liners, trash cans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;toilet paper, soap, shampoo, tooth paste, tooth brushes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;kids books, coloring books, crayons, puzzles, play-doh, dolls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nerf balls of all kinds, matchbox cars, school supplies, back packs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;diapers any size, wipes, new baby bottles, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;kitchen supplies pot &amp;amp; pans cooking utensils, dish soap, dish rags&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;bath towels, wash cloths&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any monetary donations should be made by check payable to "American Red Cross."&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We would like to encourage all of our band families to contribute to this great cause if they can.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://campaign.r20.constantcontact.com/render?m=1103816735023&amp;amp;ca=dfd35d60-63fb-4ac3-8552-a730463009f4"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please click here for more information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-09-08 07:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-09-08 07:31:25</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>noro-schools-partner-to-help-victims-of-hurricane-harvey</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>