<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Fruit Sale Blitz Rescheduled</title>
  <description>REVISED FRUIT SALE BLITZ WEEKEND INFORMATION:

Due to the impending landfall of Hurricane Irma, proj</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;REVISED FRUIT SALE BLITZ WEEKEND INFORMATION:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to the impending landfall of Hurricane Irma, projected to hit Florida this weekend ‪through Tuesday as a Cat. 4 or 5, we have been advised by our fruit company to hold off on our Fruit Sale. We receive the majority of our citrus fruit for the sale from Florida. Until the hurricane has passed, we will not know how our growers will be impacted.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We will be rescheduling our Blitz Packet Handout to ‪Wednesday September 20th. Band members will still be reporting to Cafeteria 2 after 6-9 practice. We still need volunteers for the hand out that day ‪from 8:30pm - 9:30pm. Please see the revised Sign Up Genius to volunteer.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We will be doing our Fruit Sale Blitz on Saturday, September 23rd. (We do realize some of you may have prior commitments for that day such as Cross Country meets etc. These students may also sell on Sunday the 24th as well. We will be available on Monday the 25th after Band practice by the Band room to collect those few Blitz packets as well.)&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;The schedule for the 23rd is pictured below and is also on &lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com/performances.html" style=""&gt;Mr. Vitale's website&lt;/a&gt;. We will hold our Blitz Packet turn in and Pizza Party (on September 23rd) after the Band Members have reported for the Twinsburg football game. We need volunteers for this day to help with packet collection and pizza from 4pm - 5:30pm Please see the revised Sign Up Genius to volunteer.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-20179" class="cta-purple buzz-out"&gt;Volunteer Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We will be handing out packets for the Personal Fruit Sale after 6-9 practice on September 27th.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We very much appreciate your flexibility, understanding, and support with these unexpected changes. If you have any questions, don't hesitate to contact us. Please keep our growers and all the families in the path of this hurricane in your thoughts. This could be a catastrophic situation for all of those in the path of this destructive monster which could cause loss of lives, homes and livelihoods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;br&gt;Jaimie Poplin ‪228-217-8084, jaimie.poplin@gmail.com&lt;br&gt;and Heidi Cmich ‪216-224-2968 heidi.cmich@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-09-06 19:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-09-06 19:26:59</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>fruit-sale-blitz-rescheduled</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>a70d94a8-5d3c-44aa-b4d6-29cb41d521c4</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>