<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Booster News</title>
  <description>Hello NoRo Nation Band Parents,
 
Congratulations to all of our kids! A Superior Rating, Grand Champ</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello NoRo Nation Band Parents,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to all of our kids! A Superior Rating, Grand Champions, Best Music in Class AA, Best Music Overall, Best General Effect Overall, Best General Effect in Class AA and Best Auxiliary in Class AA. What a great representation of our school and community! Even though the weather was less than enjoyable, listening and watching our kids perform was. They made sitting in the cold, wind and rain worth it.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Since many people ask how our band is evaluated, I thought including the process from the OMEA website in this newsletter might be helpful.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;OMEA (&lt;a href="www.omea-ohio.org"&gt;Ohio Music Education Association&lt;/a&gt;) –&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This circuit is governed by the Ohio Music Education Association.  Classification of bands is determined by school size in grades 10-12 and includes C, B, A, and AA. NRHS is in the largest school class as class AA.  Judges at OMEA events include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; 
&lt;li&gt;2 Music Judges – 90 points each (then averaged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 Percussion Judge – 10 points (added to averaged music score to total 100)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 Visual Performance Judge - 50 points &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 Visual Effect Judge – 50 points &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 General Effect Judges- 100 points each (then averaged )&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 Auxiliary Judges (color guard) – 100 points (then averaged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 7 main judges (excluding the auxiliary) are totaled for 300 total points.  Ratings (I = Superior to V = Poor) are slightly more complicated… The overall band rating is determined by the total ratings given by each of the 7 main judges. Their individual ratings must fall in a certain point range for their caption. You need an 80% or higher in a caption to receive a Superior rating, so a GE score must be 80 or above, and a Music score must be 72 or above, etc. The final rating is determined by adding up all the judge’s ratings. 7 Superiors (1s) would equal 7 points and would be a Superior rating. Any added combination of ratings up to 10 points is an overall “Superior” (I) Rating. 11-14 would be an overall “Excellent” (II) rating, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;State Finals Competition &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any band receiving a Superior Rating at a local competition qualifies for the OMEA Marching Band State Finals. This event is held in late October or Early November.  At State Finals bands perform for ratings only as a culminating event for the season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, based on this information, we must have scored quite well since we have already qualified for states!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h2&gt;Band Booster News&lt;/h2&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sale&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The deadline is Oct. 17. Please continue to sell fruit. If you need more forms, they are located in the band room or at our band booster table at the home football games. You can also find them on our website.
 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Membership/hoodies/buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hoodies have been delivered. Buttons have been distributed. They look great! Thanks to Shirley Berish, Rima Chehade and Nancy Chester for their efforts. The membership drive is still going on and buttons are still available online. If you haven't joined, please check the website for contact information and forms. You can print off a membership form and send it in with your bando who can then drop it in the white band box.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;A few membership levels include tickets to our holiday concert, so don't miss out!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Hand Warmers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are selling hand warmers for $1.00 for the rest of the football season. These will be available at the home games at the band booster table.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Upcoming Events&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week we travel to Brecksville on Friday for football and to Norton for contest on Saturday. Hopefully, the weather will be more enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;The following week, (Oct. 16) is Senior Band night at halftime. Prepare to stick around to watch the kids perform the contest show after the game.
 &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a busy season for us all! I look forward to seeing you at our upcoming events.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;br&gt;
Band Booster President&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-10-05 19:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-10-05 19:55:08</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-booster-news</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>