<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Oranges,Apples,Pears...and Cheesecake!</title>
  <description>Dear Band Families,
 
The marching band's annual fruit sale will be starting next month.  This is a </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;The marching band's annual fruit sale will be starting next month.  This is a major fundraiser for the band and will be a huge success with everyone's participation.  We will be offering navel oranges, grapefruit, tangelos, apples, pineapples, pears, and new this year... STRAWBERRY SWIRLED CHEESECAKE!! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please make a note of the following:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fruit Blitz Weekend- September 9th &amp;amp; 10th &lt;/b&gt;– All students sell door to door in groups of two or three in our local neighborhoods.  The ACT Test is Saturday, the 9th, but students can sell any time during that weekend.  All fruit orders and collected money are due on Monday, September 11th.  The kids will be treated to pizza and drinks after band that day for working so hard over the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Personal Sale-&lt;/b&gt; Once the blitz packets are collected, each student will receive a new packet to gather orders from friends and family members.  The very last day orders will be accepted is October 14th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information to follow soon.  Please check your email and/or Facebook and the Band Boosters Website to stay on top of the events as they get closer. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you!!      &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heidi Cmich 216-224-2968
&lt;br&gt;
Jaimie Poplin 228-217-8084&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-08-16 21:08:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-08-16 21:10:52</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>oranges-apples-pears-and-cheesecake</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>