<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Beverage Resquest for State Band Contest Concessions</title>
  <description>Dear Freshman Band Family Members,
 
On Friday, May 1 and Saturday, May 2 North Royalton High School</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Freshman Band Family Members,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;On Friday, &lt;b&gt;May 1&lt;/b&gt; and Saturday, &lt;b&gt;May 2&lt;/b&gt; North Royalton High School will host the OMEA Ohio State Band Adjudicated Event. Cafeteria 2 will be open to students and parents serving food and beverages such as pizza, Chick-Fil-A sandwiches, muffins, donuts, chips, water, Gatorade/Powerade and other assorted items. This event is a Fundraiser for the band.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;We are asking the Freshman families to donate the following based on the letter of your last name:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="line-height: 1.428571429;"&gt;A – R - 12 - 20 oz. bottles of Gatorade/Powerade (Also G2)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="line-height: 1.428571429;"&gt;S – Z - 24 - cans of pop – Please get some diet as well&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;For those families interested in donating more, we can use anything pre-packaged. Rice Krispy Treats, Granola Bars, Muffins. Anything you donate becomes a profit for the band.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donations can be dropped off at 11127 Malvern Dr. in Southhampton Woods Development any time after Wednesday, April 22 in the bin located by the garage. If possible please bring it before Wednesday, April 28. Please put your last name on the package.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;E-mail or call with questions: Holly Michalke 216-926-8836&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thank you so very much for donation and your support!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Regards, Holly Michalke&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-04-19 21:04:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-04-19 21:11:37</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>beverage-resquest-for-state-band-contest-concessions</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
    <category>fa6094d0-c8e0-4964-8deb-b6349a6dd281</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>