<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>We Need Your Help September 19</title>
  <description>Hi Everyone,

Band Festival is next week on Saturday, September 19th, and it will be an entertaining</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Band Festival is next week on Saturday, September 19th, and it will be an entertaining evening of music! We are expecting 8 GUEST bands, most from our neighboring communities and with the bands we are expecting a large crowd for the event so we are asking for YOUR help in the areas of:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Ticket Sales and Collection --&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;North and South Gates. This is a fast paced but simple job. We provide cheat sheets for all the ticket combinations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Ushers --&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep the areas assigned for visiting bands clear and help seat people who need assistance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Concessions --&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We need additional help with concessions. If you are not sure if you signed up for Band Festival concessions, please contact Dawn Rembowski at 216-990-0271 or &lt;a href="mailto:dawnrembowski@att.net"&gt;dawnrembowski@att.net&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Program sales --&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We need additional help with program sales and 50/50 raffle. If you are not sure if you signed up for 50/50 Raffle and Program Sales, please contact Elisa Race at 216-407-5625 or &lt;a href="mailto:erace@wideopenwest.com"&gt;erace@wideopenwest.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Easter Seals 'Fill the Truck'---&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We need volunteers to 'man' the truck for our 2nd Fill the Truck. Please consider helping. Shifts are only 1.5 hours! Please contact Amanda Kost at 440-864-6543 for more info.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can use quite a few volunteers in EACH of the areas. Please consider taking the time to volunteer and help the North Royalton Marching Band…. it is a wonderful time to meet other band families! To sign up to volunteer, click on the link below. Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054eafa729a02-nrhs" class="cta-purple buzz-out"&gt;Signup to Volunteer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;*Please Note: On some mobile devices it takes a while for all the information to come up. You may want to visit this link on a computer.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-09-13 07:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-09-13 07:53:16</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>we-need-your-help-september-19</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>a70d94a8-5d3c-44aa-b4d6-29cb41d521c4</category>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>