<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Front Registration Instructions</title>
  <description>Hello Band Front Families,

It is time to register for the 2015-2016 band season. Registration will </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Band Front Families,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is time to register for the 2015-2016 band season. Registration will be taking place on-line over the next few weeks. The deadline is June 29. All fees and information are needed at this time. All payments are made through PayPal only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To complete the process, you must submit 2 forms (&lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/band-front-registration"&gt;Band Front Registration Form&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/volunteer-form"&gt;Volunteer Form&lt;/a&gt;). Once you have completed your registration you will receive three emails: One from PayPal with your payment information; and two from Band Boosters (one with your Band Front information and one with your Volunteer information). We recommend saving these emails as they are your receipt for your registration and you may wish to refer to them later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Band Front Registration Form:&lt;/h3&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;On &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/band-front-registration"&gt;this form&lt;/a&gt; you will be filling out parent and student information and paying the band front, course and activities fees. Be sure to select the correct option for your student’s NRHS Band Front Fees.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose Option 1 if you have already registered and paid your band course and activities fees using the Band Registration Form. You only need to pay the Band Front Fee. This usually happens when a student participates in band for the full year (i.e. he/she plays an instrument during the year when it is not marching band season).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose Option 2 if you need to pay all the necessary fees (band course and activity fees and the band front fee). This usually happens when a student only participates in band front (i.e. does not play an instrument during the year).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After filling out the form click Submit and you will be taken to PayPal to pay your fees and complete this portion of the registration process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Volunteer Form:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We ask each family to support their student and the band by &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/volunteer-form"&gt;signing up for at least two activities&lt;/a&gt;. One of the reasons we have a great band is the high level of parent and family support and involvement. The majority of the funds needed to support the band (uniforms, instruments, etc.) come from these fundraisers. Note that we will close individual activities once we have enough volunteers, so sooner is better than later if you prefer specific activities.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;When you finish the &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/volunteer-form"&gt;Volunteer Form&lt;/a&gt; you will be taken Band Registration Form. Do NOT fill out the Band Registration Form. You are done registering, just close the browser window.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or problems, please don’t hesitate to ask!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-05-21 20:05:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-05-22 07:20:22</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-front-registration-instructions</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>fa6094d0-c8e0-4964-8deb-b6349a6dd281</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>