<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Booster Newsletter 11/2</title>
  <description>Hello Parents!

It has been such a busy week! The bandos had auditions for concert season, the last </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Parents!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been such a busy week! The bandos had auditions for concert season, the last football game of the season and their trip to State Marching Band Finals. The seniors sure have a lot to be proud of with many lasting memories of the last four years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to our fine 2014 Marching Band! This was our 25th year in a row of receiving a "1" (Superior) at States!...even with some of the most adverse conditions possible. And we have 75 straight "1" ratings at competitions!  Such a great tradition of excellence! It was nice to see Mr. Becerra, Mr. Gurka and Dr. Kelly supporting us and cheering us on in Columbus!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for all the hard work and dedication to the Pit Crew volunteers. They come early, work in all weather conditions, stay late and are some of our biggest fans!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A special thanks to Becky Cozzens for organizing and distributing Halloween candy to the band Friday after the game! The kids were very appreciative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday is the last after school gathering for this season. Marching band students will be going to the middle school to perform and then returning to the high school to listen to the judges’ tapes from state band competition.&lt;/p&gt;

This Wednesday night is our Marching Band concert in the High School gym and will be the final performance of the marching band music. This concert will be professionally (audio) recorded. Forms will be available at the door of the gym. Only 75 CD's will be made. The concert starts at 7 pm. Check Mr. Vitale's website for complete details.&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Car raffle tickets are now past due. If your band student has not turned in the money or returned the tickets to the white box please do so as soon as possible! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marching band uniform turn in information will be coming soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don't forget to vote on Tuesday.  This bond issue directly affects our kids. Our vote is very important. Mr. Vitale announced at our booster meeting that the practice parking lot WILL be reconditioned with the money generated from this bond money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See you at the Marching Band Concert!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-11-03 19:11:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-11-03 19:10:56</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-booster-newsletter-11-2</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>