<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>50-50 Raffle Volunteers Needed</title>
  <description>Hello Everyone!

    Welcome to another football season! We are in need of approximately 5 more peop</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Welcome to another football season! We are in need of approximately 5 more people for each home game to help with selling tickets. It's a fun job and the commitment is only until right before halftime during home games.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Details below include a specific job description...&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;We meet at the Stadium entrance by the board office at 6:00. Sign in at the gate. You don’t have to pay to enter the game, so don’t buy a ticket. We have a table and chairs right inside that gate to the left. Selling takes place from 6:30 until shortly before the half time. We usually stop selling when the second quarter has 3 minutes left on the clock. You will be done in plenty of time to watch the band preform. If you have never done this before, don’t worry they are very easy to sell! We need a minimum of 10 people selling to do a good job!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;If you have any questions please call me at 216-407-5625. Brenda Calovini is the co-chair for the raffle and she will also be there every game so please look for both of us!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This week’s sellers are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Amanda or Steve Kost&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Bruce or Dianne Difrancisco&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Dan or Nancy Kyle&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Brad or Emily Fraser&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Holli Milsap&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Michelle or Jason Grimes&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;We could really use at least 2 more sellers for the first game and 5 more for the other 4 home games, so if you are available please let me know!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Also, this week only...we are having a get together at the “3 Spot" starting at 4:30 and they are hoping to sell raffle tickets there. Think of this like a band booster pep rally!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Thank you, and see you Friday night!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;
        Elisa Race
        &lt;a href="tel:216-407-5625"&gt;216-407-5625&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-09-03 11:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-09-03 11:49:04</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>50-50-raffle-volunteers-needed</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>