<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>A Message From Mr. Vitale</title>
  <description>Dear Band Families
 
On behalf of the Band Boosters, I just wanted to remind parents that we still n</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Families&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;On behalf of the Band Boosters, I just wanted to remind parents that we still need volunteers for this weekend’s Air Show. We have slots that need to be filled for Saturday, Sunday, and Monday. It is not hard work, there are plenty of breaks, and lunch is provided! You can even make an event of it with your student, because they can help as well (as long as they are over 15) and then you guys get to see the Air Show while you are helping out!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;You can &lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandboosters.us15.list-manage.com/track/click?u=f9c4e414afe05390874757772&amp;amp;id=ad8e97c2ae&amp;amp;e=79b990d89d"&gt;&lt;b&gt;signup online using our form&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;You can also call and contact Gary Diehl 440-915-1178 or Amanda Kost 440-864-6543 if a phone call is easier.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;This is one of our biggest fundraisers for the Band - and if we are not able to fully staff it, then we run the risk of not being invited to run it in the future. This is a great opportunity that many sports and organizations would love to have, and we are very fortunate to have this fundraiser - so let’s work hard to make sure we can hold onto it! Any time you can give towards this fundraiser is greatly appreciated and directly benefits your student. Please use the link to sign up or call one of the above people to help with this. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;-Mr. V.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-08-28 07:08:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-08-28 07:15:20</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>a-message-from-mr-vitale2</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
    <category>fa6094d0-c8e0-4964-8deb-b6349a6dd281</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>