<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Cleveland Air Show</title>
  <description>Dear Band Families
 
As summer gets into full swing we would like you to check your calendars for La</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Families&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;As summer gets into full swing we would like you to check your calendars for Labor Day weekend, September 5, 6 &amp;amp; 7. We need at least 80 volunteers each day for the Cleveland Air Show. Please consider volunteering to help with this event if you are available any day. This is our largest fundraiser for the band. If we fill all the spots we can earn $10,000, AND it involves minimal planning and other resources. Volunteers just need to show up and collect/sell tickets from the general public walking or driving in to enjoy the show. Volunteers can be any family members or friends as long as they are high school age or older.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;This year we are using &lt;a href="www.SignUpGenius.com/go/70A0C4DACAE29AB9-cleveland/"&gt;SignUp Genius to register volunteers&lt;/a&gt;. Please follow &lt;a href="www.SignUpGenius.com/go/70A0C4DACAE29AB9-cleveland/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;this link to register&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; if you can help on any or all of the days. After completing the SignUp you will receive an email confirmation from SignUp Genius. Additionally SignUp Genius will send updates and reminders as the event approaches.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE NOTE:&lt;/strong&gt; Families who volunteered for the Air Show when they registered their student for band will find that their information is already entered into the SignUp. These families do not need to sign up again.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;If you would like to know more about this event, please contact Becky Cozzens at &lt;a href="mailto:thecozzens@yahoo.com"&gt;thecozzens@yahoo.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-06-20 06:06:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-06-20 06:25:19</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>cleveland-air-show</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
    <category>fa6094d0-c8e0-4964-8deb-b6349a6dd281</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>