<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Booster Newsletter Week 4</title>
  <description>Hi Parents,

                 Welcome to week #4 of Marching Band Season!  This week proves to be a </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Parents,&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt; Welcome to week #4 of Marching Band Season!  This week proves to be a busy one with the Fruit Sale blitz winding down, the car raffle ticket sale beginning on Wednesday, a home game on Friday and our Booster Hosted Band Festival on Saturday.  Please check the director’s page for details about our upcoming performances.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sale&lt;/h3&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Although the Blitz was this past weekend, &lt;b&gt;the fruit sale continues until October 17&lt;/b&gt;.  Please continue to offer fruit to relatives, people at work, or neighbors that may have been missed during the blitz. This is a very profitable fund raiser for our kids and band program.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;h3&gt;Car Raffle&lt;/h3&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Each year band students are asked to sell car raffle tickets.  Half of the ticket price goes to our Band and the other half goes to the Stadium Foundation.  The grand prize is a car from Serpentini Chevrolet.  Band students will get their tickets on Wednesday after band in Cafe 2.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;h3&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Buttons will be available for pick up at the main entrance (north entrance) from 6:30 until halftime at this Friday's home game. If anyone is interested in ordering buttons, please contact Nancy Chester at &lt;a href="mailto:n.chester@sbcglobal.net"&gt;n.chester@sbcglobal.net&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;h3&gt;Uniforms for Band Festival&lt;/h3&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Be aware that students are expected to wear contest pants for Saturday's performance. Please try them on before Saturday to make sure they don’t need to be fixed, hemmed, etc.  Also, be sure to check &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonhighschoolband.com/"&gt;Mr. Vitale's page&lt;/a&gt; for specific details on contest attire.&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you at the game on Friday! And bring your family and friends to the Band Festival on Saturday and our first view of Celebration of The Seasons contest show!  Just remember to wear your band spirit wear!&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-09-16 20:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-09-16 20:26:58</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-booster-newsletter-week-4</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>