<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Boosters Newsletter - Parent Mixer, Air Show, Picture Day, Easter Seals and More!</title>
  <description>Hello Parents!

    Is it August already?  Why is summer so short and winter so long? I would imagin</description>
  <content> &lt;p&gt;Hello Parents!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Is it August already? Why is summer so short and winter so long? I would imagine many of your bandos came home with some interesting tan/burn lines on Friday. One parent mentioned to me to be sure to get my son's hair cut before summer band camp or he will have an interesting tan line for school pictures when they do get it cut! As a mom of a freshman boy, I took her advice!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Band students learned Pregame! Now it's on to halftime! Band music checkoffs are in full swing! It's amazing to me how dedicated these kids are to memorizing their music to secure a spot on the 100% board! I would imagine there will be someone on that board by the end of rehearsal on Monday! The more kids on that board, the louder and better we sound! GO BANDOS!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Water, Water and more Water! - Be sure kids come WELL HYDRATED to rehearsal. Starting the day well hydrated makes a long rehearsal day easier to manage. Water breaks help, but coming to rehearsal well hydrated is the key! Sports drinks and water are the best way to achieve this. Caffeine and carbonated beverages actually are NOT a good solution. Please pass this information on to your child.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Parent Mixer -&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Thursday, Aug. 13 - Mark your calendars for some fun!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Our parent mixer is next week, Thurs. Aug 13 from 6-9 at The 3 Spot. Come join us for some food, drinks and fun! We'd like to get to know you!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Air Show Update -&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Although there are some new people signing up, it is still not full. We need about 20 people for Sunday and 65 for Monday. We are asking you to do 2 things...&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ol&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;If your bando is planning on helping, please be sure they are signed up so we have an accurate count of our volunteers.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;If you haven't signed up, please check your calendar and join us! It is a great way to get to know the rest of the band family!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Here is &lt;a href="www.SignUpGenius.com/go/70A0C4DACAE29AB9-cleveland/"&gt; the link to sign up&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Picture day - Wednesday morning, Aug. 12.&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Paperwork was sent home with your bando this past Thursday. Students wear their FULL uniform. If you have not picked up your uniform or are missing any uniform accessories (ie. shoes, white shirt, long black dress socks, gloves) please be sure to take care of this NOW!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Membership -&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Membership into our Band Boosters is an opportunity to show your support for all the hard work your child contributes to our outstanding band. This is where we sell our spirit wear. The first opportunity to do this is at our Parent Mixer on Thursday, Aug. 13 from 6-9 at The 3 Spot.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Buttons -&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;Pictures for band buttons will be taken on Picture Day as well. This is separate from the photography company. This is a booster fundraiser, and will be available for you to purchase during the first few weeks of band. More details will be forthcoming. Attention All Seniors- we will need a picture taken this day for the Senior Night program.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Car Raffle -&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;These tickets were given to your bando during uniform distribution. PLEASE DO NOT LOSE THESE! You are responsible to sell or return these tickets. However, if a ticket is returned it is a $10 loss to our booster organization.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Easter Seals –&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;On August 22 (9am-6pm) and August 23 (1pm-6pm) we will be hosting a “Fill the Truck” fundraiser. The truck will be parked next to the North Royalton Board of Education and we will be collecting any and all cloth items. We will be compensated based on how much we collect. We need volunteers to help man the truck in 1.5 hour shifts. If you can help &lt;a href="www.SignUpGenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-easter"&gt;please sign up here&lt;/a&gt;. If you have any questions, please feel free to contact Amanda Kost &lt;a href="mailto:atamandabethkost@gmail.com"&gt;atamandabethkost@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or at 440-864-6543&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Volunteering -&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you follow the &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/contact"&gt;Contact link on our website&lt;/a&gt;, you will see a list of our Officers as well as a list of Committees and Committee Chairs. Here is where you will find the many different ways we work to support our kids! If you have not gotten involved but are interested, please don't hesitate to reach out to one of these people to offer your support. It truly takes a village to raise an award-winning marching band like ours! The work you do for these kids is so rewarding!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Old White Band T Shirts -&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have an old white band t-shirt you no longer use, and it is in good condition, please stop down to the booster room during uniform distribution on Monday 4-8 pm or find a uniform volunteer during picture day. Please be sure it is laundered! We could use a few extras for emergencies.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Florida Trip -&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;It's a trip year! Information is posted on the home page of Mr. Vitale’s website, &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;www.northroyaltonhighschoolband.com&lt;/a&gt;. Please check his page regularly for more details!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;I look forward to seeing you at The 3 Spot on Thursday, August 13!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;br&gt;North Royalton Band Booster President&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-08-04 07:08:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-08-04 07:39:37</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>and-boosters-newsletter-parent-mixer-air-show-picture-day-easter-seals-and-more</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>