<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Booster Newsletter with Important Reminders &amp; Updates</title>
  <description>As another marching band season comes to an end, I would like to thank the Concessions Chairs - Moni</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;As another marching band season comes to an end, I would like to thank the Concessions Chairs - Monica Hrin, Darlene Kelly and Tammy Patrick, Hospitality Chair - Amanda Kost, Membership Chairs - Shirley Berish and Rima Chehade, Festival of Bands Chair – Beth Burdick, Visiting Band Chair - Kim Kozempa, 50/50 Chair - Elisa Race, Chaperone Chairs - Susanna Schwab and Lynn Marencik, Badge a Minute Chair - Nancy Chester, Uniform Chairs - Michelle Kelly, Vicky Turske and Anthony Amato, and Pit Crew Chiefs Bob Franko and Rich Hrin for all your time, dedication and commitment to our program and our kids! What a fantastic season it has been!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;IMPORTANT REMINDERS &amp;amp; UPDATES:&lt;/h3&gt;
 
&lt;h4&gt;Marching Band Uniform Turn In – &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turn in is this Friday (11/21) from 6pm to 8pm and Monday (11/24) 6pm to 8pm in the NEW UNIFORM ROOM, ROOM 310.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h4&gt;Marching Band Concert CDs and 25th Anniversary T-shirts - &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Orders are due Friday (11/21). You can download the order forms from the homepage of the Booster website, &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com"&gt;northroyaltonbandboosters.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h4&gt;Band Booster Meeting – &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our next meeting is Monday, November 24, at 7pm in the High School Community Room.  This is the last meeting until January.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h4&gt;Fruit Sale Update - &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now we are on the schedule with Florida River Groves to have our fruit delivered the first week in December.  We will not have a more accurate date until right around that time.  Keep watching your email, the band website and Facebook for updates.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h4&gt;Holiday Concerts - &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our holiday concerts will be Sunday, Dec.14th at 2pm and 7pm and Monday, Dec. 15th at 7pm. The ticket order form can be found on Mr. Vitale’s website under &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonhighschoolband.com/forms__pdfs"&gt;Forms &amp;amp; PDFs&lt;/a&gt;. Make sure to order tickets for the correct concert. Different bands play at different concerts. For example the Freshmen/Concert band plays in both the concerts on Sunday, but not in the concert on Monday. Also, Remember to subtract the cost of 2 tickets if you joined Band Boosters at a level that included tickets.  There is a line for that on the form.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h4&gt;Holiday Ornaments - &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Holiday Ornaments will only be sold at the Holiday Concerts this year (December 14 and 15).  They will be $10 each.  See the attached flyer for a picture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/FILES%2f2014%2f11%2fBandOrnament-11-2014.pdf.axdx"&gt;BandOrnament-11-2014.pdf (104.1KB)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h4&gt;Raffle Fundraiser Event - &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SAVE THE DATE! The Band Booster Raffle Fundraiser Event will be on Saturday, February 28, at the 3 Spot. More information will be coming soon.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h4&gt;States DVDs – &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, BandVideos had a power outage during our performance at States.  They are no longer taking orders for DVDs.  If you ordered a DVD they are refunding the $30 and they will also be sending a DVD of the parts of the performance that they have.  Kevin Brewer posted a video of the performance here 2014 North Royalton State Marching Band Competition. A Seasonal Celebration.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to hearing the bands this holiday season. Stay warm and safe! Be glad we don't live in Buffalo!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-11-20 11:11:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-11-20 12:01:59</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-booster-newsletter-with-important-reminders-and-updates</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>