<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>NRHS Band News - Band Camp starts next week, Aug 3rd!</title>
  <description>Band Camp starts next week, Aug 3rd!
UNIFORM distribution next week – READ BELOW!!!!

Marching Band </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Band Camp starts next week, Aug 3rd!&lt;br&gt;
UNIFORM distribution next week – READ BELOW!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Marching Band Uniform Distribution&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marching Band / Band Front Uniforms will be distributed in ROOM 310 (up by the Community Room) according to the following schedule:&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
                  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 2&lt;/b&gt; – 5:30 – 7:30p – SENIORS&lt;/li&gt;
                   &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 3&lt;/b&gt; – 5:30 – 7:30p – JUNIORS &amp;amp; BAND FRONT&lt;/li&gt;
                   &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 4&lt;/b&gt; – 5:30 – 7:30p – SOPHOMORES&lt;/li&gt;
                   &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 7&lt;/b&gt; – 5:30 – 7:30p – FRESHMAN&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mark these dates on your calendar now! You must have your uniform for Picture Day.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;If you still need your REQUIRED tshirts and polos, they will be available for purchase these evenings. Tshirts: $10 and Polos :$20&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note: all registration fees and/or outstanding fees must be paid or you will not be able to receive your uniform.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Any questions? Please call Anthony Amato: 216-401-7763&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;New Parent Meeting!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;August 9 at 6:15pm in the HS Media Center&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come and meet the Booster Exec board and many of our dedicated chairpersons at this meeting!  If you are new to our band program, this is your chance to hear about the booster organization and what our role is in supporting this fantastic band program.  Looking forward to meeting everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Needed: Assistant Chairpersons for Various Committees&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are in need of a few parents to help out our committees. It is a lot of fun to work on these committees. You will meet wonderful parents and every minute of your time directly benefits our band program&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;To volunteer for a position: CONTACT AMANDA KOST: 4408646543 or memandy@ameritech.net. THANKS!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Here is what we need:&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;VISITING BANDS &lt;/b&gt;– need a parent to contact the directors of visiting bands to check on the size of their band. We have a form email for you to send to the directors. We need the information because we supply water and snacks to our visiting bands. There are only 5 home games.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;PHOTO BUTTONS&lt;/b&gt; – need a parent to help the chairperson with Picture Day, process the pictures, help make the buttons and distribute at home games. It is a lot of fun… especially making the buttons!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;50/50 RAFFLE&lt;/b&gt; – need a parent to assist our chairperson the nights of the home games. You would help check in our volunteers, distribute tickets to our volunteers to sell, collect money, tear tickets and help close out the raffle. Involvement is from 6pm – halftime.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CHAPERONES&lt;/b&gt; – help chairperson to make sure all busses have chaperones. May require calling or emailing volunteers. Need to be able to chaperone the busses to away games and contests. It is a great way to meet the band and no worries about parking or driving to away events!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CONCERT UNIFORMS&lt;/b&gt; – need a parent to help the chairperson prepare the uniforms, distribute and collect for CONCERT season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mark Your Calendar!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 3 &lt;/b&gt;– FIRST DAY OF BAND CAMP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 2,3,4,7&lt;/b&gt; – Uniform Distribution (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 9&lt;/b&gt; – NEW PARENT MEETING – MEDIA CENTER 7pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 15&lt;/b&gt; – Picture Day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 18&lt;/b&gt; – Parent Preview Night and Ice Cream Social&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 18 – 20&lt;/b&gt; – EASTER SEALS DONATION DRIVE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 20&lt;/b&gt; – Home Days Parade&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 28&lt;/b&gt; – BOOSTER MEETING – MEDIA CENTER 7pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-07-28 08:07:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-07-28 08:34:38</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>nrhs-band-news-band-camp-starts-next-week-aug-3rd</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>