<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Support Our Band &amp; Pictures From Friday Are Online</title>
  <description>Hi Everyone,

As a booster organization it is our job to help support and promote our band and its s</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a booster organization it is our job to help support and promote our band and its students.  Band Boosters provides marching, contest and concert uniforms; flags; music licensing; show writing and choreography; instruments and instrument repair; dry-cleaning; paint for dots; awards; trip support; and so much more.  None of this would be possible without fundraisers that are staffed, run and supported by parents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately over the past five years, we have lost several big fundraisers: Nautica ($34,000), Entertainment Books ($1,500) and, just last year, Market Day ($8,500). We have been able to soften these blows mostly by maximizing our current fundraisers. We are concerned that everyone understands that every fundraiser is vitally important to the band. In order to keep providing the same excellent experience for our students, we have to make the most of the fundraisers we have. Additionally, what we truly do not want to happen is the loss of another fundraiser, such as Air Show. Depending on how we do with these fundraisers we may have to investigate other options. Here are the fundraisers that we have going on right now.  Please consider helping out in any way you can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Cleveland Air Show&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;September 3, 4 &amp;amp; 5 --Sign up NOW&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contact: Gary Diehl at work, 440-717-4063, cell phone 440-915-1178, or email, &lt;a href="mailto:gdiehl@broadview-heights.org"&gt;gdiehl@broadview-heights.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently our largest fundraiser, the Air Show doesn’t cost anything except volunteer time. We need 80 volunteers each day to collect/sell tickets.  We work in teams of two from 8:00am- 4:00pm. Students can participate as long as they are high school aged. If we fall short of volunteers for any of the days we will lose money from the potential $10,000 for this year, and we could possibly lose this as a fundraiser for future years. This is our largest fundraiser and we need it to not only be successful this year, but future years as well. Right now we still need about 40 more. Volunteers need to sign up NOW.  If you can help contact Gary or &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/20f054ba8ab2ca1f49-nrband"&gt;sign up here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h3&gt;Car Raffle&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tickets on sale now through September 30&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contact: Jane Coleman at &lt;a href="mailto:mattnjane.coleman@att.net"&gt;mattnjane.coleman@att.net&lt;/a&gt; or 440-759-9864&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the ninth consecutive year, our district is participating in the Car Raffle Fundraiser sponsored by Serpentini Chevrolet of Strongsville.  Your student should have received two tickets from us. If you haven’t seen them please ask your student. The tickets are sold for $20 each ($10 will go to the band and $10 will go to the North Royalton Stadium Foundation).  If every student sells both of their tickets we would raise over $5,500! The seller of the winning ticket will receive $500 too! Because we really want each student to sell both tickets, Band Boosters is adding an additional incentive.  Each band student who sells BOTH tickets and turns in the ticket stubs and money by September 30 will be entered into a drawing to win a contest hoodie (size large).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Booster Membership&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contact: Shirley Berish at 440-717-1532&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are several Booster Membership levels with different incentives to choose from.  This is a great opportunity to get items that show your support for all the hard work your kids do! A membership form was sent home in the band packet last Friday. If you did not get your membership form, &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/band-booster-membership"&gt;click here to print one&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Concessions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contact: Dawn Rembowski at 216-990-0271 or &lt;a href="mailto:dawnrembowski@att.net:&amp;gt;dawnrembowski@att.net&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Volunteers are needed to cashier, take orders, run orders, warm food and prep food at home games and Band Fest. Workers arrive 30 minutes before game time to assist with set-up AND stay after the game to help with clean-up. Sign-up is for each event so you can sign up for what fits your schedule. The concessions team has a lot of fun and you will get to meet every hungry person in the stadium! &amp;lt;a href=" http:="" www.signupgenius.com="" go="" 20f0f4daca62baaff2-concession"=""&gt;If you can help please sign up here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;50/50 Raffle Sales&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contact: Elisa Race at 216-407-5625&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Volunteers are needed to sell 50/50 raffle tickets in the stands games and Band Fest. All you have to do is talk to people coming into the stadium or sitting in the stands. The tickets actually sell themselves! Plus you get to watch the band as the sales at halftime. You do not have to volunteer for every game. You can choose which ones will fit in your schedule. Use &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054eafa729a02-5050"&gt;this link if you are available to help&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please help our band by contributing in whatever way you can – whether it is volunteering your time, buying/selling Car Raffle tickets, or becoming a Band Booster member. If everyone does a little, no one will have to do a lot. There will also be other opportunities to help and contribute throughout the year. Remember, anything you do will only benefit our kids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amanda Kost &amp;amp; Becky Humes&lt;br&gt;
Band Booster President &amp;amp; Vice President&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. Pictures from Friday night have been added to &lt;a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/nrhsmarchingband/albums"&gt;our Flickr site&lt;/a&gt;. Thanks Chuck!!!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-09-03 07:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-09-03 07:41:49</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>support-our-band-and-pictures-from-friday-are-online</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>