<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>NRMB Newsletter – October 17, 2016</title>
  <description>GRAND CHAMPIONS!  This show just keeps getting better!  A strong and confident performance from our </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;GRAND CHAMPIONS! This show just keeps getting better! A strong and confident performance from our band under a beautiful full moon sky! Way to go Bandos! Let's do it again at Brunswick!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Support our band by attending our contest performance at Brunswick, October 22nd at 8:00pm. Only two performances left of the entire show. Please come out and support and acknowledge all the hard work of our band!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LINKS you need to know:&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Mr. Vitale’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandboosters.com"&gt;Band Booster’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/North-Royalton-Band-Boosters/164850233634290"&gt;FaceBook North Royalton Band Boosters -- Like Us!!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other Fundraisers: GFS and Smile.Amazon.com (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;DATES you need to know:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oct 21 – Football game AWAY Cuyahoga Falls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 22 – CONTEST – BRUNSWICK 8:00pm performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 24 – BAND BOOSTER MEETING -- 7PM MEDIA CENTER&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oct 28 – Football game HOME Stow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oct 29 – STATES – Hilliard Bradley HS -- 3:45 block w 4:30 performance time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nov 2 – Marching Band Concert GYM 1 7:00pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nov 2 – Marching season is officially over&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Car Raffle&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are still missing MANY car raffle tickets. Please check with your bando and return either sold or unsold tickets. We need to account for every ticket! Please place your envelope in the white band box asap.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Order Your CD/DVD of Our Marching Band Now!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/FILES%2f2016%2f10%2fNRMB-CD-DVD-OrderForm.pdf.axdx"&gt;Attached is the order form&lt;/a&gt; to order your personal copy of the Marching Band Concert (CD) and the State Performance of The Elements (DVD).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Band Boosters will be offering the ONLY DVD that will be available of our marching band at States. You cannot order a DVD at States like we did in previous years because of all the changes in the copyright laws.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Order both the CD and DVD at a reduced price! Order by NOV 3rd to secure your copies! Call Amanda Kost 440-864-6543 with questions.&lt;/p&gt;
 
 
&lt;h3&gt;Other Fundraisers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GFS: If you shop at GFS, remember to mention: North Royalton Band Boosters and Marching Band at checkout. We have an account there and accumulate $$$$ for everything YOU spend!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Smile.Amazon Are you an Amazon shopper? Set up a SMILE.AMAZON account and a percentage of what you purchase will be added to the North Royalton Band Booster account:&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;YOU can help North Royalton High School Band Boosters when you shop for back-to-school supplies and many other items that you purchase from Amazon! This link will help you set up your SMILE account!.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Support us when you shop for back-to-school items. #StartWithaSmile at &lt;a href="http://smile.amazon.com/ch/34-1817202"&gt;http://smile.amazon.com/ch/34-1817202&lt;/a&gt; and Amazon donates.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-10-18 19:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-10-19 19:38:21</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>nrmb-newsletter-october-17-2016</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>