<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Committee Chairs and Board Members Needed for 2014-2015 Band Season</title>
  <description>We have begun to plan for next season and we need a number of parents to step up and fill the open s</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
                    We have begun to plan for next season and we need a number of parents to step up and fill the open slots vacated by those parents that have graduating seniors. The Band Boosters are the lifeblood of the North Royalton band program and provide the majority of the support and funding required for instruments, uniforms, transportation, etc. Without the boosters, there would be no Marching Band or Concert Band program. Help us to keep the North Royalton band program one of the top programs in the state of Ohio.
                &lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;p&gt;We are looking for volunteers to fill the slots listed below. Ideally, candidates will be available for 2 years and have some previous experience with the band boosters. However, past experience is not required. If you are unsure of the duties, the out-going chairs are more than happy to work with you to ensure a smooth and orderly transition. Contacts are listed along with the descriptions below. For general questions, or to volunteer, please contact the Booster president, Rich Hrin at (440) 668-7428 (&lt;a href="mailto:hrinmor@sbcglobal.net"&gt;hrinmor@sbcglobal.net&lt;/a&gt;) if you can help out.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;ul&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Treasurer (contact Rich or Russ Klimczuk, &lt;a href="mailto:rklimczuk@clevelandart.org"&gt;rklimczuk@clevelandart.org&lt;/a&gt; for more info)&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Air Show (contact Rich or Kathy Pishnery, &lt;a href="mailto:kathypish@aol.com"&gt;kathypish@aol.com&lt;/a&gt; for more info)&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Visiting Band Hospitality (contact Rich or Martha Custer, &lt;a href="mailto:marthalcuster@sbcglobal.net"&gt;marthalcuster@sbcglobal.net&lt;/a&gt; for more info)&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Raffle Fundraiser (contact Rich or Carol Shivley Mizes, &lt;a href="mailto:carolcola4@gmail.com"&gt;carolcola4@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; for more info)&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Car Raffle Fundraiser (contact Rich or Jeff or Kris Paulus, &lt;a href="mailto:jeff@pauluseng.com"&gt;jeff@pauluseng.com&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href="mailto:kmp@pauluseng.com"&gt;kmp@pauluseng.com&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;/ul&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Thanks for helping us to make 2014-2015 the best year ever!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-07-27 09:07:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-07-27 09:43:18</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>committee-chairs-and-board-members-needed-for-2014-2015-band-season1</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>