<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Contest Hoodies, Band Fest, and Much More...</title>
  <description>NRHS Band News 
Air Show
A sincere ‘thank you’ to all the bandos, their families, and friends for ta</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;NRHS Band News&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Air Show&lt;/h3&gt;A sincere ‘thank you’ to all the bandos, their families, and friends for taking the time out of their busy holiday weekend to volunteer at the Cleveland Air Show! It is truly appreciated… Please post any pictures you have on our FB page!&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Contest Hoodies&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in purchasing a Contest Hoodie…. Order forms are DUE by SEPT 7th! NO EXCEPTIONS!!! We only order exactly what we need and the order must go in so the hoodies arrive before our first contest! Questions? Contact Shirley Berish: 440-717-1532&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sale Blitz Weekend&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sept 9-10 is our Fruit Sale Blitz weekend… packets will be handed out in Cafeteria 2 after the Wednesday 6-9 practice. A few things to remember: travel in groups and ONLY during the daylight hours, wear the Purple Band Polo uniform, (the one you wore for the Home Days Parade!), stay on the street you signed up for, do not enter any one’s home and have fun!! The NR Police are aware that we will be going door to door for this fruit sale. Monday after extended practice, stop by Café 2 for Pizza as a Thank You from the Boosters! Any questions? Contact: Jayme Poplin – 440-457-7417 or Heidi Cmich – 216-244-2968&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Band Fest - September 16&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The preview of our contest show will be Saturday, Sept 16 at Band Fest! We will be hosting 12 bands in total and there will be more than 1800 performers! WOW!!!!! Plan to come for the entire evening to enjoy the show. Tshirts will be sold at the event! We still need a few volunteers to help sell programs. &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-20174"&gt;To volunteer&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Football Game Date Change&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a reminder that the Twinsburg game is SATURDAY, SEPTEMBER 23 at 7pm We still need chaperones!!! &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-20175"&gt;To volunteer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Car Raffle Tickets&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your bando received two car raffle tickets to sell after the practice last Wednesday. Sold tickets and payment should be returned to the white band box. You can get extra tickets to sell by contacting Joyce Fink: 440-237-1636&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Mark Your Calendar!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 7 – LAST DAY FOR CONTEST HOODIE ORDER!!!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 8 – HOME – Highland&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 9-10 – Fruit Sale Blitz Weekend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 15 – AWAY - Stow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 16 – Festival of Bands – check Mr. Vitale’s website for reporting details&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 23 – AWAY – Twinsburg NOTE THE DATE CHANGE!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 25 – Booster Meeting - 7pm in the Media Center&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 29 – HOME - Hudson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 30 – CONTEST – Avon Lake&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-09-06 07:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-09-13 07:31:07</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>contest-hoodies-band-fest-and-much-more</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>