<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Air Show Volunteers Needed</title>
  <description>Hello everyone!
Thank you to those who have volunteered to participate in the North Royalton Band Bo</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you to those who have volunteered to participate in the North Royalton Band Boosters largest fundraiser of the year, the Cleveland National Air Show. The Band Boosters have provided manpower to the air show for many years and we are given preferential treatment by the organizers due to the large number of hard working and enthusiastic volunteers we offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to fully staff the air show and maximize our fundraising opportunity, we need to supply 80 volunteers each day of the air show. We will sell and take tickets at the Plaza booth and at Gate 13, where we will also managing the parking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of you who have not worked the air show before, this is a great way to get to know your fellow band parents and have a fun time meeting people. Volunteering at the Air Show is usually a family event so moms, dads, and siblings are all welcome along with our “Bandos.” Children must be 15 years of age to participate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To sign up for your slots, we have set up a form at &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/20f054ba8ab2ca1f49-nrband"&gt;www.signupgenious.com&lt;/a&gt;. All you need to do is select your day, indicated the number of volunteers in your group and provide a phone number and email address.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/20f054ba8ab2ca1f49-nrband"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here is the link to our signup form&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: Monday is usually the hardest day to fill so if you are available Monday, please select that day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any questions? Please contact Gary Diehl: 440-915-1178&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-07-25 21:07:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-07-25 21:06:55</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>air-show-volunteers-needed</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>fa6094d0-c8e0-4964-8deb-b6349a6dd281</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>