<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Another Fruit Pick Up Date Added and More</title>
  <description>Hello, Fellow Fruit Lovers.
 
Hopefully by now you are enjoying your delicious Florida fruit!  If yo</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello, Fellow Fruit Lovers.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully by now you are enjoying your delicious Florida fruit! If you didn't make it to pick-up today, don't worry! We will give you one more chance to get your orders. We will be located in the same place this &lt;b&gt;Monday, December 7th, from 5pm-7pm&lt;/b&gt;. Please plan on picking up your fruit and delivering it right away to ensure your customers get their fruit at its freshest!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We have extra fruit available for you to purchase, just in case you wish you had ordered more. We will be selling it before and after all of the holiday concerts, December 13th &amp;amp; 14th, while our supplies last. Please visit our table so we can take care of all of your fruit needs.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Also, this year we are having BBYB (Bring Back Your Bags). We purchase the bags that are used for the 10 pound fruit orders. They cost about $1 per bag. Please help us save money next year by carefully opening your bags and then returning them to us. You can return them to us at the Holiday Concerts on December 13 and 14.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for supporting our sale!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Susie: &lt;a href="mailto:susielbp@juno.com"&gt;susielbp@juno.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Karen: &lt;a href="mailto:svo@wideopenwest.com"&gt;svo@wideopenwest.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-12-06 07:12:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-12-06 07:03:38</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>another-fruit-pick-up-date-added-and-more</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>