<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Raffle Fundraiser and Band Awards Night Help</title>
  <description>Dear Band Families,
 
PLEASE HELP!  We know this is a crazy time of year but we need a few more volu</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;PLEASE HELP!  We know this is a crazy time of year but we need a few more volunteers to help with the Raffle Fundraiser on Saturday and the Band Awards Banquet on Wednesday. We also need a few more beverage donations for the Awards Banquet. The only way these events can be successful is with your help. Please consider signing up below.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Volunteers For Band Raffle Fundraiser (Saturday) &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We need a few more volunteers to help at the 3 Spot this Saturday to sell tickets and check people in. You will NOT have to work the entire evening. Shifts are only for one hour.  See the Signup Genius link below and if you can help out it would be greatly appreciated. If you are having a problem with &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080c4da5ae23a6fc1-nrbb"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Signup Genius&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or if you would like to help but can’t work the exact hours listed, please call, text or email Anne at 330-304-2499 or iannehdg@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;h3&gt;Volunteers For Band Awards Banquet (Wednesday) &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We need a few volunteers to help set-up, serve and clean-up for the Band Awards Banquet on Wednesday, May 10th.  See the Signup Genius link below and if you can help out it would be greatly appreciated. If you are having a problem with &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/409044daeab2da20-band1"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Signup Genius&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or can’t work the exact hours listed, please call or email Helen Kelly at 440 746-9048 or alandhelenkelly@cox.net.&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;h3&gt;Beverages For Band Awards Banquet &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are also in need of a few more beverages for the dinner.  If you could kindly donate some beverages for this event please signup.  The drinks can be dropped off at Cafeteria I (next to PAC) beginning at 3:00 PM on Wednesday, May 10, 2017. Someone will be in Cafeteria I to accept your donation. NO beverages should be dropped off in the band room or the main office.  &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/409044DAEAB2DA20-drink1"&gt;Please see Signup Genius link.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;p&gt;Thanks in advance for your assistance and donations! &lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-05-06 07:05:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-05-06 07:52:11</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>raffle-fundraiser-and-band-awards-night-help</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
    <category>fa6094d0-c8e0-4964-8deb-b6349a6dd281</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>