<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>2016 Fruit Sale THANK YOU!</title>
  <description>We want to say “Thank You!” to all of you for making this year’s fruit sale a successful! Our total </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;We want to say “Thank You!” to all of you for making this year’s fruit sale a successful! Our total profit was just over $12,000! Wow! That is fantastic!&lt;/b&gt; This would not have been possible without everyone playing a part in the sale. We would like to thank the following people for helping: Thank you if you met with the fruit company rep, weighed in on the fruit company decision, helped sign out packets for the blitz, drove your child to walk during the blitz, walked your route during the blitz, took donations during the blitz, turned in your blitz envelope, offered a personal sale packet to anyone, turned in your personal sale packet, placed any orders online, sent out emails to the band about the fruit sale, read all of the fruit sale emails, added fruit sale information to the band website, handled a lot of money and checks from the blitz and personal sale, made sure the payment got to the fruit company, alerted us the fruit had arrived, ran up to the school on a minute’s notice and did inventory, moved boxes around in the annex, made up bags of fruit, put up with hyper fruit committee people, made and donated beautiful thank-you cards, taste-tested fruit, picked up your order, picked customer orders, double-checked customer orders, took orders to cars, drank hot chocolate, ate doughnuts, made fruit people, ate fruit, enjoyed the fruit, gave fruit as gifts, delivered all of the blitz orders, delivered personal sale orders, gave out our beautiful thank-you cards, helped move fruit from the annex to our cars, then into the school, then back out to our cars, bought some of the extra fruit, put up with a couple of us pretty much only talking fruit for months, decided you would love to take over the fruit sale committee, sent in your fruit bags to be reused, read through this entire thank-you email! Whew! It really did take a lot of people helping to earn the band that much! We apologize if we forgot anyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going back to the thank-you cards, &lt;strong&gt;Lake Erie Graphics&lt;/strong&gt; printed those for us at no charge. Please consider using them for any printing needs you have. &lt;a href="http://lakeeriegraphics.com/"&gt;Here is their website&lt;/a&gt;. You can see they do fantastic work and we really do appreciate them always being so generous!&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;br&gt;Karen and Susie&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-01-31 19:01:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-01-31 19:20:27</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>2016-fruit-sale-thank-you</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>