<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>We Need You! Volunteers for States May 1 &amp; 2</title>
  <description>Hi Everyone,
 
We still need volunteers for States on May 1 and May 2. We need 29 on Friday afternoo</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,
 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We still need volunteers for States on May 1 and May 2. We need 29 on Friday afternoon/night and 13 on Saturday morning to fill 2-3 hour shifts. Most students are required to work a shift for the band directors. Consider joining them and helping out at our final fundraiser of the school year. If we do not get enough volunteers, we will need to work longer/extra shifts.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;If you can help, &lt;b&gt;please email me at &lt;a href="mailto:holly.rmc@gmail.com"&gt;holly.rmc@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; by Friday, April 24&lt;/b&gt;, so that we can complete the schedule and get that information out to everyone.  Please be sure to indicate what band your student is in so that we do not schedule you during their performance.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;I would like to thank all the volunteers that have already come forward to help. Your confirmed assignment will be sent to you this coming weekend. Thanks for your patience and understanding in this scheduling process!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Please remember, that if we all do a little, no one will have to do a lot!  &lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thanks in advance for your continued support! &lt;br&gt;
Holly Michalke&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-04-23 19:04:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-04-23 19:45:24</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>we-need-you-volunteers-for-states-may-1-and-2</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>fa6094d0-c8e0-4964-8deb-b6349a6dd281</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>