<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Fruit Sale Pick-Up</title>
  <description>Your attention, please!
The moment you have all been waiting for is almost here! Our fruit pick-up d</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Your attention, please!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The moment you have all been waiting for is almost here! Our fruit pick-up day is set! Please make note of the details listed below so that you can add this event to your schedule for that day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who -&lt;/b&gt; Every band family that placed a fruit order.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;What -&lt;/b&gt; Band Fruit Pick-Up Day!&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where -&lt;/b&gt; The football annex. This is the area located just behind the board of education office, which is right next to the stadium on Royalton Road. You can park in front of the board office and then walk between that building and the stadium. The door to the annex will be down on your right, and we will have the entrance clearly marked with fruit boxes.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;When -&lt;/b&gt; Saturday, December 10th, from 9am-1pm.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why &lt;/b&gt;- We want to keep all of our supporters happy by delivering fresh fruit to them. Please make plans to distribute the fruit to all of the people on your order form as soon as possible. If customers call because they haven’t received their fruit, we will call the student who is responsible for that order to make sure it gets delivered. Please make your deliveries right away to ensure customers do not need to call to check on their orders.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;How - &lt;/b&gt;Simply show up on pick-up day, wait in line, give us the name your order is under and wait. A volunteer will pick your order, have it checked, and then some friendly bandos will help you get your order to your car if you would like. Please be patient if the line is long. We will move things along as quickly as possible. Once you leave with your fruit, why not stop and deliver all of the orders?!&lt;/li&gt;

 &lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are not able to get your fruit on the pick-up day, please contact one of us to make other arrangements. Please spread the word about this exciting event so that everyone knows about it. Let’s plan on getting all of the fruit delivered ASAP!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;More important fruit pick-up information!&lt;/h3&gt;
  
&lt;p&gt;If you ordered from a band student who came to your door in September, please do not come to pick up your fruit on Saturday.  One of the perks of supporting this fundraiser is that your fruit will be delivered to you.  Please allow a few days for your fruit to show up.  Many will make deliveries this weekend, but some may not get to it until early next week.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We appreciate your patience and your support of our band!  Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;br&gt;Susie 440-877-1299 &amp;amp; Karen 440-213-6414&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-12-03 07:12:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-12-05 20:07:10</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>fruit-sale-pick-up</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>