<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Booster News - Holiday Concert, Uniform Turn In, Pies And More</title>
  <description>Hi Everyone,
 
It is amazing that we have already closed this incredible 2015 Marching Band Season. </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;It is amazing that we have already closed this incredible 2015 Marching Band Season. This season will always have fond memories for my family and me since it was the only year both of my children performed together on the football field. I know I am not alone. There were so many lifelong memories made both on and off the field this season for all of us. This activity offers so many opportunities! I would like to thank the Royalettes and Royalaires for the signature role you played in the 2015 season. We look forward to seeing you at the holiday parade and again in the spring for our Florida trip and Memorial Day parade.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Flickr pictures&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for lasting memories from the football season, check out our flicker account. It was nice to see so many pictures of our kids working hard and enjoying the marching experience. A special thanks goes out to Chuck Allen for all his time spent taking and posting these pictures.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Holiday Concert&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next performance experience takes place December 13 and 14. Tickets are on sale. Visit the &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonhighschoolband.com/performances"&gt;director’s website&lt;/a&gt; and order your tickets now! These shows sell out fast! If you receive complimentary tickets because of joining boosters, don't forget, you still need to fill out an order form indicating which concert(s) you plan to attend.
 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Marching Band Uniform Turn In Dates&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marching Band Uniform turn in is this Tuesday and Wednesday, November 17 and 18, between 6:00pm-8:00pm. Please refer to the emails that went out November 4 regarding the specific dry cleaning and washing directions. These can also be found on our website, www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com. (You may have to scroll down the page to see them.) Freshman and Sophomore Boys Only – Right after you turn in your uniform, go to the concert uniform committee to be measured for your concert uniform (tux). Do not forget as these uniforms need to be ordered at that time to ensure delivery by the Holiday concert. Freshman Boys Only – You will also need to purchase your tux shirt for $21 (checks to Tuxedo Junction).&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Booster Meeting&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our next Booster Meeting is Monday, Nov. 16, in the Media Center at 7:00 pm. This is our last meeting until Jan. - come join us!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Five Guys and Holiday Pies&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Five Guys was a huge success! We brought in $420 just by feeding our family. Our next food experience is the Bakers Square holiday pie sale. Pie gift cards are $14 each. Get your pies for Thanksgiving and the holiday season through this fundraiser and help our band program at the same time! Pie gift cards do not expire until the year 2064 so you can buy now for the whole year and beyond. Order forms are in the band room but you can also &lt;a href="/FILES%2f2015%2f11%2fPieSaleOrderForm-2015.pdf.axdx"&gt;print one from our website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;It won't be long before we are all together again for the holiday concert. Warmest wishes to our band family for a wonderful Thanksgiving.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;br&gt;
Band Booster President&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-11-15 07:11:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-11-15 07:43:13</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>booster-news-holiday-concert-uniform-turn-in-pies-and-more</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>