<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Newsletter - Memorial Day Parade, Concert Uniforms, Band Shoes &amp; More</title>
  <description>Hello Everyone!
 
As another school year comes to a close, it is just remarkable to me the level of </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Everyone!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As another school year comes to a close, it is just remarkable to me the level of dedication, support and passion our volunteers possess. It is no wonder our band program thrives! It is a trifecta that perpetuates the cycle. Very talented directors, dedicated parents and enthusiastic kids! A successful combination that continues to prove itself!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Memorial Day Parade&lt;/b&gt; is the final event scheduled before we close out the 2015-16 school year. It is a great way to celebrate the holiday and the city of Broadview Hts. does such a nice job hosting this event. Come join us! The parade starts at 11 am.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;As I complete my term as Band Booster President, I would like to thank you for ALL of your help. Whether it was a small effort or showing your continuous support. I could not have made it without you! Seeing our children succeed at this level and showing them we support their actions is worth the effort! My motivation to be involved in the Band Boosters came from the fact that this program inspired me to become a music educator over 30 years ago! I know what music does for others and I just wanted to give back anyway that I could! It has been one of the most rewarding things I have ever done! Consider getting involved! You won't regret it!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Congratulations to our soon to be graduated boosters&lt;/b&gt;. Their knowledge will continue to carry on our tradition of excellence! It has been a pleasure working with you the past 4 years! Please join our alumni Facebook page and encourage your son/daughter to do the same! It’s a good way to stay involved! You are always welcome in the band family!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;We would like to welcome our new parents!&lt;/b&gt; Join us on Facebook, become a booster member and get involved! It is very rewarding! You can find all the links at &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com"&gt;www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;As we look forward to next year, please be sure to pay close attention to the summer band camp dates in June (Tues. - Thurs. June 14 -16) as well as the August dates. The calendar can be found on &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Mr. Vitale’s website&lt;/a&gt; under Forms and PDFs. Visit his website often to get information and updates directly from him. It is also a good idea to bookmark this page on your phone and/or computer.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Get Involved!&lt;/h3&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We are in need of a treasurer! This position has recently opened and we need to fill this as soon as possible! Please let us know if you are interested!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Air Show Chairman Update&lt;/b&gt; - Gary Diehl has agreed to chair the Labor Day Airshow project. He could really use 1 - 2 assistants. If you are interested, contact Amanda Kost.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;If you haven't filled out your &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/volunteer-form"&gt;volunteer form for next school year, please follow this link&lt;/a&gt;. It takes over 300 different jobs to run this program effectively. Get involved and join the team! If everyone does a little, it makes the work a whole lot easier and much more fun! If you are uncertain about what to choose, contact us, we will help guide you!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;AIRSHOW - Save The Date!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our first event will be the Airshow Labor Day weekend (Sept. 3-5). This event is our biggest money maker and requires no selling. We are responsible for parking cars and collecting ticket money. That’s it! But, we need 80 people per day. Please consider saving a spot during your Labor Day Weekend to help with this event. Parents and students 14 and older are welcome to volunteer!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;A FEW IMPORTANT HOUSEKEEPING ITEMS&lt;/h3&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Final Concert Uniform Turn in &lt;/b&gt;- Tuesday, May 24 from 6 to 8. Several people have not returned their concert uniforms. Please be sure to deliver your uniform to the uniform room at this time.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Shoes, T-Shirts &amp;amp; Polos &lt;/b&gt;- Any marching shoes MUST BE ordered by Saturday, MAY 28 at Royalton Music TO AVOID EXTRA CHARGES. They will be available for pick up at June rehearsal dates. &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/post/2016/05/18/2016-marching-season"&gt;See the related post for details&lt;/a&gt;. The Band Boosters will also have the required white band t-shirts ($10) and purple band polos ($20) available for purchase at the high school directly after evening rehearsals on June 14 &amp;amp; 15. PLEASE NOTE - THE WHITE T-SHIRTS WILL NO LONGER HAVE THE DATES ON THE BACK.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;If you have questions, Please don't hesitate to contact us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-05-26 07:05:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-05-26 07:30:46</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>newsletter-memorial-day-parade-concert-uniforms-band-shoes-and-more</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>