<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Volunteers needed for Honors Band Rehearsals</title>
  <description>Dear Band Families:
 
We need 3 volunteers on Friday, November 14, and Saturday, November 15, to JUS</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Families:&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We need 3 volunteers on Friday, November 14, and Saturday, November 15, to JUST BE PRESENT while the Honors Band rehearses for their performance at Cleveland State.  We need 1 parent during each of the following shifts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="no-more-tables"&gt;
 &lt;table class="table table-striped table-hover row table-contact"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Shift 1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Shift 2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td class="numeric"&gt;Shift 3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td data-title="Shift 1"&gt;Friday (11/14)  - 8:30AM-12:30PM
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td data-title="Shift 2"&gt;
Friday (11/14) - 12:30 PM-4:00PM
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td data-title="Shift 3" class="numeric"&gt;
Saturday (11/15) - 1:30-PM-4:00PM
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
 &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the agreement with Cleveland State University hosting this event, each school is required to send 1 parent or Band Booster to be on site in case of an emergency. Because of this, we are looking for 3 parents that might be able to help us out and be on site to fulfill this requirement. The parent doesn’t need to “do” anything except be there.  They can do work, read the paper, listen to the rehearsal, eat in the student center, watch the news, etc. Mr. Vitale has checked with the powers that be, and this person wouldn’t even have to be in the music building, they could hang out at the Student Center – which is connected by a walkway to the music building. Attached is a document with more information.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;If you can help, please contact Mr. Vitale at &lt;a href="mailto:david.vitale@northroyaltonsd.org"&gt;david.vitale@northroyaltonsd.org&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-11-06 07:11:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-11-06 07:18:00</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>volunteers-needed-for-honors-band-rehearsals</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>fa6094d0-c8e0-4964-8deb-b6349a6dd281</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>