<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>NRHS Band Program Newsletter – MAY 22, 2017</title>
  <description>Congrats to all of our graduating Seniors…. May you always dream and reach for those dreams and make</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Congrats to all of our graduating Seniors…. May you always dream and reach for those dreams and make music a part of your life….&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thank you to every person who helped make this band season a HUGE success… all the hours chairing a committee, volunteering, bringing your student to practices and supporting our bands is greatly appreciated. This program runs well because of YOU!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LINKS you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Mr. Vitale’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandboosters.com"&gt;Band Booster’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/North-Royalton-Band-Boosters/164850233634290"&gt;FaceBook North Royalton Band Boosters -- Like Us!!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;FINAL DATES for the season that you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May 22 – Band Booster Meeting in the Media Center at 7PM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May 24 – Band-A-Rama – 7PM in Gym 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May 29 – Memorial Day Parade – see Mr.Vitale’s site for details&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;June 13-14 – Tshirt / Polo sale 8 – 8:30pm Cafeteria 2&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to order your shoes for the next marching season!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Donations Requested For End of the Year Ice Cream Social and Parade&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are still in need of a few items for the last two end of the year events. Please &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054eafa729a02-donations1"&gt;follow this link if you can donate&lt;/a&gt; and bring your donations to either the Booster Meeting this Monday, May 22 OR to the band room before Band-A-Rama, May 24th. Thank you in advance for your donations&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;h3&gt;Mark Your Calendar - June 13th-14&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tshirts ($10) and Polos l($20) will be sold AFTER the evening rehearsals. Tables will be set up in Cafeteria 2 from 8 – 8:30PM. Cash or Checks ONLY. Checks are to be made out to the North Royalton Band Boosters. Any questions, please call Amanda Kost – 440-864-6543&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-05-24 07:05:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-05-24 07:24:15</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>nrhs-band-program-newsletter-may-22-2017</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>