<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Marching Band Cup &amp; Contest Hoodies</title>
  <description>Dear Band Families,

We are in the middle of our membership drive. We have many membership levels to</description>
  <content>&lt;img src="/FILES%2f2017%2f08%2fNR-band-cup-sm.jpg.axdx" class="pull-right" title="" style=""&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are in the middle of our membership drive. We have many membership levels to choose from and this year you can also add on a wonderful Tervis cup with the NRHS Marching Band logo for $25. This cup is only available to members. The add on is at the bottom of the form. If you have already joined you can still order cups. Just fill out the top of the form with your name and contact info, fill in the Tervis cup add on box with the number of cups you want, and then write next to it that you are already a member. &lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandboosters.us15.list-manage1.com/track/click?u=f9c4e414afe05390874757772&amp;amp;id=d294c4c31c&amp;amp;e=79b990d89d" style=""&gt;Please click here to download the Membership Form&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is also time to order your contest hoodies and pins. Please note that all orders (including orders made through our Grand Staff Membership) are due in the white band box by September 7. We do not order extras and no late orders can be accepted. If you want a contest hoodie be sure to turn your order in on time. &lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandboosters.us15.list-manage.com/track/click?u=f9c4e414afe05390874757772&amp;amp;id=5045f78278&amp;amp;e=79b990d89d" style=""&gt;Please click here to download the Contest Hoodie &amp;amp; Pin Order Form&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contact Shirley with any questions at 717-1532.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-08-25 06:08:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-08-25 06:30:35</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>marching-band-cup-and-contest-hoodies</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>