<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Fruit Sale Blitz!</title>
  <description>Hello, Band Families!
 
Our annual fruit sale is just about to begin!  This sale is a huge fundraise</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello, Band Families!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/FILES%2f2016%2f09%2fNR-FruitSale-Flyer-2016.pdf.axdx"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Download Fruit Sale Flyer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/FILES%2f2016%2f09%2fNR-FruitSale-OrderForm-2016.pdf.axdx"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Download Fruit Sale Order Form&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our annual fruit sale is just about to begin! This sale is a huge fundraiser for our band and will be a great success with everyone participating. This year we are using a new supplier, Pee Jays Fresh Fruit. We will be offering grapefruit, tangelos, navel oranges from California, pears, pineapples and some mixed assortments. Yummy stuff! The big kickoff to our sale will be our &lt;b&gt;Blitz Weekend, September 10th &amp;amp; 11th&lt;/b&gt;. This is the weekend when our bandos hit the streets to offer our fantastic selection of fruit to the local communities. All students will sell door-to-door in groups of two or three at some point during that weekend. There is an ACT test the morning of the 10th, so please keep that in mind when picking a time to help with this fundraiser. We ask that each group go out for at least two hours. Please remind your children that they will be representing the North Royalton High School Marching Band, so we ask them to be polite and appreciative. They are to wear some kind of band shirt, such as the purple polo or white band t-shirt. &lt;b&gt;This Wednesday, September 7th, after the 6-9 practice, all groups will sign out a blitz packet to be used for the door-to-door sale&lt;/b&gt;. One person from each group will be considered the captain and be responsible for getting &lt;b&gt;the entire envelope, including the order form and money, returned to school the following Monday, September 12th&lt;/b&gt;. We will collect the envelopes and treat the kids to pizza for all of their hard work! Once your child brings home a blitz packet, please look inside to get familiar with the contents and read the sheet that contains instructions and reminders. This sheet will also be sent in an email as a reminder for everyone. Because packets will be distributed after 6-9 practice, your child may be a few minutes later leaving rehearsal this Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Please encourage your bando to be enthusiastic during the door-to-door sales blitz! Our band has been selling fruit and doing other fundraisers for years with a "pay-it-forward" attitude. Others gave of their time so that our current students would benefit, so we all need to do the same for those who will follow in future years.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Please let us know if you have any questions. Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
 
 
&lt;p&gt;Susie Perez 440-877-1299 Karen Svoboda 440-213-6414&lt;/p&gt;     </content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-09-07 06:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-09-07 06:39:06</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>fruit-sale-blitz</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>