<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Supporting Our Band</title>
  <description>Hi Everyone,
    As a booster organization it is our job to help support and promote our band and it</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As a booster organization it is our job to help support and promote our band and its students. Band Boosters provides: marching, contest and concert uniforms; flags; music; writing and choreography; instruments and instrument repair; dry-cleaning; paint for dots; awards; trip support; and so much more. None of this would be possible without fundraisers that are staffed, run and supported by parents.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Unfortunately this summer we lost Market Day, one of our largest fundraisers. Market Day was purchased by World's Finest Chocolate, and they decided to discontinue the traditional grocery program. This equates to a yearly cut of about $8,000 to our fundraising budget. Coming after the loss of the Entertainment Book and Nautica fundraisers within the last few years this is a fairly serious budget issue. Maximizing our current fundraisers is especially important as we try to offset this loss. Depending on how we do with these fundraisers we may have to investigate other options. Here are the fundraisers that we have going on right now. Please consider helping out in any way you can.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Cleveland Air Show&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;September 5, 6 &amp;amp; 7&lt;br&gt;Sign up before August 19&lt;br&gt;Contact: Becky Cozzens at &lt;a href="mailto:thecozzens@yahoo.com"&gt;thecozzens@yahoo.com&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Currently our largest fundraiser, the Air Show doesn’t cost anything except volunteer time. We need 80 volunteers each day to collect/sell tickets. We work in teams of two from 8:00am- 4:00pm. Students can participate as long as they are high school aged. If we fall short of volunteers for any of the days we will lose money from the potential $10,000 for this year, and we could possibly lose this as a fundraiser for future years. This is our largest fundraiser and we need it to not only be successful this year, but future years as well. Right now we still need 10 volunteers for Sunday and 55 for Monday. Volunteers need to sign up by August 19 so that we can turn the list over to the Air Show. If you can help, please &lt;a href="www.SignUpGenius.com/go/70A0C4DACAE29AB9-cleveland/"&gt; sign up here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Easter Seals “Fill the Truck” Fundraiser&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;August 22 &amp;amp; 23&lt;br&gt;Contact: Amanda Kost at &lt;a href="mailto:amandabethkost@gmail.com"&gt;amandabethkost@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or at 440-864-6543&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;This is a new fundraiser for us this year. It is great because it benefits the band and the community, PLUS we don’t have to sell anything. The truck will be parked next to the North Royalton Board of Education and we will be collecting any and all cloth items (clothing, blankets, towels, shoes, etc.). We earn money based on how many pounds we collect. Please donate and encourage others to do so as well. You will receive a tax receipt from Easter Seals, so you won’t even lose out on the potential tax benefits of making a donation. HOWEVER, while this fundraiser won’t cost us any money we do need volunteers to give some time to help man the truck. We are asking for just 1.5-2 hours of your time. Currently we need 22 more volunteers for this fundraiser. If you can help please &lt;a href="www.SignUpGenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-easter"&gt;sign up here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Car Raffle&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Tickets on sale now through September 11 Contact: Jane and Matt Coleman at &lt;a href="mailto:mattnjane.coleman@att.net"&gt;mattnjane.coleman@att.net&lt;/a&gt; or 440-759-9864&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;For the eighth consecutive year, our district is participating in the Car Raffle Fundraiser sponsored by Serpentini Chevrolet of Strongsville. Your student should have received two tickets from us when they picked up their uniform. If you haven’t seen them please ask your student. The tickets are sold for $20 each ($10 will go to the band and $10 will go to the North Royalton Stadium Foundation). If every student sells both of their tickets we could raise over $5,500! This year they have an incentive drawing on September 25 with the seller of the ticket drawn winning $200. Because we really want each student to sell both tickets, Band Boosters is adding another incentive. Each band student who sells BOTH tickets and turns in the ticket stubs and money by September 11 will be entered into a drawing to win a contest hoodie (size large).&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Booster Membership&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contact: Shirley Berish at 440-717-1532 or Rima Chehade at 440-526-7016&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;There are several Booster Membership levels with different incentives to choose from. This is a great opportunity to get items that show your support for all the hard work your kids do! A membership form was sent home in the band packet last Friday. If you did not get your membership form, &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/band-booster-membership"&gt;click here to print one&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Please help our band by contributing in whatever way you can – whether it is volunteering your time, donating your old clothing, buying/selling Car Raffle tickets, or becoming a Band Booster member. If everyone does a little, no one will have to do a lot. Remember, anything you do will only benefit our kids.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Becky Humes&lt;br&gt;Band Booster Corresponding Secretary&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-08-14 06:08:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-08-14 07:00:25</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>supporting-our-band</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
    <category>fa6094d0-c8e0-4964-8deb-b6349a6dd281</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>