<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Booster Newsletter 10.17.14</title>
  <description>Hi Band Families,
 
It's hard to believe we are in our 8th Week of Football! This Friday is Senior B</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;It's hard to believe we are in our 8th Week of Football! This Friday is Senior Band Night. Halftime will be used to honor all the Senior Band Students and their parents. It is an honor that these students have dedicated 4 years to our band program! Their leadership helps carry on our traditions and defines who we are!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Please be sure to bring your store bought baked goods (Freshman) or water bottles/2 liter bottles of soda (Juniors) to Cafe 2 before rehearsal on Friday if you haven’t already turned them in. Remember, rehearsal starts promptly at 4 pm...this is an earlier start time due to Senior Band Night. Check &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Mr. Vitale’s website&lt;/a&gt; for the complete itinerary.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;After the game, the North Royalton High School Marching Band will perform the entire contest show for us so stick around after the game and enjoy the show!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Saturday's Contest is in Copley. Please visit Mr. Vitale’s website to get the latest details regarding our last competition before States.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;I would like you to know that the band is close to tying or beating some of their all-time record scores! These kids are doing an awesome job! I'm so proud to be a part of such an awesome organization! State contest here we come!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-10-17 07:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-10-18 07:23:04</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-booster-newsletter-10-17-14</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>