<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Coming Soon...Rhythm and Raffle!</title>
  <description>Dear Band Families,

As you know, our Rhythm and Raffle Fundraiser is just around the corner on Satu</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you know, our Rhythm and Raffle Fundraiser is just around the corner on Saturday, February 24th. It will be an evening full of family fun, fantastic music, and fabulous baskets. But did you know you can help make this event incredible with very little effort? The committee is hard at work looking for donations for those fabulous baskets and would love your help. No donation is too big or too small. Maybe you received a gift card for the holidays that you will never use. Or you’d like to advertise for your favorite salon with a gift certificate. Or let everyone know about that favorite bottle of wine you discovered. Or maybe you’d like to promote your business by becoming a sponsor at one of our four donor levels. All donors will be recognized in the program, in our local newspapers, and on the Band Booster website. Please click on &lt;a href="https://northroyaltonbandboosters.us15.list-manage.com/track/click?u=f9c4e414afe05390874757772&amp;amp;id=85bef17920&amp;amp;e=79b990d89d" style=""&gt;2018 Rhythm &amp;amp; Raffle Donations&lt;/a&gt; to see some of the items we are looking for. If you have something else in mind that you’d like to donate, please email Corresponding Secretary Regina Atkinson at &lt;a href="mailto:reggiem1209@yahoo.com"&gt;reggiem1209@yahoo.com&lt;/a&gt;. As always, thank you all for your support of our outstanding band program and we can’t wait to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2018-01-27 10:01:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2018-01-27 10:08:42</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>coming-soon-rhythm-and-raffle</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>