<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Booster Newsletter - Band Camp, Band T-Shirt &amp; Polos and More</title>
  <description>Welcome to the beginning of our 2016/2017 Marching Band Season! A few quick reminders as we start in</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the beginning of our 2016/2017 Marching Band Season! A few quick reminders as we start the season:&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Band Camp&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Band Camp is in session next week June 14-16th. Please check Mr. Vitale’s site for your practice times! Click here to visit the &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;director’s site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Please bookmark this site for reference and check back frequently. The site contains performance information, registration information and much more!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Band T-Shirts and Polos&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Band Boosters will be selling the required band t-shirts and polos after practice June 15th and 16th in Cafeteria 2 at 8PM. Please note that during registration you were asked if you intended to buy a t-shirt or polo. You did not actually order or pay for any t-shirts or polos at that time. This is a cash and carry sale. Prices are: T-shirts - $10 and Polos - $20. Cash or Check made out to the NR Band Boosters will be accepted! If you have any questions, please call Amanda Kost at 440-864-6543.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Band Shoes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Royalton Music Center will be at the school after practice on June 15 and 16 with the shoes that were ordered before May 28. RMC will be in cafeteria 2 at 8PM for the distribution of those paid orders.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Munching for Music&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a reminder that we are having a Dairy Queen Fundraiser all day Tuesday, June 14, at the Dairy Queen on Sprague Road near W 130th! Come out and have a treat and support the band! Please take the flier with you or let them know you are with the NRHS Marching Band!&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/FILES%2f2016%2f06%2fDairyQueenDay.jpg.axdx" alt="Dairy Queen Flyer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the weekend and we are off to a great season!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Amanda Kost&lt;br&gt;NRHS Band Booster President&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-06-09 21:06:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-06-09 21:13:06</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-booster-newsletter-band-camp-band-t-shirt-and-polos-and-more</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>