<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Uniform Distribution, Picture Day, Air Show &amp; More -  July 2014 Newsletter</title>
  <description>Hi Everyone,
                Welcome back to another great season with the North Royalton High Schoo</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Welcome back to another great season with the North Royalton High School Marching Band! What a great organization to be a part of! I look forward to volunteering my time to support it. It's hard to believe band camp starts this week! Please check the website (&lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com&lt;/a&gt;) often to stay in touch with the daily events during this busy time of year. As you will see below, there are many volunteer opportunities to help out! The success of this great organization is not only because we have some of the best directors around, or the best school district, or even the best kids. It really is because we have the best parents! Our involvement is what makes the wheels on the band bus go around! Think about it, without you, these kids wouldn't be here. Get ready for the busiest and potentially most rewarding time of the year.&lt;/p&gt;
[more]
                &lt;h3&gt;Marching Band Uniform Distribution - July 30&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; - August 1&lt;sup&gt;st&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;As previously announced, Band picture day is Wednesday, August 13&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;each Band member must have their uniform &lt;/strong&gt;before this date. Before you can receive your uniform your registration must be complete and all fees must be paid.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;h4&gt;Uniform Distribution Schedule:&lt;/h4&gt;
                &lt;ul&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Wednesday, July 30&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; – 6:00-9:00 – Seniors and Juniors&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Thursday, July 31&lt;sup&gt;st&lt;/sup&gt; – 6:00-9:00 – Seniors, Juniors and Sophomores &lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Friday, August 1&lt;sup&gt;st&lt;/sup&gt; – 6:00-9:00 - Freshmen&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Band Front: Wednesday, July 30&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; – All Band Front - 6pm to 9pm&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;/ul&gt;
                &lt;h3&gt;Picture Day - Wednesday, August 13&lt;/h3&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We need volunteers for picture day from 8 am to about 11am.&lt;/strong&gt; We need 3-4 parents with cameras that have removable memory cards to assist in taking pictures for Band Buttons. We also need a few parents to help organize the students at the High School Football Stadium. This will make the button lines go more quickly. If you are available, please contact Nancy Chester at &lt;a href="mailto:n.chester@sbcglobal.net" target="_blank"&gt;n.chester@sbcglobal.net&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;
                    We also &lt;b&gt;need 4 volunteers on Saturday, August 16&lt;/b&gt; to help with sorting and printing pictures for the buttons. We would like to have buttons available for sale at the Parent Preview Night. Contact Nancy Chester at &lt;a href="mailto:n.chester@sbcglobal.net" target="_blank"&gt;n.chester@sbcglobal.net&lt;/a&gt;
                    to help.
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;h3&gt;Cleveland Airshow - Major Band Fundraiser has returned! Volunteers Needed!&lt;/h3&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is a $10,000 fundraiser!&lt;/strong&gt; We need your help! We need volunteers for the airshow from 8:00 to 4:00 on Saturday, Aug. 30th, Sunday, Aug. 31st and Monday, Sept. 1st of Labor Day Weekend. We are short on all days, but especially Sunday and Monday. Sign up in groups of 2. All family members that are high school age or older are welcome!&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Air Show Job Description: &lt;/b&gt;Our job is to charge for admission and take tickets. We work in teams of two, usually an adult and a student.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;We work from 8:00- 4:00 or until the show reaches capacity. A box lunch and drinks are provided to workers. &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;We need 80 volunteers EACH DAY to reach our fundraising goal.&lt;/b&gt; If we don’t fill all the spots we will not get the full $10,000. Please help us to reach our goal! Go to the volunteer form on the Booster web page &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com&lt;/a&gt; or email Rich Hrin at &lt;a href="mailto:hrinmor@sbcglobal.net" target="_blank"&gt;hrinmor@sbcglobal.net&lt;/a&gt; to fill these open time slots!&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;h3&gt;First Booster Meeting and Freshman/New Booster Member Info Meeting &lt;/h3&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The first meeting will be in the first half of August.&lt;/b&gt; We will be having a Freshman Parent/New Member meeting afterward. More details coming soon. All parents are welcome. Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;h3&gt;1&lt;sup&gt;st&lt;/sup&gt; Annual Tailgate Parent Mixer - September 5&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Event – Mark the Date! – Friday, September 5 at 4:30 at the 3 Spot.&lt;/b&gt; - Come join us for our 1st annual Tailgate Parent Mixer before the first home game! Meet new people, get fired up before the game, and share your spirit for the Purple and the Gold! More details coming soon.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;h3&gt;New Website Coming Soon&lt;/h3&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Watch for our new web page look! We are putting the final touches on our website to make it easier to collect and distribute information. We hope you like it. The link to our website is &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;I'm looking forward to great season working with this great organization!&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Band Booster President&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-07-28 19:07:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-07-28 19:58:15</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>uniform-distribution-picture-day-air-show-and-more-july-2014-newsletter</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>a70d94a8-5d3c-44aa-b4d6-29cb41d521c4</category>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>