<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Our Raffle Fundraiser is this Saturday, from 6pm to 9pm at the 3-Spot</title>
  <description>Band Raffle Fundariaser, prize basket descriptions</description>
  <content>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you have already registered and paid, please check in at the door to receive your drink tickets and wristband for dinner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you haven’t registered already it isn’t too late! You can still join us by paying at the door. Please do NOT put an RSVPs/payment in the white band box. The cost is $25 per person. The buffet dinner includes pasta, pizza, wings, salad, dessert and four drink tickets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be basket raffles (raffle tickets 6 tickets/$5) and sideboard drawings throughout the evening, so bring your cash! All proceeds go to support our Band.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;This year we have OVER 35 baskets ranging in value from $105 to $300&lt;/b&gt;. They include wonderful items such as night out packages with overnight stays, golf outings, tickets to great places and events, massages, reserved stadium seats, restaurant gift cards, a fender acoustic guitar and much, much more! &lt;a href="/FILES%2f2015%2f02%2fRaffleBaskets.pdf.axdx"&gt;See the attached list for more details.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Please join us for a fun evening and help support our band students at the same time! Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-02-25 20:02:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-02-26 20:16:51</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>our-raffle-fundraiser-is-this-saturday-from-6pm-to-9pm-at-the-3-spot</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>