<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Booster Newsletter</title>
  <description>Hello everyone!
 
As another school year comes to a close, it is just remarkable to me the level of </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;As another school year comes to a close, it is just remarkable to me the level of dedication, support and passion our volunteers possess. It is no wonder our band program thrives! It is a trifecta that perpetuates the cycle. Very talented directors, dedicated parents and enthusiastic kids! A successful combination that once again has proven itself!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;I would like to thank you for all of your help this year. Whether it was a small effort or showing your continuous support. We could not have made it without you! Seeing our children succeed at this level and showing them we support their actions is worth the effort!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to our graduated boosters. Their knowledge will continue to carry on our tradition of excellence! It has been a pleasure working with you the past 3 years! Please join our alumni Facebook page and encourage your son/daughter to do the same! It’s a good way to stay involved! You are always welcome in the band family!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We would like to welcome our new parents! Join us on Facebook, become a booster member and get involved! It is very rewarding!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we look forward to next year, please be sure to pay close attention to the summer band camp dates in June as well as the end of July and August. The calendar can be found on Mr. Vitale’s website under Forms and PDFs. While you are on Mr. Vitale’s website, look around. He posts Director’s Notes, upcoming performance info and much, much more. Check it frequently throughout the year and get information and updates directly from him. &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Here is the link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Get Involved!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you haven't filled out your &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/volunteer-form"&gt;volunteer form&lt;/a&gt; for next school year, please follow the link below. It takes over 300 different jobs to run this program effectively. Get involved and join the team! If everyone does a little, it makes the work a whole lot easier and much more fun! If you are uncertain about what to choose, contact us, we will help guide you!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;AIRSHOW - Save The Date!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our first event will be the Airshow Labor Day weekend (Sept. 5-7). This event is our biggest money maker and requires no selling. We are responsible for parking cars and collecting ticket money. That’s it! But, we need 80 people per day. Please consider saving a spot during your Labor Day Weekend to help with this event. Parents and students are welcome to volunteer!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;If you have questions, Please don't hesitate to contact us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke Band Booster President holly.rmc@gmail.com 216-926-8836&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-06-14 09:06:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-06-14 09:23:25</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-booster-newsletter1</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>