<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Easter Seals Is This Weekend!</title>
  <description>Hi Parents,
 
 Our Easter Seals event is this weekend! The event runs Saturday from 9-6 and Sunday f</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Parents,&lt;/p&gt;
 
 &lt;p&gt;Our Easter Seals event is this weekend! The event runs Saturday from 9-6 and Sunday from 1-6. We will temporarily close for the parade and reopen again after. I would like to thank the numerous people that have signed up to help this weekend, we could not do it without you! This is a very successful fundraising opportunity that requires no out of pocket expenses, just a little of your time and the willingness to clean out your unwanted soft goods from your closets!!!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Here are the final details...&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you are scheduled to work…&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Come dressed for the weather - hopefully, we will be able to dodge the raindrops! (But you can hide out in the truck if rain is eminent.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will bring 4 plastic chairs for you to sit on.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only accept soft goods - ABSOLUTELY NO HOUSEHOLD NICKNACKS, PICTURE FRAMES, LAMPS, BOOKS, CD'S etc. WILL BE ACCEPTED.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If a person donates these unacceptable goods, try to kindly give them back and explain why...or just set them aside and we will dispose of them after the sale.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NO SLEEPING BAGS OR PILLOWS ARE PERMITTED. However, stuffed animals and all other bedding items are acceptable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are expecting to come close to filling the entire truck, so please start at the back of the truck and completely fill that area before moving forward.&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ol&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;That's it! We truly appreciate you! There are a few open spots on Saturday and Sunday. Check out the link below and sign up. It is very easy and actually quite fun and rewarding to see how many people are helping a really good cause.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-easter2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here's the sign up genius link.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to seeing everyone this weekend!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Questions? Text or call me at 216-926-8836&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-08-20 06:08:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-08-20 06:56:08</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>easter-seals-is-this-weekend</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
    <category>fa6094d0-c8e0-4964-8deb-b6349a6dd281</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>