<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>OMEA State Contest</title>
  <description>Hello Fellow Band Parents,
 
We are very proud to be sponsoring the OMEA States event in our school!</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Fellow Band Parents,&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We are very proud to be sponsoring the OMEA States event in our school!  As you know, our bands SWEPT the Westlake District Band Contest with SUPERIOR ratings.  Let’s show our support and spirit and give our visiting bands a WARM welcome to NRHS!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;State Band Contest is on &lt;b&gt;Friday, April 28 (3:30-11:30 pm)&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Saturday, April 29 (7:30-11:30 am)&lt;/b&gt;.  It takes roughly 100 volunteers to support this event! We only have 25% of the spots filled. It is another significant fundraiser for the Band Boosters and will be successful because of our parent volunteers. &lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;All band students will be assigned a job by Mr. Vitale to help with hosting this event. Please consider joining us for a 3 hour (or more) position of your choice. It's a great way to be with friends, show your NORO pride and help out the band! The jobs are simple, and we can assure you that, due to the flexibility of the schedule, you will get to see your student perform.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Please &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-omea1"&gt;&lt;b&gt;click on this link and sign up&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; today!&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;p&gt;You can also &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-easter1"&gt;&lt;b&gt;click here to help with the Easter Seals Fill the Truck fundraiser&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; on Friday and Saturday, April 28-29!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-03-23 07:03:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-03-23 07:18:22</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>omea-state-contest</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>