<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Senior Band Night Donation Requests</title>
  <description>Hi Freshman Band Families,

On Friday, October 17, we will be honoring the senior band members. Dinn</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi Freshman Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On &lt;b&gt;Friday, October 17,&lt;/b&gt; we will be honoring the senior band members. Dinner for them and their immediate family will be served at 5:30, right after practice and before the game. The rest of the band will enjoy pizza, bakery and beverages. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are asking all Freshman Band Families to bring a &lt;b&gt;store bought dessert &lt;/b&gt;with &lt;b&gt;NO peanuts&lt;/b&gt; to this event. Please send your dessert with your band student and have them drop it off in Cafeteria 2 &lt;i&gt;before &lt;/i&gt;they go to practice.  Please put your last name on the dessert.  No dessert should be dropped off in the band room. Someone will be in Cafeteria 2 before practice to take the dessert.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions, please contact me at &lt;a href="tel:440-864-6543"&gt;440-864-6543&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your support and Go Bears!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regards,&lt;br&gt;
Amanda Kost&lt;br&gt;
Hospitality Chair&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi Junior Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;

On Friday, October 17, we will be honoring the senior band members. Dinner for them and their immediate family will be served at 5:30, right after practice and before the game. The rest of the band will enjoy pizza, bakery and beverages. &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are asking all Junior Band Families to bring beverages to this event. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LAST NAME - A - K &lt;/b&gt;— Please send 1 case of water with your band student and have them drop it off in Cafeteria 2 before they go to practice or you can drop it off at my place of business by the front door Monday thru Thursday 8:00am - 7:30pm.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LAST NAME - M - Z&lt;/b&gt; — Please send 2 or 3 — 2 liter bottles of soft drinks (Sprite, Mountain Dew or Pepsi). Please send in the soft drinks with your band student and have them drop it off in Cafeteria 2 before they go to practice or you can drop it off at my place of business by the front door Monday thru Thursday 8:00am - 7:30pm.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My business address is &lt;b&gt;Balanced Fitness, 6418 Royalton Road&lt;/b&gt; directly BEHIND Key Bank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please put your last name on the case of water and/or the soft drinks so I know who dropped off the beverages. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No beverages should be dropped off in the band room. 
Someone will be in Cafeteria 2 before practice to accept your donation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions, please contact me at &lt;a href="tel:440-864-6543"&gt;440-864-6543&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your support and Go Bears!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regards,&lt;br&gt;
Amanda Kost&lt;br&gt;
Hospitality Chair&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-09-30 19:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-09-30 20:48:32</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>freshman-junior-food-and-beverage-requests</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>