<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Booster News: Solo and Ensemble, Raffle Fundraiser, Tuxes for Sale and more</title>
  <description>Hello Parents,Happy New Year! It is always difficult for me to believe how much faster time moves as</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Parents,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Happy New Year! It is always difficult for me to believe how much faster time moves as we get older. Our kids really keep us moving. Instead of our children being a part of our lives, it seems we are a part of theirs at this age. I am constantly reminded how amazing these band students are, and it is an absolute pleasure to volunteer my time for each and every one of these musicians.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Solo And Ensemble - Feb. 6&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their next event is Solo and Ensemble Contest on Feb. 6 at Tri C. Not all students participate in this event, but if your musician is, be sure to check Mr. Vitale's directors page for specific details regarding this event.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;A Huge Thank You To Our November - December Volunteers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although marching band season has come and gone, a significant amount of booster projects and committees have been hard at work! The concert and marching uniform committees collected and distributed uniforms from over 270 students and prepared the marching uniforms for our Disney trip. The fruit sale committee unloaded, sorted and distributed countless pounds of juicy and delicious citrus. The committee that handles the holiday concert reservations worked in conjunction with the membership committee to provide seats for our 3 performances and the holiday ornaments and marching band CD's were sold at every holiday concert. Thanks to all of these fabulous volunteers for their tireless efforts!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Feb 1 Community Meeting&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We often times come together to support our band program. Well, now it is time for our band family to put our heads together at the community meeting. Our school district truly values our voice. Plan to attend this very important meeting on Monday, February 1 at 7:00 pm in the High School PAC. See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Save The Date - It’s Time To Do Something Fun For Us - Saturday, Feb. 27, At 5:30 PM&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Annual Raffle Fundraiser Social event is scheduled for Feb.27 at Slim And Chubby's in Strongsville from 5:30-8:30 pm. So, save the date, get your friends together and enjoy some well deserved time together with our band family. The opportunities to win are limitless and the time you spend with friends is priceless!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Gently Used Tuxes For Sale - $30&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may have noticed that we are, once again, trying to sell our gently worn tuxes. Prom season will be upon us. Purchasing one of our tuxes is significantly less expensive than renting. Also, if you are involved in an honors ensemble or are planning to perform in college, the expectation to wear a tux will always be a reality. If you are interested or know someone that might be interested, let us know. The tux information will be posted on our website.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Florida Trip Update&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 11 short weeks our kids will be headed to Florida for our spring break trip (March 27 - April 3). Even though winter has gotten a late start, this still actually sounds quite nice!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Band Booster Meeting&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our next booster meeting is scheduled for Monday, January 25, at 7:00 pm in the High School Media Center. Come join us!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Committee Positions For Next Year&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm pleased to say that most volunteers are returning to their positions for next year, however, if you are NOT PLANNING TO RETURN, please let us know so that we can work together to find a replacement. AND if you are interested in getting more involved, please contact us or join us at our January meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Stay Warm!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;br&gt;Band Booster President&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-01-11 19:01:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-01-11 19:48:14</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-booster-news-solo-and-ensemble-raffle-fundraiser-tuxes-for-sale-and-more</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>