<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Easter Seals 'Fill The Truck' Fundraiser - April 23rd</title>
  <description>Easter Seals Northern Ohio is once again partnering with North Royalton Band Boosters to give back t</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Easter Seals Northern Ohio is once again partnering with North Royalton Band Boosters to give back to the community while helping children and adults with disabilities.  North Royalton Band Boosters is hosting a “Fill the Truck” fundraiser to benefit the North Royalton Marching Band. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;As you ‘change’ your closet for the summer season, please support our fundraiser:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="well"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Date: &lt;/b&gt;  APRIL 23RD&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt;  9am – 6pm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location:&lt;/b&gt;    North Royalton Board of Education, 6579 Royalton Road&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;What are we collecting:&lt;/b&gt;  ANY cloth items (even stained or torn), shoes, boots, purses&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;We need your help!  &lt;a href="www.SignUpGenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-easter1"&gt;Click here to volunteer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;North Royalton Band Boosters will be compensated based on the number of bags/pounds of cloth collected.  Acceptable items include (but are not limited to): clothing, comforters, blankets, towels, sheets, shoes, accessories, and purses. The Boosters will only earn money from those types of cloth donations listed above.  Even stained or torn items can be recycled into something else!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We challenge every North Royalton student to donate at least one bag of cloth.  Tell your friends and neighbors!  You do not need to have a student at North Royalton to donate items.  All donors will receive a tax-deductible receipt!  If you have any questions, please feel free to contact Amanda Kost at &lt;a href="mailto:amandabethkost@gmail.com"&gt;amandabethkost@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or at 440-864-6543.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-03-01 20:03:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-03-01 20:22:47</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>easter-seals-fill-the-truck-fundraiser-april-23rd</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>