<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Car Raffle Tickets Due Friday</title>
  <description>Dear Band Boosters and Band Members (please share with your kids):
 
We are in the final week of our</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Boosters and Band Members (please share with your kids):&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We are in the final week of our car raffle fundraiser. For those of you who have returned or sold your tickets, Thank You! Every sold ticket gives ten more dollars to support our band program. Special thanks to those families who made the extra effort to sell extra tickets. Well done!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We still have the rest of this week to sell tickets and raise more money for the NRHS Band. Please do your best to contact friends and family in these final days to offer a chance to win a new car for $20.00. Our goal is to raise as much money as we can in this last week. If you find an interested party but have already turned in your tickets, call me and I can get a ticket to you.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Please remember that &lt;b&gt;all tickets, sold or unsold, must be returned by this Friday, October 31!&lt;/b&gt; If you return your sold tickets to the white box by Friday before the game, you can find your hand-warmers outside the band room on Saturday morning, just in time for the 40 degree weather in Columbus!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thanks again for your attention and support of NRHS Band Boosters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for your hard work, Kids and Good Luck at States!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Jane Coleman&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="tel:440-759-9864"&gt;
440-759-9864&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-10-27 06:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-10-27 06:10:28</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>car-raffle-tickets-due-friday</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>