<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Fruit Sale - Thank You</title>
  <description>Hello Band Families!
 
We hope all of you had a wonderful break, holiday season, snow/cold days and </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Band Families!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We hope all of you had a wonderful break, holiday season, snow/cold days and extra days off with your families.  We hope you enjoyed eating lots of fruit during these past few weeks too!  We want to say thank you very much to everyone who helped make the fruit sale a huge success!  Our final profit amount is $9,600!  This truly could not have been accomplished without all of you.  Whether you helped sign out packets for blitz weekend, walked around and sold fruit during the blitz weekend, drove kids around so that they could sell fruit during the blitz weekend, asked friends and relatives to buy fruit, bought fruit yourself, helped unload the fruit from the truck, helped count fruit boxes, helped make up bags of fruit, helped pick fruit orders, helped take fruit orders to cars, delivered fruit from the blitz weekend or to those you personally sold to, bought extra fruit after the sale, ate fruit, saved your fruit bag and returned it to us for next year, sent out countless emails about the fruit sale, read countless emails about the fruit sale, gave ideas on how to improve the fruit sale or just had kind words to offer about the fruit or the sale in general.....THANK YOU!!!  We truly appreciate everything that everyone did to make this such a great fundraiser!  We counted on a lot of people to help out in many ways, and we want you to know that your efforts were definitely noticed.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We received some wonderful donations from two local businesses that we want to mention.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lake Erie Graphics, Inc.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
    5372 W. 130th Street, Brook Park&lt;br&gt;
    (216) 265-7575&lt;br&gt;
    &lt;a href="http://www.lakeeriegraphics.com"&gt;www.lakeeriegraphics.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Augie's Pizza &amp;amp; Ribs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
    14084 State Road, North Royalton&lt;br&gt;
    440-237-2080&lt;br&gt;
    &lt;a href="http://www.augiescatering.com"&gt;www.augiescatering.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We really appreciate these businesses supporting our fundraiser and our band.  Please consider patronizing these businesses when you are in need of the products they provide.&lt;/p&gt;
   
&lt;p&gt;Be watching for information about the 2015 Fruit Sale in about seven months!  :)&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Karen &amp;amp; Susie&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-01-19 18:01:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-01-19 18:25:51</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>fruit-sale-thank-you</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>