<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>It's a Busy Time in Our Band Nation!!</title>
  <description>Hello Everyone!
 
What a great showing by our NoRo Band Nation this past weekend! We had many people</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello Everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;What a great showing by our NoRo Band Nation this past weekend! We had many people take notice of all the North Royalton people helping out at the air show and received many compliments on our dedication to this event! The administration from the air show just loves having us involved. We make their job so much easier. It truly is a win – win experience for us all! And…we maximized our goal! Thank You so much for helping out with this important fundraiser! Special thanks goes out to all the team leaders as well as Becky Cozzens, Becky Humes and Heidi Eisaman for their extra involvement in making sure everything went smoothly! We hit another home run!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;As I stated at our Meet The Band Night, in order to avoid adding extra fundraisers to make up for the loss of our Market Day fundraiser, we felt it was a good idea to maximize the earning potential of our current fundraisers. So far, we have done just that! Our next goal is to sell as many of the Car Raffle Tickets as we can, sell fruit, promote Easter Seals and get involved in our Band Festival! Below is a list of our active fundraisers.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Car Raffle –&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The deadline is this Friday, Sept. 11. All ticket stubs, money, and unsold tickets must be returned by this deadline. A winner of a Contest Hoodie will be drawn from all the students that sold both of their tickets. There is also a potential of $200 cash if your name is drawn at the Homecoming football game! So far, it appears we are doing well with this fundraiser too!! Keep selling those tickets!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sale –&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event kicks off with our neighborhood canvas event this weekend – Please be sure your team captain picks up the fruit sale packet Wednesday Evening after the 6-9 rehearsal. All students that return their sales forms from the blitz on Monday will be treated to pizza, compliments of the band boosters! The sale runs through Oct. 17!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;50/50 –&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This fundraiser is operated by a small group of band parents that walk around the home games selling 50/50 raffle tickets. This has been a very beneficial fundraiser to us. If you are interested in helping out, contact Elisa Race at 216-407-5625 or &lt;a href="mailto:erace@wideopenwest.com"&gt;erace@wideopenwest.com&lt;/a&gt;. I believe she could use a few more people.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Membership –&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our membership drive is going on now. Membership will be at our first home game this Friday…so if you haven’t been able to join our boosters, check us out at our table near the front gate on Friday! If you are unable to join us at this time, the membership form is always available on our website! Just print off a copy and send it and your payment with your band student to put in the white box located in the band room.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Spirit Buttons –&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buttons will be available at the home football game this Friday! You will be able to not only pick up your orders, but you will be able to order new buttons at this time as well! Look for the table near the main entrance!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Easter Seals –&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Encore Performance will take place the same day as our Band Festival Event - Saturday, Sept. 19 from 9am – 8pm. Sign Ups are now located in the Sign Ups are located in the &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054eafa729a02-nrhs"&gt;Band Festival Sign Up Genius&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Band Festival –&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is our chance to Shine! Not only do the kids get to showcase their talents to 8 other schools, we get to show what great hosts we are and how dedicated we are to our Marching Band Program. Because this event is so important, there is a significant need for volunteers. Approximately 50 parents are needed to effectively host this event. Most of these jobs are easy and fun! Please &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054eafa729a02-nrhs"&gt;check out the Sign Up Genius link and join us&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Band Fest will be our last fundraiser that requires a large group of volunteers until May. However, considering the fact that we had over 250 volunteers this past weekend, the 50 volunteers needed to run this event is a mere 1/5 the size! Keep up the great effort and STAY ACTIVE! We Really Need Your Help!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We do understand that there are a great deal of fundraising events happening at the same time, but the realization is that these events make up a significant part of our yearly budget and cannot be held at any other time. The end is in sight! Thank you again to ALL our volunteers and for all you do as parents! We see how hard our kids work to create their show for us; the least we can do is support them with our time!!! This proves to them that we find value in what they do!!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke Band Booster President&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-09-10 21:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-09-10 21:09:29</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>it-s-a-busy-time-in-our-band-nation</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>