<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Fest Info</title>
  <description>Hello NRHS Marching Band Parents!
 
We are less than a week away from our very own Band Festival!!! </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello NRHS Marching Band Parents!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We are less than a week away from our very own Band Festival!!! I cannot wait to see our kids perform their contest show!! We are expecting over 4000 people on Saturday! That's a large crowd of band kids and parents all in one place at one time when you really think about it! AND...all 8 bands are going to perform a final selection at the end of the night! Get your recorders ready for that one! What a great GRAND FINALE!!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;We really need help this Saturday!&lt;/b&gt; We are welcoming a large number of people into our home and we want to be good hosts and make a good impression. We cannot do that if we don’t fill our volunteer spots. We have spots for both Band Fest and the Easter Seals drive. The jobs are easy and fun! And you will be able to watch your student perform the contest show! If you have any questions about what to sign up for, call Amanda at 440-864-6543 and she will help you out.&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054eafa729a02-nrhs"&gt;Please sign up here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Also, remember to sell fruit, get your car raffle tickets turned in, and fill your bags with your Easter Seals donations!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to working with you and enjoying the show on Saturday! Come join us!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke &lt;br&gt;Band Booster President&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-09-15 20:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-09-15 20:33:51</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-fest-info</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6defe6a0-9313-4c69-ade3-77b41afc975c</category>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>