<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Air Show Information</title>
  <description>We Need Your Help!
Dear Parents,
Our biggest fund raiser is the Air Show. We work in the parking lot</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;We Need Your Help!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear Parents,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our biggest fund raiser is the Air Show. We work in the parking lots and at the entrance gates Labor Day weekend rain or shine. We have a good time!&amp;nbsp;The air show provides us with lunch,&amp;nbsp;and we get free admission to the Air Show once our shift is over. For new parents, this is a way&amp;nbsp;to spend time with your teen and meet other band families. Funds from this event are budgeted&amp;nbsp;to the marching band contest show materials and equipment. Without the Air Show, we do not have a quality marching band contest show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are in need of a committee of four to five people to take over coordinating the air show. I understand this is last minute. Doug Payne will be the lead for the committee. Please make a decision to be part of this committee so we can make this event a success and fund the contest show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your support and dedication to the band program and most importantly the bandos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Care,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kathy Payne&lt;br&gt;NRHS Band Booster&amp;nbsp;President&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Air Show Oops! 😉 Correction&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear Parents,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We appreciate you all and your patience as we as your New Band Booster Board learn all the ropes.&amp;nbsp;We had a bit of information get crisscrossed and we wanted to let you know the funds we raise from the Air Show are allocated to the Band Trip Fund i.e. the Disney Trip, not our contest&amp;nbsp;show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that said, this is our largest fund raiser&amp;nbsp; We work in the parking lots and at the entrance gates&amp;nbsp;Labor Day weekend rain or shine and we have a great&amp;nbsp;time! We look forward to having you help volunteer as well as if you are willing to co-chair please let us know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your support and dedication to the band program and most importantly the bandos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Care,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kathy Payne&lt;br&gt;NRHS Band Booster&amp;nbsp;President&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2018-06-16 07:06:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2018-06-16 07:26:13</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>air-show-information</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>