<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>NRMB Newsletter – September 19, 2016</title>
  <description>WOW! The ELEMENTS sure helped our contest show get off the ground at Festival of Bands! FANTASTIC jo</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;WOW! The ELEMENTS sure helped our contest show get off the ground at Festival of Bands! FANTASTIC job to our bandos… performing so well despite the crazy rainstorm!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;By The Way, did you see the hidden ‘Mickey Mouse’ in movement 3?? Keep looking!!!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;LINKS you need to know:&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Mr. Vitale’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandboosters.com"&gt;Band Booster’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/North-Royalton-Band-Boosters/164850233634290"&gt;FaceBook North Royalton Band Boosters&lt;/a&gt; -- Like Us!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other Fundraisers: GFS and Smile.Amazon.com (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DATES you need to know:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 23 – Football game – AWAY Hudson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SEPT 26 – BAND BOOSTER MEETING – MEDIA CENTER 7PM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 30 – Football game – AWAY Wadsworth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 30 – Car Raffle Tickets are DUE in white band box.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OCT 7 – SENIOR BAND NIGHT -- more info coming!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oct 7 – Football game – HOME Brecksville/Broadview Hts --- HOMECOMING!&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;North Royalton Stadium Foundation Car Raffle&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marching Band sales have just two weeks left to sell raffle tickets! Please return your sold ticket stubs and money to the white band box by Friday, September 30th. If you have not sold them by then, return them in the original ticket envelope. The $20.00 cost of any tickets not returned will be charged to you.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;A word document that you can personalize to help sell to family and friends is attached to this newsletter. Please consider sending out an email or posting your version to social media today! The more tickets you sell, the more money we have for band and the greater your chances of winning $500.00!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Please email or text me if you need additional tickets or have questions. Jane Coleman mattnjane.coleman@att.net 440-759-9864 Thank You!&lt;/p&gt;
 

 
&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sale - Keep Selling Fruit! We would love to sell a TRUCKload&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Marching Band Fruit Sale is officially underway. Your bando did receive their PERSONAL packet to sell fruit to family and friends last Wednesday. Forms are due back to the White Band box by October 15th! If you need another, they are in the band room.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Membership&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our membership drive is underway! JOIN the Band Boosters! There are many membership levels! Print the form at the bottom of this newsletter OR go to the &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/page/band-booster-membership"&gt;Membership page&lt;/a&gt; to get the form! Questions?&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Contact: Shirley Berish – 440-667-0811&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;50/50 Raffle: We Still Need Help&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did you hear how large our payout was on Sept 16? We have been giving $1000+ away each home game…. and it is all due to you--- our volunteers! Let’s keep the payout growing!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We can use help with our next two home games! Please &lt;a href="http://www.SignUpGenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-5050"&gt;click this link&lt;/a&gt; or contact: Elisa Race -- 216-407-5625&lt;/p&gt;
 

 &lt;h3&gt;Other Fundraisers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GFS: If you shop at GFS, remember to mention: North Royalton Band Boosters and Marching Band at checkout. We have an account there and accumulate $$$$ for everything YOU spend!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smile.Amazon Are you an Amazon shopper? Set up a SMILE.AMAZON account and a percentage of what you purchase will be added to the North Royalton Band Booster account:&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;YOU can help North Royalton High School Band Boosters when you shop for back-to-school supplies and many other items that you purchase from Amazon! This link will help you set up your SMILE account!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Support us when you shop for back-to-school items. #StartWithaSmile at &lt;a href="http://smile.amazon.com/ch/34-1817202"&gt;http://smile.amazon.com/ch/34-1817202&lt;/a&gt; and Amazon donates.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-09-19 20:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-09-19 21:15:01</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>nrmb-newsletter-september-19-2016</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>