<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>NRMB Newsletter – December 12, 2016</title>
  <description>DATES you need to know:

Dec 18 -19 – EASTER SEALS COLLECTION
Dec 18 -19 – Holiday Shows
 
This will</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;DATES you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dec 18 -19 – EASTER SEALS COLLECTION&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dec 18 -19 – Holiday Shows&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be the final newsletter for 2106… Have a happy, safe and peaceful Holiday from the Exec Board!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;READ BELOW:&lt;/b&gt; Final date for Holiday Tickets and Easter Seals Info!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OPEN CHAIRPOSITION: FRUIT SALE CHAIRPeople (2) NEEDED: Contact: Susie Perez – 440-877-1299&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LINKS you need to know:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonhighschoolband.com"&gt;Mr. Vitale’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://northroyaltonbandboosters.com"&gt;Band Booster’s Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/North-Royalton-Band-Boosters/164850233634290"&gt;FaceBook North Royalton Band Boosters -- Like Us!!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other Fundraisers: GFS and Smile.Amazon.com (see below)&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;/ul&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Holiday Ticket Order Form&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Holiday Concerts are just around the corner! The absolute final date to turn in your ticket order is Tuesday, December 13. NO ORDERS WILL BE ACCEPTED AFTER THIS DATE! Any seats still available may be purchased at the door the day of the concert. Please don't delay as seating is limited. &lt;a href="/FILES%2f2016%2f11%2f2016_HolidayConcertTicketOrderForm.pdf.axdx"&gt;Download Order Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions regarding your ticket order, please contact Janet Frantz: 440-877-1627 or &lt;a href="mailto:janetfrantz516@gmail.com"&gt;janetfrantz516@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Easter Seals&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The NRHS Band is hosting a "Fill the Truck" event for Easter Seals on Sunday, December 18 (12pm-2pm and 4pm-7pm) and Monday, December 19 (4pm-7pm). The truck will be parked outside the NRHS Performance Arts Center entrance and the band will be collecting clothing, blankets, towels, shoes, purses, stuffed animals, cloth lunchboxes and backpacks, etc. Even stained items can be recycled! All donations are tax-deductible and you will receive a receipt when you drop off your items. What a great way to help the band and the community while cleaning out your closets! Thanks for your support!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;We also need a few people to help man the truck for short periods. The truck will be closed during performances! Please consider helping us and &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/10c0a45a5a92ca4f49-easter"&gt;sign up through the link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Questions? Contact: Holly Michalke -- 216-926-8836&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Other Fundraisers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GFS: If you shop at GFS, remember to mention: North Royalton Band Boosters and Marching Band at checkout. We have an account there and accumulate $$$$ for everything YOU spend!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Smile.Amazon Are you an Amazon shopper? Set up a SMILE.AMAZON account and a percentage of what you purchase will be added to the North Royalton Band Booster account:&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;YOU can help North Royalton High School Band Boosters when you shop for back-to-school supplies and many other items that you purchase from Amazon! This link will help you set up your SMILE account!.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Support us when you shop for back-to-school items. #StartWithaSmile at &lt;a href="http://smile.amazon.com/ch/34-1817202"&gt;http://smile.amazon.com/ch/34-1817202&lt;/a&gt; and Amazon donates.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2016-12-12 18:12:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-12-12 19:04:12</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>nrmb-newsletter-december-12-2016</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>