<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Fruit Sale Reminder</title>
  <description>The kids did a wonderful job during the Blitz Weekend for the FRUIT SALE. Thank you all for your har</description>
  <content>&lt;img style="-webkit-user-select: none" class="pull-right" src="http://highcountrypress.com/weekly/2010/10-21-10/00_photos/rotary.jpg"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The kids did a wonderful job during the Blitz Weekend for the FRUIT SALE. Thank you all for your hard work! Just as a reminder though, the FRUIT SALE is still continuing! Please keep asking friends, family members, neighbors, co-workers, etc. to support the marching band by purchasing some tasty, fresh, Florida fruit!  You can encourage them to help us out by telling them that the fruit is picked, loaded on the truck and immediately driven up to us, so it's the freshest fruit they will probably have all season! Besides enjoying the yummy, juicy fruit, they will also get a warm feeling inside knowing they have helped the band out in a huge way!  Please feel free to turn in any completed order forms at any time to the white box in the band room. Extra forms are available on the table next to the white box in the band room. &lt;b&gt;All orders are due in by October 17th&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/page/Fruit-Sale-Order-Form" class="cta-purple buzz-out"&gt;Fruit Sale Order Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for supporting our great band program!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Susie &amp;amp; Karen&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-10-04 07:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-10-04 10:30:25</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>fruit-sale-reminder</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
    <category>8a8649e2-a13d-47f8-abcb-7c344cb83e51</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>