<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Car Raffle Sale</title>
  <description>Some notes about The Stadium Foundation Car Raffle (Please share with your band member)

The deadlin</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Some notes about The Stadium Foundation Car Raffle (Please share with your band member)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The deadline to turn in money, ticket stubs, and unsold tickets is &lt;b&gt;Friday, September 11&lt;/b&gt;. Students who sell their tickets by this deadline have a chance to &lt;b&gt;win $200.00&lt;/b&gt; in a drawing at the Homecoming Game on Sept. 25th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are working with other NRHS groups to raise money for the Stadium Foundation, but &lt;b&gt;we get to keep $10.00 of every ticket WE sell&lt;/b&gt;. Our goal is for 100% participation from each band member. To help you with your sales we've provided two resources that are easy to access:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attached is a letter that each student can personalize by filling in the missing information and emailing to friends and family. (You know all those Aunts &amp;amp; Uncles &amp;amp; Grandparents who comment on how great you bandos are? Give them a chance to show their support by buying a raffle ticket.) We have included a teaser about the upcoming fruit sale, too. In case people don't want raffle tickets, maybe they will buy some fruit for the next fundraiser.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;We have also posted two photos on the &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/North-Royalton-Band-Boosters/164850233634290"&gt;Band Booster Facebook Page&lt;/a&gt; that everyone can share to their own wall. Write a customized note to go with it and let people know how to contact you for tickets. It's easy to find customers if you just get the word out.&lt;/li&gt;


&lt;p&gt;It is very important that you return your money and tickets by September 11th. We really want each band member to sell their two tickets. However, &lt;i&gt;if you have no intention of selling your tickets, please return them to the band box ASAP&lt;/i&gt;. Another student might want them for their sales. Each ticket, sold or unsold, must be accounted for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember, you could win $200.00 just for selling your tickets by September 11th AND ... &lt;b&gt;if you sell both tickets you could win a free contest hoodie from Band Boosters, too!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kids, Thank You for doing your part. Parents, Thank YOU for your help! Good Luck!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jane Coleman ~ Car Raffle Chair &lt;a href="mailto:mattnjane.coleman@att.net"&gt;mattnjane.coleman@att.net&lt;/a&gt; 440-759-9864&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-09-04 18:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-09-04 18:25:26</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>car-raffle-sale</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>