<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Munching For Music Weekend+</title>
  <description>Dear Band Families,

 
You are reading that correctly! We are about to have an entire weekend+ to su</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Dear Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;p&gt;You are reading that correctly! We are about to have an entire weekend+ to support Munching for Music! Our friends at &lt;b&gt;Tom+Chee&lt;/b&gt; have generously offered to donate 15% of sales from our revenue back to our band! Even better, they are giving us a whole weekend+ to do it! Crazy! Three whole days to help raise funds for the band! You can tell this is an exciting event because of all of the exclamation marks in this paragraph!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please plan on eating at &lt;b&gt;Tom+Chee on February 10,11 &amp;amp;12, 2018, Saturday, Sunday and Monday&lt;/b&gt;. Yes, we are suggesting to eat there each one of those days. There are plenty of choices to keep things from getting boring. They offer grilled cheese plus other melts, soups, salads, and sides. If you’re really feeling adventurous, try a filled, grilled donut! WHAT?! Yes, grilled donuts with various fillings! That alone is a great reason to eat there for an entire weekend!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please &lt;a href="https://northroyaltonbandboosters.us15.list-manage.com/track/click?u=f9c4e414afe05390874757772&amp;amp;id=1f5e55c9c2&amp;amp;e=79b990d89d"&gt;print out the attached flyer&lt;/a&gt;, or pick up a copy from the band room, and take it with you to the restaurant. This will be the best way to ensure we get credit for your purchase. You can also show the flyer on your phone if you forget to take one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spend an early Valentine’s Day with your loved one at TOM+CHEE!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Thank you supporting our band!&lt;/p&gt;
 </content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2018-02-08 07:02:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2018-02-08 07:19:39</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>munching-for-music-weekend</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>