<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Fruit Blitz,Donations Needed,Disney and more!</title>
  <description>WOW! Band Fest was certainly a MAGICAL night for all… so many wonderful comments from our visitors a</description>
  <content>
&lt;p&gt;WOW! Band Fest was certainly a MAGICAL night for all… so many wonderful comments from our visitors and the music and performances were outstanding! A sincere THANK YOU to everyone that helped make this evening a HUGE success!&lt;/p&gt;

 

&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sale Blitz is This Weekend&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Fruit Sale Blitz weekend has been changed to SEPT 23 – 24 due to Hurricane Irma. We appreciate your flexibility. Packets will be passed out Sept. 20 after 6-9 practice. Please see Mr. Vitale’s website for report time changes for the Twinsburg game due to the Pizza Party the Boosters will be giving the band. After rehearsal, stop by Café 2 for Pizza as a Thank You from the Boosters! Any questions? Contact: Jayme Poplin – 440-457-7417 or Heidi Cmich – 216-244-2968&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Donations Needed For the Pizza Blitz Party&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are in need of water, paper plates and napkin donations for our Pizza Blitz Party on Saturday. If you are able to donate, &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-fruit"&gt;please follow this link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;h3&gt;Chaperones Needed For Twinsburg Game&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just a reminder that the Twinsburg game is SATURDAY, SEPTEMBER 23 at 7pm. We still need FOUR chaperones!!! &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944A5AE2FA4FF2-20175"&gt;To volunteer:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;h3&gt;Disney Trip Registration is Still Open&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is not too late to register for the Disney trip! Registration will remain open until the end of September. &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonhighschoolband.com/yahoo_site_admin/assets/docs/Disney2018FirstLetterHome.pdf"&gt;To register&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 
&lt;h3&gt;Car Raffle Tickets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your bando received two car raffle tickets to sell after the practice last Wednesday. Sold tickets and payment should be returned to the white band box. You can get extra tickets to sell by contacting Joyce Fink 440-237-1636.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt;Volunteer Button on Band Booster Webpage&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An easy, one stop volunteer location is now on the homepage of the Band Booster website. The button is top left and by clicking you can see every event this going on with open volunteer opportunities!&lt;/p&gt;
 

&lt;p&gt;Mark Your Calendar!&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 23 – ** NEW DATE** FRUIT SALE BLITZ AND PIZZA PARTY.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 23 – AWAY – Twinsburg **NOTE THE DATE CHANGE!!**&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 25 – Booster Meeting - 7pm in the Media Center&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 29 – HOME - Hudson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sept 30 – CONTEST – Avon Lake&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-09-21 07:09:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-09-21 08:03:50</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>fruit-blitz-donations-needed-disney-and-more</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>53e26df9-477c-4527-97c4-bce1fcd9688b</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>