<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Band Boosters News - Fundraiser/Volunteer Postings</title>
  <description>Band Families,
    Cabin fever has left me with time to reflect on many things. One of which is how </description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;Band Families,&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Cabin fever has left me with time to reflect on many things. One of which is how fortunate I feel to belong to such a strong and supportive organization that truly values the benefits of music education. It is hard to believe more than half of the 2014-15 school year is over. And in true NR fashion, our ensembles sound as good as ever! The Holiday Concerts were AMAZING!!! We do have talented band directors, but let’s face it, it is our children and our involvement that keeps this fine tradition alive!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Raffle Night Approaching&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Saturday, February 28, is our annual Raffle Night at The 3 Spot -&lt;/b&gt; There is still space available and the event promises to be a great time! It is an important event that will help us reach our fundraising goal for the season while enjoying time with friends! This is my favorite fundraiser of the year! The baskets are AMAZING and the door prizes and raffles add a fun game of chance to the evening. Shirley, Rima and Lynn have worked hard to put together this event for you!! We are certain you will not be disappointed! Please consider adding this event to your calendar! &lt;a href="http://www.northroyaltonbandboosters.com/FILES%2f2015%2f01%2fBandRaffle2015.pdf.axdx"&gt;Attached is the flier&lt;/a&gt; with the details for the evening. You can pre-register at our band booster meeting on Monday evening or return the attached form with payment to the white band box at school.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;*Although a limited number of tickets will be available at the door, it would be advisable that you purchase your tickets by Tuesday Evening, February 24, so Shirley can give an attendance number to The 3 Spot in advance.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Volunteer Positions Available For Next Year&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It is that time of year again! If you would like to take an active role (which I highly recommend) in the booster organization please let us know! It is an enriching and fulfilling experience. There are many Senior parents graduating this year that have done a fantastic job in their roles as booster committee members or booster officers. Please consider getting involved to help continue our fine tradition of excellence! The directors truly cannot do it without us and our children are the ones that benefit!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Below is a list of the major openings for next year. Let us know if you have any questions, we will be happy to assist!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Banquets and Hospitality &lt;span class="badge"&gt;2 People&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Bus Chaperones &lt;span class="badge"&gt;1 Person&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Air Show &lt;span class="badge"&gt;2-3 People&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Concession Stand &lt;span class="badge"&gt;3 People&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Market Day&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In addition, the Executive Board has members who will retire as their children will not be in the band next year. If you are interested in any board positions please contact me. It’s so important that we all contribute so the band can continue its great tradition going forward.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;See you all next Saturday!!!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Holly Michalke&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2015-02-21 07:02:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2015-02-21 08:02:25</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>band-boosters-news-fundraiser-volunteer-postings</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>8fccb9f0-4993-489b-b231-4593baca27ee</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
    <category>fa6094d0-c8e0-4964-8deb-b6349a6dd281</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>