<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>NRMB Spring Easter Seals Event</title>
  <description>Spring Easter Seals Update - Event date is April 28-29
 Spring Has Sprung!
 
With only one week left</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spring Easter Seals Update - Event date is April 28-29&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;h3&gt;Spring Has Sprung!&lt;/h3&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;With only one week left until Easter, How well did you do with the 40 bags in 40 weeks challenge? It's ok, if you haven't started yet because honestly, I have just recently given up some of my winter clothes and soft goods (gotta love Cleveland weather!).&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;This is such a great event and an excellent fundraiser for the band! The timing is perfect for spring cleaning. Please join us! Collect your soft goods and bring them to State Band Contest on April 28-29 between Friday, 4-8:30 pm and Saturday, 9 am -1:30 pm. Since it was so successful at The holiday concerts, we will be parking the Easter Seals truck right outside the PAC again!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;h3&gt; NRECEPTA Resale Event&lt;/h3&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ALSO COLLECTING UNSOLD ITEMS FROM THE NRECPTA EVENT ON SATURDAY, APRIL 22 AND NEED 5-10 PEOPLE/STUDENTS TO COLLECT THESE GOODS between 11 and 2. It is also a great way to collect service hours, help the vendors, help Easter Seals and our band program! It is a win-win-win-win! Come join me!&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;EASTER SEALS IS ALSO a fundraiser within a fundraiser! Support the band by volunteering your services for State Band contest and bring your donated items to the Easter Seals truck to further support the band and an amazing cause! Click on the links to hop on the bandwagon! &lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Share this event on all your social media to further spread this upcoming event. Any questions, please contact Holly ‪216-926-8836. &lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-easter1"&gt;Volunteer here:
EASTER SEALS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;State Band Contest Fundraiser&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please volunteer your time - You will still be able to see your concert band member perform!  Any questions, please contact Amanda Kost at ‪440-864-6543 or by email: &lt;a href="mailto:memandy@ameritech.net"&gt;memandy@ameritech.net&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/805054EAFA729A02-omea1"&gt;Volunteer here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

 </content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2017-04-11 18:04:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2017-04-11 18:39:05</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>nrmb-spring-easter-seals-event</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>6d8a90b6-376d-4bfc-b998-4281154f0d7b</category>
    <category>04fc31b2-00cd-4a3d-ae40-f49af9a917eb</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>