<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<page>
  <title>Volunteer Now!</title>
  <description>Volunteer Here!
We need many volunteers throughout the year to help support and promote our band and</description>
  <content>&lt;h3&gt;Volunteer Here!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We need many volunteers throughout the year to help support and promote our band and its students. Many of these volunteer activities raise money that goes directly towards uniform upkeep and replacement, instrument upkeep and replacement, trip expenses, scholarships, and so much more. The links after an activity will take you to signup genius where you can find more information and sign up. Activities are listed in chronological order, from late summer until spring!&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;h3&gt;Air Show&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Airshow is one of our largest fund raisers. The Cleveland Air Show at Burke Lakefront airport over the Labor Day weekend. We will need many volunteers to work for one day to sell tickets (8 am to 5 pm). Lunch for each worker and parking are included. Workers need to be 14 years or older so students can volunteer with their parents. Friends and family are also welcome to help out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944a5ae2fa4ff2-20172" class="cta-purple buzz-out"&gt;Volunteer for Air Show&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Marching Band Uniform Committee&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This committee works with the Marching Band Uniform Chairs. We need volunteers to help distribute the marching band uniform (jacket, pants, hats, garment bags, etc.) during evenings in late July or early August. The Marching Band Uniform committee also collects the marching band uniforms after the season is over in the late fall. If it is a trip year, the committee may also be called upon to help get uniforms ready before the trip and help collect them and put them away after the trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Band Photo Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boosters make and sell buttons with each student’s picture, as well as the band logo, contest logo, etc. We need volunteers to help take pictures and organize students on picture day, take orders for and sell the buttons at Parent Preview Night and Band Fest, make the buttons, and distribute the buttons at the first home game. If you have a camera and are willing to take pictures please note that in the comments box.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944a5ae2fa4ff2-20171" class="cta-purple buzz-out"&gt;Volunteer for Band Photo Buttons&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 

&lt;h3&gt;Pit Crew/Band Truck&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Volunteers are responsible for packing up and transporting the marching band’s percussion instruments and field commander stands for every performance of the marching band season (football games and competitions) for both home and away events. This committee may be requested to assist the directors with the maintenance of the band room and instrument cases and help repair the trailer and golf cart as well as other miscellaneous duties. A FULL year commitment is required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Concession Stand Volunteers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Volunteers are needed to sell food and merchandise at the concession stands at home football games and Band Fest. Volunteers are needed to cashier, take orders, run orders, warm food and prep food. This activity is fun and a great way to work side-by-side with your band family members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944a5ae2fa4ff2-20176" class="cta-purple buzz-out"&gt;Volunteer for Concession Stand&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 

&lt;h3&gt;50/50 Raffle Ticket Sales&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Volunteers are needed to sell 50/50 raffle tickets in the stands at home football games (until half time) and Band Fest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944a5ae2fa4ff2-20173" class="cta-purple buzz-out"&gt;Volunteer for 50/50 Raffle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 

&lt;h3&gt;Chaperones&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Volunteers accompany/chaperone band students on North Royalton school buses to a variety of events throughout the year: away football games, marching band competitions, and concert band competitions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944a5ae2fa4ff2-20175" class="cta-purple buzz-out"&gt;Volunteer for Chaperones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Fruit Sale&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This committee supports the annual fall sale of Florida fruit. The fruit sale is a one day, door to door, sales event held in mid-September. The order forms are also distributed to the band students at school for them to sell to their families, friends, and neighbors. The fruit is delivered in early December. Volunteers are needed to help distribute packets, unload the fruit from the delivery truck, prepare and sort the fruit and help distribute the fruit. This is a great fundraiser for the band and many people really look forward to their annual box of fresh Florida fruit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944a5ae2fa4ff2-20179" class="cta-purple buzz-out"&gt;Volunteer for Fruit Sale&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Band Fest&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The annual Festival of Bands is a terrific event where some of the great area marching bands can showcase their competition or non-competition shows. It is usually the first performance of our band’s contest show. We need extra help with concessions, ushering, program sales, ticket sales and ticket collection.&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944a5ae2fa4ff2-20174" class="cta-purple buzz-out"&gt;Volunteer for Band Fast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 

&lt;h3&gt;Hospitality Committee&lt;/h3&gt;This committee assists the chairpersons with events where refreshments are provided. Volunteers are needed for three events: Senior Band Parent Night in early October, the Marching Band Concert at the end of football season and the Band Awards Banquet in May. Volunteers set up the tables and help set up and serve food (desserts and drinks for Senior Band Night and Marching Band Concert and a catered dinner for Band Awards).&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944a5ae2fa4ff2-20177" class="cta-purple buzz-out"&gt;Volunteer for Senior Band Night&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944a5ae2fa4ff2-20178" class="cta-gold buzz-out"&gt;Volunteer for Marching Band Concert&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944a5ae2fa4ff2-201710"&gt;Senior Band Night Bakery Donations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080944a5ae2fa4ff2-201711"&gt;Senior Band Night Beverage Donations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Concert Band Uniform Committee&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This committee works with the Concert Band Uniform Chairs. The concert band uniform committee distributes the concert band dresses and tuxes in late fall and collects them at the end of the school year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Raffle Fundraiser&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This fundraiser is a special evening out for band booster supporters involving dinner, games of chance, and basket raffles. It occurs during the spring. The Raffle Committee starts planning for the evening event after the marching band season ends. Volunteers are needed for promotions/marketing, donation solicitation/follow up, basket assembly, set up, help during the event, recap and thanks/acknowledgements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Concert Band - State Contest – April 28 &amp;amp; 29&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We host the OMEA State Contest in the spring. We need extra volunteers to work in shifts Friday and Saturday. They act as information guides, door keepers, stage crew to setup and move chairs and stands, judge’s assistants, and more.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <keywords />
  <slug>volunteer-now</slug>
  <parent>00445e81-2b6e-4ccf-9b8f-c829b2bc4084</parent>
  <isfrontpage>False</isfrontpage>
  <showinlist>True</showinlist>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <datecreated>2017-08-22 21:08:00</datecreated>
  <datemodified>2017-10-02 20:21:16</datemodified>
</page>