<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<page>
  <title>About the North Royalton Band Program</title>
  <description>About the North Royalton Marching Band</description>
  <content>
&lt;p&gt;The North Royalton Band program has a long-standing tradition of being one of the finest band/music programs in the State of Ohio. The North Royalton High School Band Program is proud to be the largest student organization on campus with over 280 members. &amp;nbsp;The Band Program incorporates a competitive corps-style marching band, 4 Concert Bands, 2 Jazz Bands, Pit Orchestra, Winter Drumline, Winterguard, Winter Dance Team, Brass Choir, Woodwind Choir, and Saxophone Choir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are numerous benefits to being a part of the high school band including:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Self-discipline&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What teen doesn't need self-discipline these days? A rigorous practice schedule during band practice at school, after-school rehearsals, weeks of band camp in the summer before school starts and individual practices require a lot of self-discipline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Teamwork&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While it is very important for students to hone their individual skills on their own instruments, the band moves as a unit during their "show." When one person is off, it throws off others and messes up formations. So, the teens must work together, watching others, and maintaining time and step along with their music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Commitment&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Band is not a "blow-off" class. It is hard work. It can also be expensive. Being in the marching band requires a commitment on the part of the student to practice, show up for rehearsals and do his best every day. Aside from that, it's a commitment for parents, too, both financially and time-wise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Multiple-skills training&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Performing in the marching band promotes a lot of skills. Students must have good eye-hand coordination, a sense of rhythm and critical thinking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Friends for life&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being in the band assures students of a group with whom they are familiar. They may not be close friends with everyone but it is a stable circle of students with a common interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Competition&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is both individual and group competition in band. Individuals may try out for position within their instrument section and become section leader. There are also individual competitions within school districts for students to receive honors. The band competes as a group, as well. What a sense of pride for students when the band scores well in a competition!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Appreciation of the Arts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Studies have shown that students who are involved in the arts (music, art) exhibit a higher level of math proficiency than those not involved in the arts. They score better on standardized tests and are more well-rounded academically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These skills are all beneficial for teens and can be used to succeed later in life.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <keywords>About the Band</keywords>
  <slug>about-the-band</slug>
  <parent>c17ec5bc-2c27-468b-acf6-5e30d22c774c</parent>
  <isfrontpage>False</isfrontpage>
  <showinlist>True</showinlist>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <datecreated>2014-04-23 21:04:00</datecreated>
  <datemodified>2014-05-17 14:55:48</datemodified>
</page>