<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<page>
  <title>Volunteer Needs</title>
  <description>Volunteer Needs</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;While we always need volunteers, from time to time, our need is urgent to help support a near term event or staff a critical volunteer activity. If you can help out, please contact us per the information below.  Thanks so much!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr class="clearfix col-md-12"&gt;
&lt;dl class="def-list"&gt;
        &lt;dt class="col-sm-4 col-md-4"&gt;&lt;dfn&gt;State Concert Contest at North Royalton High School&lt;/dfn&gt;&lt;span&gt;(April 25/26, 2014)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
        &lt;dd class="col-sm-8 col-md-8"&gt;Support the State Band Contest in April at the NR high school with the following activities:
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;4 volunteers needed to assists the bands in Pac Friday and Saturday&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;4 volunteers needed to assist bands in Gym 2 Friday and Saturday&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;2 adults needed in the office both days&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;We will also need between 10 and 12 adults per day to help with concessions&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;

            &lt;p&gt;Expect Friday to go from 4:00 pm until 11:30 pm and Saturday from 8:00 am until 3:30 pm. We will ask people to arrive thirty minutes before the start to get areas ready. This is a major fundraiser for us, so please consider volunteering. &lt;/p&gt;
           &lt;p&gt;Contact Rich Hrin, &lt;a href="tel+440-668-7428"&gt;440-668-7428&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="mailto:hrinmor@sbcglobal.net"&gt;hrinmor@sbcglobal.net&lt;/a&gt; to volunteer.&lt;/p&gt; 

        &lt;/dd&gt;
        &lt;hr class="clearfix col-md-12"&gt;
        &lt;dt class="col-sm-4 col-md-4"&gt;&lt;dfn&gt;Air Show co-chairperson&lt;/dfn&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
        &lt;dd class="col-sm-8 col-md-8"&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will help organize the volunteers that support the annual Cleveland Air Show held over the Labor Day weekend at Burke Lakefront airport. Volunteers sell tickets and assist with parking and receive lunch and free parking. &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Contact Rich Hrin, &lt;a href="tel+4406687428"&gt;440-668-7428&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="mailto:hrinmor@sbcglobal.net"&gt;hrinmor@sbcglobal.net&lt;/a&gt; or Kathy Pishnery, &lt;a href="tel+440-652-6263"&gt;440-652-6263&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="mailto:kathypish@aol.com"&gt;kathypish@aol.com&lt;/a&gt; for more information and/or to volunteer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/dd&gt;
        &lt;hr class="clearfix col-md-12"&gt;
        &lt;dt class="col-sm-4 col-md-4"&gt;&lt;dfn&gt;Car Raffle co-chairperson&lt;/dfn&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
        &lt;dd class="col-sm-8 col-md-8"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This committee is formed only in the event that a car is donated to the High School. Volunteers are responsible for the planning, distribution, and collection of the car raffle tickets and the funds. It involves a weekly commitment during the program. The committee will make arrangements with the band director to set up a distribution/collection table in the band room. This may involve being in the band room during afternoon or late evening hours before and after band practice. At the end of the fundraiser all unsold tickets or money must be returned. Funds support the general fund.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;Contact Jeff or Kris Paulus, &lt;a href="mailto:jeff@pauluseng.com"&gt;jeff@pauluseng.com&lt;/a&gt;/&lt;a href="mailto:kmp@pauluseng.com"&gt;kmp@pauluseng.com&lt;/a&gt; or Rich Hrin, &lt;a href="tel+440-668-7428"&gt;440-668-7428&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="mailto:hrinmor@sbcglobal.net"&gt;hrinmor@sbcglobal.net&lt;/a&gt; for more information and/or to volunteer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/dd&gt;
        &lt;hr class="clearfix col-md-12"&gt;
        &lt;dt class="col-sm-4 col-md-4"&gt;&lt;dfn&gt;Visiting Band Hospitality&lt;/dfn&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
        &lt;dd class="col-sm-8 col-md-8"&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will help coordinate with the band director to arrange for refreshments for visiting bands during football games.&lt;/p&gt;
             &lt;p&gt;Contact Rich Hrin, &lt;a href="tel+440-668-7428"&gt;440-668-7428&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="mailto:hrinmor@sbcglobal.net"&gt;hrinmor@sbcglobal.net&lt;/a&gt; or Martha Custer, &lt;a href="mailto:marthalcuster@sbcglobal.net"&gt;marthalcuster@sbcglobal.net&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/dd&gt;
        &lt;hr class="clearfix col-md-12"&gt;
        &lt;dt class="col-sm-4 col-md-4"&gt;&lt;dfn&gt;Raffle Co-chairperson&lt;/dfn&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
        &lt;dd class="col-sm-8 col-md-8"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Help organize and coordinate the annual Raffle fundraiser held during the Spring, which consists of a evening out for band booster supporters that includes food, drinks, basket raffles and games of chance. This committee starts planning for the evening event in November right after the marching band season ends. Volunteers work on this program periodically until the event date which is usually in March or April. Volunteer Categories include Promotions/Marketing, Donation Solicitation, Basket Assembly, Event Set, Event Help, and Post-event help. &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Contact Rich Hrin, &lt;a href="tel+440-668-7428"&gt;440-668-7428&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="mailto:hrinmor@sbcglobal.net"&gt;hrinmor@sbcglobal.net&lt;/a&gt; or Carol Shivley Mizes, &lt;a href="mailto:carolcola4@gmail.com"&gt;carolcola4@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/dd&gt;
                &lt;/dl&gt;</content>
  <keywords>Volunteer Needs</keywords>
  <slug>volunteer-needs</slug>
  <parent>00445e81-2b6e-4ccf-9b8f-c829b2bc4084</parent>
  <isfrontpage>False</isfrontpage>
  <showinlist>True</showinlist>
  <ispublished>False</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <datecreated>2014-04-19 09:04:00</datecreated>
  <datemodified>2016-08-27 06:54:29</datemodified>
</page>