<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<page>
  <title>North Royalton Band Directors</title>
  <description>North Royalton Band Directors</description>
  <content>&lt;h2&gt;David Vitale&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure class="pull-right"&gt;
&lt;img src="/FILES%2f2014%2f05%2fdavid-viatale.jpg.axdx" alt="David Vitale" class="img-responsive img-thumbnail"&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;David Vitale&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;David has been a Band Director with the North Royalton City Schools since 2002 and is currently serving as the Director of Bands where he directs the Marching Band, Wind Ensemble, Freshman Band, Jazz Band I, Jazz Lab Band, as well as the Brass Choir, Woodwind Choir, and Saxophone Choir. The Marching Band and Concert Ensembles under his direction have received numerous Superior Ratings at OMEA Adjudicated events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to his directing responsibilities, he also serves as the instructor for Music Theory and Music Technology as well as the marching band show designer. Mr. Vitale is an Alumnus of North Royalton High School (1998). He earned his Bachelor of Music Education degree from Bowling Green State University (2002) where he earned the Mark Kelly award for Music Education. He earned his Master of Music Degree at BGSU as well in 2005. During his graduate studies, he worked with the BGSU concert bands and The BGSU Falcon Marching Band where he assisted with music arranging and drill writing for the ensemble. His master’s thesis, “Characteristics of Exemplary Marching Band Directors and Their Programs,” has been referenced and cited in doctoral dissertations throughout the country. Marching band shows that he designed have consistently earned titles of “Best General Effect” and “Best Visual Effect” at OMEA Marching Band Adjudicated events. He is an active composer and arranger, is published through Ludwig Masters Publications, and currently has repertoire on the OMEA Solo &amp;amp; Ensemble Required List. He has been recognized by the state of Ohio with the “Master Teacher” award and he is very active with OMEA where he serves as an adjudicator for Marching Band and Large Group Band Adjudicated Events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2013, David Vitale was selected to serve as president-elect for the Ohio Music Education Association District 4. OMEA is the third-largest of the 52 federated state affiliates of The National Association for Music Education. OMEA is divided into 17 geographic districts and District 4 covers half of Cuyahoga County and all of Lorain County. It is a six-year role, moving from two years as president-elect, two years as president and then two years as past-president. The president of each OMEA district is responsible for all activities throughout the year for that district and attending all state board meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Christopher Burdick&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure class="pull-right"&gt;
&lt;img src="/FILES%2f2014%2f05%2fchristopher-burdick.jpg.axdx" alt="Christopher Burdick" class="img-responsive img-thumbnail"&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Christopher Burdick&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chris has been a Band Director with the North Royalton City Schools since 1994. He directs the North Royalton Middle School Sixth &amp;amp; Eighth Grade Bands, North Royalton High School Symphonic Band and Musical Pit Orchestra. He is the brass instructor for the Fifth Graders and assists with the Seventh Grade Bands as well as the award winning North Royalton High School Marching Band. The concert bands under his direction have received Superior Ratings at OMEA Adjudicated District Events every year since 1996 and 10 of the past 12 years at the State level. Mr. Burdick is originally from Western New York and graduated from Hamburg High School in 1988. He earned his Bachelor’s degree in 1992 from The Crane School of Music at SUNY Potsdam. It was here he received the Julia Crane Award; voted on by the faculty as most likely to succeed as a music director. Mr. Burdick was a graduate assistant at Kent State and member of the Kent Faculty Brass Quintet while earning his Master’s in Trumpet Performance in 1994. He was nominated for a Cooperating Teacher of the Year award from Kent’s School of Education. Mr. Burdick has served as a guest conductor and clinician around Northeast Ohio most recently with the 2010 Medina County Middle School All-Star Band. He has performed and soloed with the Kent-Blossom Orchestra, The Sounds of Sousa Band and the North Royalton and Medina Community Bands. He and his wife Beth reside in North Royalton and have three children, Ryan, Brendan and Sarah.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Mike Nary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure class="pull-right"&gt;
&lt;img src="/FILES%2f2014%2f05%2fmike-nary.jpg.axdx" alt="Mike Nary" class="img-responsive img-thumbnail"&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Mike Nary&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mike has been a Band Director with the North Royalton City Schools since 2010. He directs the Seventh Grade Gold Band and High School Concert Band. Both organizations have received Superior ratings at OMEA events under his baton. Teaching at both the North Royalton Middle School and High Schools, Mr. Nary is privileged to teach students in grades 5-12. Mr. Nary previously served as Director of Bands for Garfield Heights City Schools from 2008-2010. Mike is a 2007 graduate of The Ohio State University where he earned his Bachelor’s degree in Music Education and was awarded student teacher of the year (2007). Mike had the rare privilege of dotting the “i” during the 2008 BCS National Championship game played in the Superdome in New Orleans. As an alumnus of North Royalton, Mr. Nary takes great pride in giving back to an organization that gave him so much. Mike has been married to his wife Katie since 2010 and their son Connor was born in November 2012.
&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <keywords>Directors</keywords>
  <slug>directors</slug>
  <parent>c17ec5bc-2c27-468b-acf6-5e30d22c774c</parent>
  <isfrontpage>False</isfrontpage>
  <showinlist>True</showinlist>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <datecreated>2014-04-19 09:04:00</datecreated>
  <datemodified>2014-05-17 14:58:10</datemodified>
</page>