<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<page>
  <title>Privacy Policy</title>
  <description>Privacy Policy</description>
  <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;North Royalton Band Boosters will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
          
    &lt;p&gt;Thank you for visiting the North Royalton Band Boosters web site. The North Royalton Band Boosters are committed to protecting your privacy and will collect no personal information about you unless you choose to provide that information to us. Such information is securely stored within the North Royalton Band Boosters private network. Some information may also be shared with North Royalton Band Boosters business partners and other organizations and individuals with which the North Royalton Band Boosters have established a strategic alliance or other contractual relationship. The primary purpose behind the sharing of information is to better the services being provided to you by the North Royalton Band Boosters and by the organizations and individuals for which the North Royalton Band Boosters has established contractual relationships. Information will also be used to improve North Royalton Band Boosters marketing, and charitable efforts.&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;h2&gt;How we handle information about your visit to our site&lt;/h2&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;If you read or download information, we automatically collect and store:&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;the requested web page&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;the domain from which you access the Internet (e.g. wowway.com)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;the date and time you access our site&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;status of the request (e.g. success or failure)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;the type and version of your web browser (Firefox, Explorer, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;the operating system (Windows, Mac, Unix, etc.) of the machine running the web browser&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;/ul&gt;
          &lt;h3&gt;Links &amp;amp; Disclaimer&lt;/h3&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Our web site has links to many other organizations with their permission. Upon leaving the North Royalton Band Boosters web site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site. North Royalton Band Boosters is not responsible for the availability of the systems being linked to and these links are provided to you as a service for you to better understand the different business relationships that North Royalton Band Boosters has established.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <keywords>Privacy Policy</keywords>
  <slug>privacy-policy</slug>
  <parent>00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000</parent>
  <isfrontpage>False</isfrontpage>
  <showinlist>False</showinlist>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <datecreated>2014-04-30 21:04:00</datecreated>
  <datemodified>2014-05-15 21:09:13</datemodified>
</page>